<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Ruby Pink Romance</title>
	<subtitle>Classy smut for classy people</subtitle>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/"/>
	<updated>2024-10-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Ruby Pink</name>
		<email>hello@rubypinkromance.com</email>
	</author>
  <icon>https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rubypink.jpg</icon>
	<entry>
		<title>Delivery Night</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/delivery-night/"/>
		<published>2024-10-31T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-10-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/delivery-night/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="horror" />
    <category term="vampire" />
    <category term="succubus" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="swallow" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/delivery-night-rWqyjOIRCd-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Jax, my man!” Gio looked up from assembling a pizza as I walked in the back door. “What are you doing here? I thought Omar was driving tonight?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He asked me to cover his shift,” I replied. “Said he caught something from his roommate.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, well, I’ve got an order about ready to go.” He held up the receipt. “Looks like you’re heading to the Pearl district.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, I hate parking over there,” I frowned. “Wait, what’s the name on the order?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh… Murray? Looks like they’re a regular. Same order every week, like clockwork. Why, you know them or something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, but get a load of this. After I said I’d cover his shift, Omar got all serious. Said if I get a delivery in the Pearl for Murray, don’t go in, even if they invite me. He was real insistent.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Murray sounds like a stoner’s name.” Gio chuckled as he pulled the pizza from the oven, dropping it in a box and quickly slicing it. “Dude probably invited him in once and talked his ear off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Knowing Omar,” I grinned, “more likely it’s some lonely housewife.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ha!” He lapsed into a low-budget porn star impression. “Oh no, mister! I don’t have any money, but maybe I can pay you some other way?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fingers crossed, man,” I laughed, slipping the box into a hot bag and walking out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behind the strip mall was a small parking lot. It exited to the street on one side, and on the other was a narrow alley between two buildings. The moon was hidden behind a heavy layer of clouds, and the parking lot light flickered out as I walked to my car, plunging me into darkness. Cursing, I pulled out my phone to turn on the flashlight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I did, a car turned down the side street, and its headlights briefly sliced through the parking lot. For just a second, I thought I saw a thin, pale figure in the alley. Probably a bum, I figured, as I unlocked the car and dropped the pizza on the passenger seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The engine struggled to start, complaining and straining. “Come on,” I grumbled. I’d just spent my last paycheck at the mechanic, and they swore they’d fixed the starter. For a second, the motor turned over, then sputtered and died. Before it did, the headlights caught that person in the alley again, closer than before. It looked like a woman, with short dark hair, staring right at me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I peered over the dash, but there wasn’t enough light to see down the alley. Shrugging, I tried the key again, and this time the engine started. The headlights flooded the parking lot and alley with light, and there was no one there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drive to the Pearl was boring, but I kept seeing some big fucking bat flying overhead. I’ve never seen bats in the city before. Plenty of rats and pigeons, but never bats. They look weird as shit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I finally found a place to park just a few blocks from the delivery address, so I felt pretty lucky when I started walking. This part of town is full of fancy bars and restaurants, so I was walking past lots of people having a fun night out. The address turned out to be an upscale apartment building. I buzzed their number, and a lady’s voice answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thirteenth floor, come on up,” she said, buzzing me in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the lobby was a wall of mailboxes, a doorway to the stairs, and an elevator. I pushed the button and waited, then I got that creeping sensation on the back of my neck, like someone was looking at me. I turned around, expecting to see someone looking in the window, but almost jumped out of my skin because there was someone standing right behind me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry!” She apologized, holding up her keys. “Didn’t mean to scare you. I came in behind you. Guess you didn’t hear me?” She had pale skin, short-cropped black hair, and dark eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah,” I laughed nervously. “I guess not.” I was sure no one had come in after me. I hadn’t heard the door or anything, and I would have noticed if she slipped in behind me. Weird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She smiled and rocked on her heels, looking at the floor readout above the elevator. I shook my head, trying to shake off an odd feeling that she was the woman I saw in the alley. But, no, that was just my mind playing tricks on me. There wasn’t anyone in the alley, remember? Besides, that was across town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the elevator finally arrived, I stepped in and pressed the button for the thirteenth floor. She followed me in, standing in the back. I looked at her, waiting to hear what button to push. “Same floor,” she remarked. Her grin seemed strangely ominous, and I tried not to shiver as I turned my back on her. Although I couldn’t see her reflection in the buffed metal walls of the elevator, I could feel her eyes on the back of my neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I left the elevator quickly, telling myself I wasn’t afraid or anything, I was just trying to deliver the pizza before it got cold. Her footsteps seemed to follow me down the hall. This was ridiculous. I couldn’t be afraid of some random woman who lived here. I took a deep breath as I approached the door and knocked, wondering who would answer that Omar had felt the need to warn me about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to suppress a grin when a voluptuous woman in a silk robe opened the door. Her hair was dyed pink, with her nails painted to match. She smiled seductively and stepped aside, swinging the door wide, inviting me in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I, um, I’m just here with your pizza,” I stammered. Gio was never gonna believe this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I could form a more coherent response, the woman from the elevator stepped around me into the apartment. She kissed the robed woman on the lips and sauntered in, kicking off her shoes and removing her jacket. My cheeks burned from how badly I’d misread the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fucking Omar, I laughed to myself. He made such a big deal of not going in, and then it turned out to just be a couple of lesbians! He must have known I’d jump to the wrong conclusion. I should have known better, this is totally the kind of prank he likes to pull. I’d have to get him back good for this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on in,” she said, patting her robe theatrically to show she had no pockets. “My purse is in the kitchen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stepped in, looking around as she shut the door behind me. The apartment was pretty nice, though all their furniture was old stuff. Probably instagram types, I thought, posting videos about restoring antiques and shit. She led me through to the kitchen, where I put the pizza on the island as she picked up her purse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Eve, I’m putting on some music,” called the dark-haired woman from the next room. “What do you want?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Portishead,” she called back, before asking me with a smile, “Where’s Omar?” There was a twinkle in her eyes that made me wonder if she was in on the joke. “He’s our usual delivery guy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sick,” I nodded. “He called me to cover his shift.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm. Are you new? I don’t think I’ve seen you before.” She licked her lips. “I’m sure I’d remember if I had.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No mistaking that. She was definitely flirting. I shot a nervous glance toward the other room, where the dark-haired woman was standing by the stereo. Slow, throbbing bass rumbled from a large set of speakers, and she started swaying in place, eyes closed, vibing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh, normally work the day shift.” I turned back to the robed woman, who was leaning on the other side of the island, rummaging through her purse. Her robe hung open just enough to tease the curve of her breasts. I swallowed, and tried to look away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, that explains it. Mina and I are night owls.” She chuckled, as though she’d said something funny, and pushed her purse away. “What’s your name?” Her fingernails absent-mindedly trailed down the lapel of her robe, drawing my attention to the way her nipples raised the thin fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jackson,” I mumbled, tearing my eyes away with some difficulty. “I’m Jackson.” She bit her lip and slowly walked around the island toward me. Her robe was coming loose. My heart was pounding in my chest. “Um, is it hot in here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took a step backward and yelped when I bumped into Mina, who was suddenly standing behind me. “Seems fine to me,” she growled in my ear. I tried to move away, but she put a hand on my shoulder, and I felt compelled to stay where I was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you think, Mina?” Eve purred as she sauntered closer. I caught a glimpse of her thigh as her robe parted. Her skin was darker than Mina’s, a rich copper, gleaming as if she’d recently rubbed herself down with oil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’s not our usual order,” Mina grumbled, pressing her face to my neck and inhaling deeply, as if trying to decide if she liked me based on how I smelled. My pulse was pounding in my ears. I felt sudden relief that I had showered before work. “What happened to Omar?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They’re all out. Tonight, we got &lt;em&gt;Jackson&lt;/em&gt;,” Eve replied, emphasizing my name. “Seems a waste to send him back.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hrm,” Mina conceded, grabbing a handful of my hair and pulling my head back to expose more of my neck. I shivered as I felt her lips brush against my skin. They were chilled, as though she’d just come in from the cold, though it was a warm night. “You &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; always telling me to try new things.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s the spirit.” Eve ran her hands over my chest, and I couldn’t help but gasp as I felt a powerful surge of lust. Confusingly, it was mixed with a sense of dread. She leaned into me, and the heat of her body made me want to tear off our clothes, to feel her skin on mine. Her breasts were soft against my chest, and I felt my cock swelling to life against her hip. She moved as if to kiss me, but at the last second swerved to kiss Mina over my shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I shivered, sandwiched between these two women, completely overwhelmed. It was all happening so quickly. My mind swirled with a fantasy of falling into bed with them, writhing and groping, thrusting and moaning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But also, some primal part of my brain was screaming that I was in danger. As badly as I wanted to stay here and let them have their way with me, I was struggling not to turn and run as far and fast as I could.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As if sensing my fear, Mina’s hand tightened on my shoulder as they broke their kiss. The music grew louder, the throbbing bass filling my brain and drowning out any thought of resisting. Eve pulled away, dancing sensuously for the two of us. Her robe fell open, and my cock strained against my jeans at the sight of her body. Large, dark nipples crowned her breasts, firm and erect, begging for my mouth. A trail of fine hair led my eyes downward from her belly button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look at her,” Mina groaned in my ear. “Isn’t she incredible?” I realized that Eve’s dance was affecting Mina the same as me. She released my shoulder and wrapped her arms around me, her pelvis grinding against me from behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have no idea how lucky you are, Jackson. Men have offered fortunes for the privilege of seeing Eve dance.” Abruptly, she grabbed my cock, nails sharp even through my jeans, and I stifled a cry of alarm. “Men have &lt;em&gt;died&lt;/em&gt; for a single night of ecstasy between her thighs.” She eased her grip, teasing her fingers along the length of my shaft. “What will you give up, I wonder?” I shuddered, eyes locked on Eve, barely resisting the urge to hump against her hand like a horny teenager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come dance with me,” Eve said, moving toward the living room, slipping out of her robe as she went. When Mina released me, I trailed after Eve, unaware of anything beyond the sway of her hips, the swell of her bottom. Without thinking, I began to remove my clothes, leaving them in a trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We came together in front of the speakers, moving as one. I’ve never been a particularly good dancer, but she guided me. Our bodies entwined, a delicious thrill as the heat of her body met mine. Her soft curves undulated at my touch. My cock throbbed, hard as steel, rubbing against her well-oiled skin. Every touch sent a shiver of pleasure through my body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our lips met in a kiss that seemed to be part of her dance. I held her breasts and gasped as she sucked on my bottom lip. Her hands roamed my body, showing me how to move with her. I felt as if she was speaking a language I’d never learned, but as long as she was here, I could almost understand it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unable to resist, I lowered my head and wrapped my lips around her nipple. She moaned and rolled her hips, tangling her fingers in my hair, without ever stopping the dance. She guided me to her other breast, gasping as I flicked my tongue. My cock throbbed against her soft skin, and I almost choked with arousal as I kissed my way down her chest and stomach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found myself on my knees, worshipping her. She moved in circles around me, and I leaned after her, trying to get closer. I yearned for more, but she stayed just out of reach, driving me wild, teasing me, and stoking my hunger for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she finally stepped closer and allowed me to bury my face between her thighs, I felt a ripple of gratification roll down my spine. She’d judged me worthy and graced me with a taste of paradise. My tongue slipped easily between her lips, slick with arousal. She rolled her hips in time to the music, letting me lick deeper each time. Her taste filled my mouth, the flavor of pure lust, better than anything I’d ever experienced. I moaned happily, body crackling with desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I became aware that Mina was standing behind me. She was leaning over me to kiss Eve deeply. Her skin was cold against my back, though perhaps that was just in contrast to the astonishing heat of Eve’s body. I could hear the passion of their kiss as Eve danced against my mouth. I could have stayed there all night, but suddenly Mina grabbed me by the hair and pulled me away with a snarl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sputtered in protest as she forced me to turn around, still on my knees. She had also removed her clothes, and her skin was shockingly pale compared to Eve’s. Her breasts were smaller, with pale nipples puckered to hard little points. She spread her thighs, revealing a startlingly pink set of lips that she yanked me towards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shivered as my lips met hers, still covered in Eve’s juices, as if using me to transfer her arousal. Even her pussy was cold. I licked deeply, trying to warm her up, to pleasure her as I’d done for Eve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mina used me more forcefully, tugging my hair hard, positioning me the way she wanted. She bucked her hips, grinding herself against my face, using me for pleasure. For a moment, doubt filled my head, the haze of lust falling away, replaced by fear. What was I doing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then I felt Eve’s hand on my back, and my concerns melted away, replaced by a warm wave of desire. Mina moaned as I sucked on her firm little clit, and slipped a finger inside. Eve’s legs were hot against my back as she leaned forward to wrap her lips around Mina’s nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mina gasped and tensed as we both focused our efforts on her. She rocked against my face, gripping my hair. “More,” she growled. I slipped another finger inside, her pussy squeezing wetly around them. “More,” she repeated. Eve purred, swaying in time to the music, pulling more of Mina’s small breast into the heat of her mouth. “Oh fuck, more!” She tugged my hair harder until I tapped another finger on her back door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“More, more, more,” she demanded. I pushed my finger harder against her tightly clenched ass, slowly working it inside. She groaned, and I felt her squeeze my fingers, wetness dripping down my arm. Urgently, I started fucking her in time with Eve’s movements. Mina groaned with each thrust, and Eve moaned along with her, seeming just as aroused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s it,” she growled as her body tensed. “Keep doing that.” My cock throbbed desperately. I had the taste of two women in my mouth. I wondered if she would let me fuck her if I made her cum. How would it feel to push my cock inside her? I imagined switching back and forth between Mina’s tight pussy and Eve’s soft cunt, savoring the contrast between them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” Mina snarled. “Fuck! I’m cumming!” With one final thrust against my mouth, her insides clenched so tightly around my fingers it almost hurt. Then she shoved me away, forcefully, shuddering as my fingers slipped out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fell hard onto my back, grateful for the thick rug as my head bounced off the floor. Before I had a chance to say anything, Eve kneeled and kissed me deeply, licking Mina’s cum from my lips. I gasped at the absurd rush of lust I felt when her lips touched me. If I didn’t know better, I’d swear her touch was getting me high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unable to resist, I wrapped my hand around my shaft and started stroking, moaning into Eve’s mouth. She purred happily and broke our kiss to watch, squeezing her breast and pulling her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” I gasped, looking up at her. I wanted so badly to fuck her. She winked and gestured for me to look down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did, and a cold wave of panic crashed over me. Crouched over my legs was Mina, but something was different about her. She looked predatory, licking her lips and panting hungrily. I let go of my cock and started trying to scrabble away from her, but bumped into Eve’s legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I warned you,” Mina said with a cruel smile. “What will you give up? No one gets to dance with my wife for free, mortal.” Her teeth suddenly looked very sharp. “And I’m so hungry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” I practically sobbed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shh,” Eve reassured me, gently caressing my chest. “Be still.” The stimulation made me shiver, and my cock twitched, but my brain was still flooded with terror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mina crawled forward, staring hungrily as my cock throbbed in time with my heartbeat. She opened her mouth and moved closer, brushing her lips over the tip and lightly dragging her teeth down the shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I moaned in horror as Eve continued to caress me and whisper soothingly. “Relax,” she breathed. “You made her cum, she’s in a good mood.” Mina’s eyes flashed dangerously. She didn’t look like she was in a good mood. She looked like she wanted to devour me. “I promise, she won’t drain you completely. &lt;em&gt;Will you&lt;/em&gt;, Mina?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mina hissed, but nodded in grudging agreement. “Fine, my love. For you, I’ll restrain myself.” Then she licked her lips, and I watched in horror as she opened her mouth to reveal two long, pointed teeth, which she promptly plunged into the side of my cock. Blood flowed freely for a moment before she wrapped her lips tightly around me, swallowing hungrily. I cried out, more from shock than pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not as bad as you thought, is it?” Eve murmured quietly in my ear. I nodded, my fear quickly melting away, replaced by a strange new form of arousal. “Vampire saliva is an incredibly potent aphrodisiac, almost as strong as anything I secrete.” My head was swimming, and I was barely able to understand her words. “Like, everyone knows a succubus will get you off, the best sex you ever had. And it’s true,” she said proudly. “But a vampire can, too. It’s an evolutionary trait…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She kept talking, but all my attention was on Mina. Her eyes were rolled back in pleasure, slurping greedily as my life flowed into her mouth. I found myself unbelievably turned on by the sight. Rationally, I knew I should be terrified, but instead my cock throbbed and pulsed for her. I gasped and reached down to touch her head, but she snarled at me, eyes flashing red.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t do that,” Eve giggled. “Here, you can touch me.” She swung her breasts over my head, and I moaned gratefully, squeezing and burying my face between them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Incredibly, I felt a familiar pressure building. Mina’s lips sucked urgently, tongue lashing against my skin. Eve’s breasts rubbed against my face, her skin hot and slick with sweat that seemed to soak into my pores, making my nerves buzz with arousal. I groaned desperately, knowing that any second my cock would erupt, spraying hot cum over Mina’s face. I wanted to, so badly, but I had a feeling that might go poorly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Eve,” I begged into her cleavage. “I need to cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, give it to me,” she purred, and quickly crawled down my side to wrap her lips around my swollen head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” I gasped, staring at the incredibly erotic sight of two women sucking my cock. Mina stared up at me through half-lidded eyes, still swallowing hungrily, and Eve met my gaze with an excited look. I felt my cock swell on her tongue as my climax crashed over me. “I’m cumming,” I blurted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eve moaned happily as I came hard, flooding her mouth with my cum. Mina, at last, released me and rocked back on her knees. I caught a quick glimpse of a trickle of blood trailing from two punctures before Eve took me deeper, pulling me hungrily into her throat. Mina laughed drunkenly, wiping blood from her lips as she watched Eve eagerly swallowing everything I could give her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that, I lay on the floor, gasping for breath and recovering as the two of them got to their feet and danced slowly together, kissing and caressing each other lovingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I finally stood up and pulled my clothes on, Eve walked me to the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here’s some cash for the delivery and a tip for your service. You’ll probably want to pick up some iron supplements. You’re a bit anemic now, but a good night of sleep will see you right as rain.” She gave me a quick kiss on the cheek and handed me the hot bag, giggling as she closed the door. “You can keep the pizza.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>What Happens on Treaty Station</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/treaty-station/"/>
		<published>2024-10-24T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-10-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/treaty-station/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="monster sex" />
    <category term="sci-fi" />
    <category term="aliens" />
    <category term="tentacles" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="anal" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/treaty-station-MnsqaNKy4_-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Ambassador Patel, we are approaching Treaty Station,” announced the ship’s AI pilot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you,” she responded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ship was a small one. Her position qualified her for something larger, with room for support staff, but she preferred this simpler, automated model. If asked, she explained it as a cost-saving measure. No need for support staff on a largely ceremonial annual visit. After all, she would chuckle knowingly, it wasn’t like the aliens were going to show up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Divya had a secret. The aliens &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; show up. Every year. This would be her seventh encounter with them. And she’d never told anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, they hadn’t always. In fact, that was why Divya had been able to gain the position. There was no real competition for ambassador to a race of aliens that wanted nothing to do with humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two generations ago, as humans spread outward from their solar system, the question of extraterrestrial life had finally been answered, in the least satisfying way possible, when human ships encountered nonhuman craft with no interest in us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They made no effort to communicate, and ignored all our attempts to do so. The only thing they did was hold position along an unseen boundary in space. Any attempt by human ships to approach was met by a non-hostile but assertive maneuver to block their way. Eventually, through trial and error, the border was mapped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not wanting to risk upsetting the only other sentient species we’d met, with who-knows-what capabilities, everyone had quickly agreed to respect their space. A station was constructed, and towed into position, directly along the boundary. It had no markings, only two docking ports, one facing human space, and the other facing them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A human ship docked, and the first designated ambassador came aboard, sitting at a large table with a copy of a treaty that basically said, “We’ll stay out of your way, but we’d like to get to know you better.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They had no idea how the aliens would react. Would they understand this was an invitation? Would they come aboard? &lt;em&gt;Could&lt;/em&gt; they come aboard? We didn’t even know if they could tolerate our atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Astonishingly, an alien ship did dock with the station. What happened next was broadcast live across all of human space, and is still, to this day, the most-watched recording of all time. The airlock opened, and a single alien entered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The creature most closely resembled a Portuguese man o’ war. That is, if a man o’ war walked upright on long squid-like tentacles, and had a mantle the size of a horse, with colors rippling along the dorsal ridge like a cuttlefish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It ducked through the airlock and approached the table. The ambassador stood, and recited a small speech that had been meticulously prepared by a crack team of scientists who were practically frothing at their mouths to define the new fields of xenobiology, xenosociology, and xenolinguistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The alien waited calmly as the ambassador spoke, tentacles rippling gently. When he finished speaking, it turned and left. That was the first and only time anyone saw the aliens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some eighty years later, Divya Patel was offered the no-longer desirable position of ambassador. She had an office in the UN, a small staff, an even smaller budget, and a single responsibility: Visit the treaty station every year, just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The previous ambassador, who had served for five years, shook her hand, and recommended she pack some books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Divya’s first visit to the station had been a surprise. She’d watched the first contact recording as much as anyone else, and thought she knew what to expect: A small room with a rather nice table of dark-stained wood, a UN flag hanging on the wall, and a single chair facing the alien’s door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, the table was pushed up against the wall under the flag to make room for a second-hand sofa on the opposite wall. There was also a cheap flat-pack bookshelf, overflowing with dog-eared paperback novels. Someone had even attempted to make the place more friendly with a few plastic plants on the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d spent her first few hours doing paperwork, but had eventually given into boredom and investigated the bookshelves. A surprising amount were romance novels, and by her third visit, she’d read most of them. On her fourth visit she brought a set of comfortable pajamas, a fuzzy bathrobe, and contributed several steamy new romances to the collection. On her fifth visit, she also brought a vibrator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which is how she found herself naked on her back, legs spread, a book in one hand, magic wand in the other, holding the rumbling head to her clit, when the airlock opened and an alien walked in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Divya squealed, dropped everything, and jumped to her feet, pulling her robe on. She apologized frantically, knowing she was babbling, and that it probably couldn’t understand her anyway. The vibrator was buzzing loudly on the floor. She cursed, switched it off, and kicked it under the couch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The alien stood, impassively, near the entrance, tentacles slowly moving as if flowing in a current.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Divya glanced around and felt a burning shame for her role in the state of the room. It looked less like an embassy and more like a dorm room. She crossed her arms, pulling her robe tighter. The air smelled like sex. Her heart was pounding with a mixture of panic and lingering arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, it dawned on her that she was only the second human in history to be in the presence of an alien. Was it the same one? How long did they live? She stared, trying to compare it to her memory of the one from the recording. That one’s mantle was a darker shade of purple, she thought, while this one had more of a zebra-stripe pattern fading from a dark cerulean to a bright lavender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her eyes constantly drifted back to the tentacles. They rippled and flowed in constant hypnotic motion, fading from a rich brown to a rosy pink. Near the mantle, they were as thick as her thigh, but they tapered down to a bulbous, ridged tip. She shook her head, unsure if they’d always looked so phallic, or if her mind was simply primed to see them that way due to her frustrated masturbation session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” she cleared her throat, with as much dignity as she could muster, reminding herself she had a job to do. “Welcome aboard. I am Ambassador Patel, and, um, I…” Her mind was a blank. There was something she was supposed to say. Some speech written decades before. The binder! She turned to the bookshelf, pulled down a faded three-ring binder, and flipped through the pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where is it, where is it,” she muttered. “Ah, here! On behalf of the human race, I, um…” She trailed off as the alien drifted toward her. One tentacle reached up, and gently pushed the binder away. Following its lead, she stopped reading and placed it on the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gazed up at the colors rippling along its dorsal ridge. Was that how they communicated? Its tentacles waved gently as it came closer. She backed away, then stopped, unsure if that would be considered an insult. It raised one arm, and tentatively brushed against her cheek, as tender as a new lover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d expected it to feel cold and clammy, but it was smooth and hot to the touch. She shivered as the tip trailed down her neck. A second arm joined the first, and they slipped into her robe, following her collarbone in opposite directions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the tentacles were quite flexible, the ends were a bit stiffer, with taut skin, and a clearly defined ridge. It really was astonishingly like a human erection. An odd coincidence of evolution that would have been fascinating in any other context, but was currently causing her to have a rather inappropriate physical reaction as the firm tips moved along her shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Divya struggled to remain professional. She was an ambassador of the human race, and this was the most interest the aliens had ever expressed. They had no eyes as far as she could tell. Perhaps they communicated by touch. This could simply be the alien equivalent of a handshake. She resolved to not ruin their second chance at alien relations by being prudish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She exhaled shakily and released her grip on the robe as it was parted by the wandering tentacles. Additional arms joined the first two, and her skin felt hot as they boldly explored her body. She felt a tip tracing her spine, another moving along her hip, one sliding down her belly, and one wandering over her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tips fumbled aimlessly, prodding her armpit, bumping along her knee, teasing along the cleft of her buttocks. One tangled curiously through her hair, while another wrapped around her breast, drawing a surprised inhalation from her as it squeezed gently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The colors on its mantle seemed to flush red, though surely, it was anthropomorphizing to see that as a sexual response. Even so, Divya found herself trembling as she parted her legs and arms to allow the alien complete access to her body. The tentacle fondling her breast seemed to be contracting rhythmically, and the surprisingly dexterous tip was nudging deliciously against her stiffened nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An arm moved sinuously around her leg, wandering up her thigh slowly enough to leave her tense with anticipation. Abandoning her hair, that tip softly explored her face, brushing over her eyelids, pressing against the tip of her nose, and tracing over her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped as the tip that had been caressing her back and buttocks slipped between her thighs from behind, teasing her most sensitive spots. Perhaps sensing a change, it moved back and forth, rubbing against the wetness coating her still-swollen lips, and sending waves of sensation rippling through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No longer able to resist, Divya gave up any further attempts at professionalism. She rocked shamelessly back and forth, gasping and sliding her slick lips over the firm heat between her legs. Another tentacle wrapped around her other breast, stimulating her nipple. She knew it was foolish to read human motivations into an alien creature, but it was hard not to think it was trying to cause her pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tip that was exploring her mouth probed between her lips. Startled, she let out a muffled cry as a thick, firm, heat pushed inward. It started flexing, rubbing along the length of her tongue. Instinctively, she wrapped her lips around it and sucked, her body rocking in the creature’s firm grasp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tentacle that was rubbing between her legs slipped further forward, angling up until the ridged tip was rubbing directly over her clit. Her insides fluttered, and she squeezed her legs around it, moaning around the shaft in her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More and more tentacles roamed her body. How many did it have? There seemed to be an endless number, caressing, prodding, rubbing. Her breasts seemed to swell in the warm massage, nipples pinched and pulled in a way that couldn’t be accidental.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt herself lifted off the ground, tentacles wrapping her legs and arms, supporting her back. As her weight shifted and her legs spread, she felt a thick tip pressing against her entrance. She moaned eagerly, squeezing a supporting tentacle encouragingly, and was rewarded. It slipped in, the bulbous head spreading her open. Another hot tentacle rested against her clit, heavy and firm, as the first pushed deeper inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She could barely focus anymore, but could still see the rippling colors flashing back and forth along the creature’s dorsal ridge. The zebra stripes on its mantle were undeniably throbbing, flashing a dark red in time with her heartbeat. A distant part of her brain wondered what was happening here. Was this mating behavior? A new stage of diplomatic relations? Was she about to be eaten? She couldn’t bring herself to care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tentacle inside her pussy seemed to be swelling, thrusting deep inside and holding before sliding out in a way that dragged the ridge over a spot that made her see flares of color. Her clit thrummed, and her nipples sang under the creature’s touch. Warmth wrapped her skin everywhere as the tentacles coiled around her, supporting her and touching her in ways a human lover never could.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then she felt a new probing against her back door. She arched her back and moaned around the cock-like shaft in her mouth. The tentacles held her firmly in the air, as the heat worked insistently against her tightly clenched ass. She tried to relax, grunting as it writhed, slick with her juices, slowly working its way in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The one in her mouth twitched, and she moaned, tasting something new, a salty flavor that reminded her of the ocean. Was it going to cum? She squirmed in its grasp, both excited and alarmed at the prospect. Some part of her worried if it was safe, but a louder and more primal part of her desperately wanted it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As if sensing her eagerness, it began moving more urgently, thrusting into her from every direction. She sputtered and groaned as it pushed deeper, sliding into her throat. She felt the shaft in her pussy swell until she felt stretched taut as it thrust over and over, alternating strokes with the one in her ass, which seemed to go deeper every time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her climax crashed through her body with astonishing force. She tensed, toes curling, fingers grasping. She felt her core clenching over and over around the intruders, hard and unyielding and radiating heat inside her. One after another, the orgasms rolled over her in waves. They grew so intense she worried she would pass out, but the creature never slowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” she tried to moan around the throbbing tentacle filling her mouth. She rocked back and forth in the creature’s grasp, cumming again and again as it fucked her relentlessly. Pleasure so overwhelming it was nearly painful. Her nipples sparked electricity down her spine, and her clit buzzed angrily as a tentacle coiled against it, still thrusting into her, and it was too much, too much, too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cum,” she begged, unintelligibly, “please!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, the creature’s entire mantle pulsed red. It began to shake and spasm. She screamed and choked as every tentacle gushed a sticky, viscous liquid over her. It coated her skin, poured down her throat, and flooded her pussy and ass. She felt a wave of euphoria as she frantically swallowed, moaning with relief and squirming in the now-slippery grasp of the tentacles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a moment, the creature shuddered, and withdrew from her all at once. She cried out at the sensation, then found herself being laid gently on the floor, gasping and drenched with the creature’s cum. For a long moment, all she could do was pant, trying to catch her breath and slow her heart rate. Dimly, she heard the sound of the airlock door cycling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she finally sat up, still shaky, hugging herself in a puddle of fluid, the alien was gone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, as she cleaned up the mess, she wondered how she would ever report this. She grimaced as she imagined trying to explain why the alien had walked in on her masturbating. Best-case scenario, she was in for some extremely awkward discussions with the scientists and politicians. Worst case, she could go to prison for ruining the only attempt by the aliens to make contact in eighty years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, as she stepped back onto her ship with a day bag containing an extremely soiled bathrobe, she decided not to tell anyone. After all, what was there actually to tell? No communication had taken place. There was, as far as she could tell, no change to the treaty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better to act like everything was normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And in the end, it was fine. After all, no one &lt;em&gt;expected&lt;/em&gt; anything to happen, so her standard report raised no eyebrows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following year passed without incident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except. Divya could not stop thinking about it. She was constantly distracted. Someone would call on her in a meeting, and she would startle out of a fantasy of being fucked by grasping tentacles. Her dreams became increasingly erotic, while at the same time, no human lover could compare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She started counting the days until the next visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she finally made the journey back to Treaty Station, she sat on the couch, wearing a scandalous set of lingerie, vibrating with tension and soaking her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the door opened and her alien stepped out, she laughed with relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasted no time, seeming just as eager as she was. It bent her over the table and took her forcefully from behind, until she cried with passion, and it drenched her with cum again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lingerie was a total loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next year, she lay on the couch, and it climbed on top of her, caressed her lovingly, then fucked her so hard she saw stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the year after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the year after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the year after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She no longer felt any guilt or shame for her secret. As far as the rest of the world was concerned, nothing had happened. There was no change in the aliens’ behavior, so why rock the boat?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someday, she would retire. Maybe she’d reveal the truth then. Or perhaps, when that day came, she would pick another young woman who looked like she could keep a secret, and pass her the keys to the station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ambassador Patel, we have docked with Treaty Station. You may go aboard,” announced the ship’s AI pilot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you, ship.” She stood up and loosened the belt on her robe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe someday. But not today.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Rylie’s Proposal: an Erotic Romance</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/rylies-proposal-ebook/"/>
		<published>2024-10-15T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-10-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/rylies-proposal-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="money" />
    <category term="prostitution" />
    <category term="dancing" />
    <category term="clubbing" />
    <category term="public" />
    <category term="airplane sex" />
    <category term="car sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="facials" />
    <category term="titjob" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="doggy style" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="threesome" />
    <category term="ffm" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rylies-proposal-QcWvoAQzNN-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Rylie’s uptight roommate Erica has just been laid off, and is freaked out that she’ll have to drop out of college and move back home. This is forcing her to admit that she wishes she hadn’t spent all her time studying, and now she wants Rylie to help her get some action before she has to move out. Rylie has an idea to solve both of her problems, but she’s not sure Erica is going to like it…&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DK41ZW68"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Rylie’s Proposal</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/rylies-proposal/"/>
		<published>2024-10-12T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-10-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/rylies-proposal/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="money" />
    <category term="prostitution" />
    <category term="dancing" />
    <category term="clubbing" />
    <category term="public" />
    <category term="airplane sex" />
    <category term="car sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="facials" />
    <category term="titjob" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="doggy style" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="threesome" />
    <category term="ffm" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rylies-proposal-QcWvoAQzNN-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“I just wanna get fucked!” Erica blurted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riley choked and struggled not to spit out her drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, not just fucked, I wanna get &lt;em&gt;used&lt;/em&gt;!” Her roommate gesticulated drunkenly, spilling her drink on the kitchen floor. “I want a guy to look at me like all he can think about is bending me over, and, and, like, pulling my hair, and screwing the shit out of me! You know what I mean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Rylie laughed. “I know what you mean.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had come home to find Erica in tears on the couch. She’d been laid off, and had no idea how she was going to find the money for tuition and rent. Rylie got them some drinks, and did her best to reassure her that things would work out somehow. She’d only intended to help her relax a bit, but had apparently overdone it and landed in drunken confession territory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie liked Erica. She was a good roommate. Easy to get along with. Always paid her bills on time, and did her share of the chores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, if pushed, Rylie might have admitted that she thought Erica was just a bit uptight. She dressed conservatively. She didn’t smoke weed. She preferred studying to partying. She’d never once brought home a random guy from the club. Or from anywhere, for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which made her aggressive pantomiming and declaration that she wanted someone to “fuck every hole until she couldn’t walk straight” a bit shocking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Erica, I’ve never seen this side of you,” Rylie chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, my older brothers are fuck-ups, so I’ve always been under all this pressure to be the perfect good girl and graduate and do a good job and not ruin my life by getting pregnant or doing drugs or ever having any fun ever.” The words gushed out of her like a burst dam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, I think you might need some food,” Rylie said, putting a pot on the stove to make some noodles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, what I &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; is to get wrecked by a big fucking cock.” She heaved a sigh and drained what was left of her drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie nodded understandingly, and replaced her glass with water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m so jealous of you, Ry. You do what you want, how you want. And &lt;em&gt;who&lt;/em&gt; you want! I always meant to ask you to help me with guys, but there were finals and work and stuff. And now I’m gonna have to go back home and live with my mom and get some shitty retail job, and, and, and…” She trailed off, sniffling and blinking away tears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey now, no more of that,” Rylie said, giving her a quick hug while fetching sauce from the fridge. “No one’s moving home. I told you, we’ll figure something out. Then we’ll go dancing, and I’d love to be your wingwoman.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There’s nothing to figure out, it’s too much money,” she gestured dismissively. “Just promise me you’ll get me laid before I leave. Like, &lt;em&gt;proper&lt;/em&gt; laid.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip as she stirred the sauce into the noodles. She wasn’t sure if what she was about to say was a good idea or not. Despite Erica’s proclamations, it might be a bridge too far for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Erica, you’re not a virgin, are you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! I’ve done it before. It’s just, you know, been a while. And the guys I have been with? They were sweet and caring and, um…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kinda boring?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” She took a deep breath. “What if I could solve both of your problems at the same time?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you talking about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You remember my friend Max?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The fuckboy?” Erica responded, then clapped her hand over her mouth, horrified at what she’d said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s alright,” Rylie laughed, “he &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a fuckboy. Total trust fund kid with no idea how the real world works, and an overinflated ego.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So why do you hang out with him?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’s fun.” Rylie shrugged, dividing the noodles into two bowls. “He likes to party, and &lt;em&gt;loves&lt;/em&gt; being the center of attention. We get into the cool clubs, go to wild places, and meet outrageous people.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica took the offered bowl and started eating. Rylie sat down across from her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And, there is one other reason.” She hesitated long enough for Erica to look up from her noodles. “Sometimes… he pays me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why does he…” Erica frowned, then opened her eyes wide in realization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not what you think,” Rylie blurted. “He just pays me to act like his girlfriend.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you have sex with him?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! Well, kinda?” Rylie blushed. “I only go down on him.” Confessing this to Erica was more awkward than she’d expected. “I told him if he wanted to pay to fuck someone, he could go find a proper escort.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica raised an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look, the point is, Max has more money than sense. Early on, he made it clear he likes spending time with me, and would be willing to pay me enough to make up for any work I’d miss if he wants to go party for a weekend or whatever. And then some. We have fun together, and I make some extra cash at the same time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And the sex?” To Rylie’s relief, Erica sounded more curious than horrified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When we get back to wherever we’re staying, he likes to watch me masturbate.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then you give him head?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. I don’t mind after I’m turned on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh.” Rylie considered this for a moment. “Wait, you said you had a way to solve my problems, then you brought up Max?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I know, just hear me out! You want to get properly fucked, right? Well, for all his flaws, Max actually has a pretty nice cock. He’s clean, he’s always respected my boundaries, and I know he’s interested in you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He is?” Erica seemed more shocked by this revelation than anything else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah. He’s told me before that you could join us anytime. I assumed you wouldn’t be interested in that kind of thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, how much money are we talking about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Enough to cover your tuition and a few months of rent.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit, really?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really,” Rylie nodded. “What do you think?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck it.” Erica grinned. “Two birds with one stone. And I won’t have to move home with Mom! Call Max, tell him I’m in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Few Days Later&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; he?” Erica asked again, pacing back and forth. “I thought you said he’d be here at lunch? It’s almost three!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He said, ‘around lunch,’” Rylie answered from the couch. “Max has never been on time to anything in his life.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Rylie had called Max and explained the situation, he’d enthusiastically agreed, and said he’d pick them up on Friday. Now it was Friday, and Erica was a ball of nerves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you sure this isn’t too short on me?” She fretted, tugging at the hem of the skirt she’d borrowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not, but even if it was, the whole point is to get you ‘properly fucked,’ remember?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica grimaced, hearing her own words quoted back to her. Rylie stood up and squeezed her shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“E, are you sure you’re still into this? It’s not too late for me to call Max and tell him to fuck off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, I mean, it’s fine, I just hate waiting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As if on cue, there was a knock at the door. Rylie gave Erica a quick hug, and let Max in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ladies! Sorry I’m late, I had lunch with some cryptocurrency guys, and they would &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; stop talking. You know how it is. How ya doing, Rylie?” He gave them both a quick hug, then dropped onto the couch, exhaling noisily. “Whew! Alright, Erica, come here, sit with me. Let’s chat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at Rylie, who nodded, then sat down next to Max. Rylie leaned against the wall, curious to see how Max would handle this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was fucking &lt;em&gt;stoked&lt;/em&gt; when Rylie told me what you’re looking for. You couldn’t have known it, but your timing was perfect. I’ve been sitting on something kinda special, waiting for the right opportunity, and babe, I think it’s for you. Here’s the deal. I’ve got this pill I ordered from a Russian catalog. A buddy tried it, said it’s like hurricane-force Viagra. This little beauty is supposed to let me fuck like a goddamn stallion all day and night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica blushed, but didn’t stop him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, you know that Rylie and I have an arrangement. We usually just do a bit of partying, a bit of dancing, then she gives me head. We keep it kinda softcore. Girlfriend experience, you know? I throw her a bit of walking-around money because I was tired of her saying she couldn’t go out because she had to work. So now she can have a good time with me, no worries. And that’s great, I love it, but like you, I am craving that next-level experience. I wanna rock it &lt;em&gt;hardcore&lt;/em&gt;, have a day that we’re both gonna remember when we’re old and gray, you feel me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She nodded, as if this was a perfectly reasonable thing to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool cool cool. Rylie told me you were looking for a good time, but I get that this is probably gonna be outside your comfort zone. Now, I don’t want you to think I’m paying you to do anything you don’t want to do. I’m gonna push your limits, sure, but what I’m spending my money on is an &lt;em&gt;experience&lt;/em&gt;, one that I think we’re both gonna savor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Plus,” Rylie interjected, “I’ll be there the whole time to make sure you’re okay. If it’s too much at any point, you just let me know.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right,” Max nodded emphatically. “So, here’s my dream, and I think this magic pill’s gonna make it happen for us. We’re gonna go out, we’re gonna have a good time. We’re gonna dance, we’re gonna party, and I’m gonna fuck you every hour on the hour.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Every hour?” Erica hesitated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Every hour,” Max nodded, glancing at his watch. “For twelve hours. So what’s it gonna be, babe? Are you in or out?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” She slowly nodded her head. “Yeah. Yeah, I’m in. Let’s do it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whoo! That’s great fucking news, ’cause I took the pill on the drive over here, that short skirt of yours is driving me crazy, and I’m already hard as a motherfucker!” He looked at his watch, and held up one finger. “Okay, the clock staaarts… now!” A timer chimed, and he quickly unbuttoned his pants to free his cock. True to his word, it looked almost painfully erect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Erica gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, babe, we’ll start slow. For now, just go down on me.” He rubbed her shoulder encouragingly, pulling her closer as his cock twitched.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at Rylie, clearly a bit hesitant to do it in front of her. Rylie gave her a wink and a thumbs-up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” Max groaned, closing his eyes as she lowered her head and wrapped her lips around him. “This pill’s got me really goddamn sensitive!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip, fascinated by the sight of her uptight roommate bobbing her head in Max’s lap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus, your mouth is so hot! It feels amazing!” Erica made a surprised sound as Max put his hand on the back of her neck, encouraging her to go lower. “Keep going! I’m not gonna last long.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie was surprised at how aroused she felt from the sight of Max using Erica’s mouth for his pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck! Fuck yeah,” Max grunted as Erica slurped loudly around his cock. “I’m getting close!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He opened his eyes and looked straight at Rylie as he pushed harder on the back of Erica’s head. She didn’t protest, just moaned in response and swallowed him deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your throat,” Max gasped, as Rylie squirmed in sympathy, “so fucking tight!” Erica’s lips finally reached the base of his cock, making him groan loudly. “Fuck! I’m gonna cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica gripped the edge of the couch cushion tightly as Max started shaking. He grunted with each spasm, still holding her head down as he shot his load into her throat. She moaned, eyes watering, trying to swallow everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he gasped and let go, collapsing back and panting. Erica popped up immediately, coughing and choking, wiping his cum from her lips. She looked at Rylie with surprise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You okay?” Rylie mouthed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica nodded, tears running down her cheek, but grinning widely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Max crowed as he buttoned up his pants. “This is gonna be &lt;em&gt;sick!&lt;/em&gt; Okay, ladies, we got a flight to catch. Tonight, I’m taking you to my buddy’s club in LA. Grab your stuff, real quick-like. Rylie, bring that little red number I bought you last month? Erica, we got just enough time to go buy you something sexy to wear.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously?” Rylie asked. “You’ve got twelve hours, and you want to spend a bunch of them on a plane?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’ll all balance out with the time zone change,” Max shrugged, unconcerned. “Hustle up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An hour later, Rylie was sitting with Max on the bench outside a changing room. Erica was inside trying on a handful of dresses. The saleswoman had been a bit rude until Max had flashed his credit card. Suddenly, she’d been more than willing to help Erica, who seemed a bit overwhelmed by the fancy shop, pick out a few things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How’s this one? Is it too much?” Erica pulled back the curtain a bit timidly. She’d had to remove her bra, and the loose purple fabric plunged daringly from her shoulders, exposing quite a bit of pale skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whoo!” Rylie grinned. “Your tits look great. Can you dance in it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica hesitated, then lifted her arms to sway to an imaginary beat. The dress barely clung to her curves, and started to shift away from her breasts. She squealed and pulled it back into place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s good.” Max nodded appreciatively. “Do you like this one or the green one better?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” she considered, “I think the green one would be better for dancing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Done deal.” He nodded, glancing at his watch. “But, uh, don’t take that one off just yet.” He stood up and put an arm around her waist, pulling her into the changing room. As the timer beeped again, he winked at Rylie and closed the curtain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica squealed in mock protest. The saleswoman looked up at the noise and narrowed her eyes when she noticed Max was missing. Rylie shrugged in a “what are you gonna do” kind of way. The saleswoman sighed and busied herself with neatening the already well-organized displays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie grinned and turned her attention to the curtain. It wasn’t quite closed all the way, and from where she sat, she could see a narrow view of Erica and Max’s reflections in the mirror. Erica had dropped to her knees, allowing the dress to fall down her arms, exposing her breasts, which she was pushing together around Max’s cock. He was whispering something while thrusting urgently into her cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked flushed, with a mixture of arousal and concern on her face, no doubt worried they’d get caught. Max clearly didn’t care about anything except the way her tits felt around his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie crossed her legs, once again surprised at how erotic she found the sight of them together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica was awkwardly leaning forward, trying to lick the tip of his cock at the peak of each thrust. Max grimaced as her tongue teased him and said something Rylie couldn’t hear. Erica looked up at him, eyes wide, as he shoved her back against the wall and fucked against her chest harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, he stiffened, and Erica let out a surprised sound as thick white cum splattered her chest. It shot across her collarbone and fell across her breasts. She eagerly leaned down to wrap her lips around him, sucking and swallowing the last of his climax as his spunk dripped down her nipples onto the purple fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stepped backward, and walked calmly, if a little winded, from the dressing room. The saleswoman frowned and pretended not to notice him buttoning his pants as he approached the counter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’ll take the green one,” he announced. “And the purple one, too. We, uh, spilled something on it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max drove like a bat out of hell to get them to the private jet terminal at the airport in time for their flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not like they’d leave without us,” Max laughed dismissively, “but I got a schedule to keep.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plane was small but luxurious. The cabin had just four seats, all facing each other, more than like recliners than airliner seats. The flight attendant got them all seated, and disappeared into a small galley area as the plane took off. After reaching altitude, she reappeared with glasses of champagne.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie sat across from Max and Erica, sipping her drink and curious to see what Max would do at the top of the hour. Erica seemed intrigued as well, but Max just grinned and made small talk until the timer on his watch went off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Erica,” he grinned, obviously pleased with himself. “Want to join the mile-high club?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, you mean in there?” She shot a hesitant look toward the restroom door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, babe, right here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here?” Erica looked apprehensive. “What if the flight attendant comes back?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She won’t. Passengers on flights like this value their privacy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” she hesitated, shooting a nervous glance at Rylie. “Okay. Yeah. Uh, how do you want to…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want you to come ride my cock.” Without waiting, he lowered his pants to around his ankles. His cock jutted upward, already hard and eagerly twitching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Erica grinned and reached under her skirt to slip off her panties, then moved to straddle him in the oversized seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip as she watched Erica wiggle her hips, imagining the way she was positioning Max at her entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max grinned as Erica slowly lowered herself, one hand on his shoulder, the other between her legs. Her skirt was draped over them, blocking Rylie’s view, but she could tell the moment he filled her from the way Erica shivered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she started moving on top of him, lifting and lowering herself. She gasped every time he slid home. From behind, Rylie couldn’t see her expression, but the tilt of her head and the way she squirmed told her everything she needed to know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few minutes of slow, sensual build-up, Max’s hands appeared on her waist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is nice and all, but I want you to &lt;em&gt;ride&lt;/em&gt; me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica squealed as he pushed her forcefully down onto him. He squeezed her hips tightly, tugging her up and slamming her down over and over. She cried out every time he thrust upward to meet her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, like that,” he groaned, “fuck me hard!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god!” Erica moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie squirmed. The cabin smelled like sex, and hearing the wet sounds of their fucking was almost more erotic than if she could see Max’s cock plowing into Erica.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” Max grunted. “Your pussy! Feels so good!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” Erica cried over and over. “Yes, yes, yes…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m gonna fuck this pussy all night long!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, fuck me,” she moaned. “Use me! Oh god, use me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m cumming!” He groaned, slamming her down one last time and holding her in place with white knuckles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” She grasped the headrest of his seat as he shuddered between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a long minute, he let her go. She quickly got to her feet and ran to the bathroom, hand between her legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” he grinned, lazily stroking his cock, which glistened with Erica’s juices. “This is fucking incredible. I gotta get more of these pills.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie didn’t say anything. Her jeans suddenly seemed very tight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few glasses of champagne later, Erica was laughing as Rylie and Max shared a story about a night clubbing when Max’s timer went off again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica set her glass aside and looked expectantly at Max, who was already unbuttoning his pants. As before, his cock sprang forth, erect and ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, he had Erica sit in his lap and ride him, gripping her hips tightly and fucking her against him until she was moaning with every thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie watched, and hoped it wasn’t obvious how turned on she was. She hadn’t really considered what effect it would have on her to watch them fuck over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica seemed overwhelmed, wordlessly groaning and gasping as he took full advantage of her body. Rylie hoped the experience was living up to her fantasy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max stared lustily at Erica’s bouncing tits, not caring at all that Rylie was there. If anything, it seemed to excite him to have an audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he came inside her again, cursing triumphantly the entire time. Erica threw her head back and gasped at the sensation, before climbing shakily to her feet and stumbling to the restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time, Rylie followed her, slipping into the tiny room with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica looked surprised, but quickly sat on the toilet to wipe up the cum leaking out of her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you doing okay?” Rylie asked, worried she’d gotten her friend in over her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay?” Erica laughed shakily. “God, I’m fucking dripping! The idea that he’s just going to keep taking me like this all night? Using my body for his pleasure? It’s incredible.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you sure? It kinda seems like… a lot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m good, Ry, I promise.” She stood up and pulled her into a hug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ll be landing soon,” Max said, the next time his watch beeped. “Get on your knees. I wanna fuck you from behind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where?” Erica looked around for a good spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right here,” Max said, gesturing at the floor between their seats and Rylie’s. The seats were big, but the cabin wasn’t, and there wasn’t enough space between the seats for what Max had in mind without practically doing it in Rylie’s lap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But,” Erica protested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie can switch seats if she wants,” Max said, with a grin. “Or she can stay there. I think she’s enjoying watching us fuck, and wouldn’t mind a closer view.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie fought back a blush at Max’s observation, and focused on Erica, trying to read how she felt about this suggestion. She looked surprised, Rylie thought, but not opposed to the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“E, I told you I’d be here the whole time, to make sure you’re okay. But if you want, I can move.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” Erica gulped, dropping to her knees. “You should stay here! To, um, keep an eye on things…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Awesome,” Max grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They got in position. There was just enough room for Max to kneel behind her, practically with his butt still in the seat. Rylie had to spread her legs to let Erica brace herself on her seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica looked up at Rylie with wide eyes as Max lifted her skirt and rubbed the head of his cock against her. She opened her mouth to say something, but before she could, Max thrust forward, burying himself completely. She groaned, mouth wide, as he started fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie could no longer pretend the situation wasn’t turning her on. Erica swaying between her thighs with every thrust. Max grinning like a wolf, knew full well the effect this was having on her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He slapped Erica’s ass, making her squeal and grab Rylie’s leg. He fucked her harder, pushing forward with more force, shoving her closer to Rylie, who was gripping the armrest tightly. The lust in Erica’s eyes, gazing up at her and squeezing her leg, caused an intense heat to blossom in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie,” she gasped, “He’s so deep!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Rylie breathed, unable to form a more coherent thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max groaned loudly, fucking her relentlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, oh!” Erica moaned. “I think, ah, I think I’m gonna cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yeah,” Max growled. “Me too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Erica gasped again. “Oh my god!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She dropped her head onto Rylie’s hip and dug her fingernails into her thigh. She groaned loudly, sending a wave of sensation through Rylie, who struggled to contain herself as Max continued fucking Erica against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly he cried out, staring wild-eyed and rocking with each pulse of his orgasm. Rylie shuddered as he and Erica came together, practically in her lap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know this incredible Korean fusion place. You ladies are gonna love it,” Max exclaimed as he sped down the street, weaving in and out of traffic in the Mustang he’d had waiting for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The restaurant turned out to be a confusing blend of styles. The decor was old-school high-class dining, with tablecloths, fancy chairs, and candles. The dim lighting barely concealed that the restaurant had been through multiple styles and cuisines as the owner jumped from trend to trend. Despite that, the dining room was crowded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The head waiter recognized Max and escorted them to a reserved table in the back corner. Max sat with his back to the wall as the waiter gave them menus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The food turned out to be quite good, though Rylie was a bit distracted by Erica’s nervousness. Her eyes kept darting to the clock on the wall, ticking closer and closer to the top of the hour. She scanned around the dining room, unsure what Max would suggest. Surely, he wasn’t planning to fuck her over the table in front of everyone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When his timer finally beeped, Erica was practically vibrating with anticipation. He calmly reached down to unbutton his pants. Rylie glanced around the dining room, but their position in the back meant no one noticed he’d just pulled out his throbbing erection. He grinned at Erica and gestured with his eyes for her to go under the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her cheeks flushed, but she licked her lips. After looking around to make sure no one was watching, she quickly ducked under the tablecloth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie couldn’t believe it. The tablecloth wasn’t very long, but the dim lighting meant anyone not looking carefully could easily miss the sight of Erica crouching under the table. And while the wet sounds of her increasingly enthusiastic blowjob seemed painfully obvious to Rylie, the music was apparently loud enough to keep anyone from noticing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you think of your—ah—kimchi tacos?” Max asked, as if his cock wasn’t in someone’s mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie didn’t bother answering. She felt flushed, and took a sip of water. Why was this so exciting? Her heart was pounding. She wasn’t even really involved, but sitting here while it happened, &lt;em&gt;knowing&lt;/em&gt; it was happening, made her feel like she was part of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max shivered in response to some unseen stimulus. He gripped the edge of the table tightly and laughed in surprise. He scooted so low in his chair that Rylie worried he might fall out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How is everything?” The waiter appeared suddenly. “Would you like any dessert?” Max could only shake his head, with a screwed-up expression on his face. The waiter looked momentarily concerned, but Rylie assured him the food was excellent, and they would not be having dessert. “Very good. And the other young lady?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She, um, stepped away to powder her nose.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The waiter nodded, and moved on to another table, politely ignoring whatever was going on with Max.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck me,” he groaned quietly as soon as the waiter was out of earshot. “I started cumming just as he walked up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip and watched as Max squirmed. She imagined Erica under the table, lips wrapped around his throbbing cock, milking the last of his orgasm. Suddenly, he shuddered and sat up straight, breathing heavily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A moment later, Erica reappeared, climbing quickly back into her seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Max laughed giddily as she took a drink of water. “You are amazing. This is the best money I’ve ever spent!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica blushed furiously, but looked pleased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There’s no point showing up to the club before midnight,” Max declared as he drove to the hotel. “We’ll get checked in here and kill a bit of time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Predictably, the suite was ostentatious. It was larger than their apartment. Hell, it was larger than her parent’s house. It had multiple rooms, a chandelier, a fireplace, and a jaw-dropping view of downtown L.A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were all standing on the balcony when Max’s watch beeped. Rylie watched, amused, as he kicked off his pants, stepped behind Erica, and lifted her skirt. She spread her legs and arched her back as he gripped his swollen prick and angled it to meet her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She gasped as he slipped easily inside. Apparently, she wasn’t exaggerating about how wet the situation made her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max wasted no time, grabbing her hips and thrusting eagerly. Erica braced herself on the chest-height glass railing. Rylie couldn’t help but notice that she was pushing back to meet him on every thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biting her lip and trying to ignore the insistent heat between her thighs, Rylie turned her gaze outward. There was another hotel across the street, and she scanned the windows idly. In one room, a family was putting their kids to sleep. In another, a man lay in bed watching TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And in one room, almost directly across from them, a woman wearing expensive lingerie stood at the window. She stretched languidly as a nude man appeared from behind and kissed her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie was distracted from the sight when Erica swore loudly. Max had grabbed her hair and yanked her head back, making her cry out with a mix of pleasure and pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Rylie looked back across the street, she was surprised to see the couple looking in their direction. The woman tapped the man and pointed. He followed her gesture and smiled when he spotted the three of them on the balcony. He said something in the woman’s ear that made her laugh, and caressed her body as they watched.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey Erica,” Rylie said, “you’ve got an audience.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Erica groaned. “What do you mean?” She opened her eyes and followed Rylie’s finger, pointing to the couple across the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god!” She squealed. “They’re watching us?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Awesome!” Max looked over her shoulder, saw the other couple, and laughed. He tugged Erica’s hair harder, forcing her more upright, and continued fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Max,” Erica moaned, “They can see us!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he agreed. “It’s hot, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god,” she moaned. “Oh fuck!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie tried not to squirm as she discreetly squeezed her thighs together. Watching Erica give in to lust was turning her on more than she wanted to admit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get ready,” Max growled, “I’m close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Will you—ah!” Erica struggled to ask, “cum on my face?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You want them to see me cum on you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Oh fuck, yes, cum all over me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get on your knees!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie and the couple across the street stared as Erica dropped in front of Max. He stroked his cock, pointing it at her lips. She panted with desire, one hand under her skirt, shamelessly rubbing her clit. She gasped as hot cum splashed across her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stand up, babe, show them how sexy you look.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica climbed shakily to her feet, and turned to face the couple across the way. They grinned and waved. She waved back, laughing deliriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An hour later, the three of them were sprawled across the enormous bed in the master suite. Erica had washed her face while Max ordered some fruit to snack on and Rylie watched a baking competition on the obscenely large television.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max hadn’t bothered to put his pants back on after cleaning up, so Rylie could see that even after cumming, the pill kept him hard. He lounged on the bed between them, legs spread, cock resting on his stomach, faintly throbbing with his heartbeat. He noticed her looking, and winked. His cock twitched eagerly, as if pleased by her attention. She rolled her eyes and turned back to the TV, pretending she hadn’t felt an answering flutter inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When his timer went off, Erica put down her grapes and sat up eagerly to see what he wanted her to do. She’d discarded her bra and top, and her nipples looked almost as stiff as Max’s cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stood up and walked to the foot of the bed, turning to face them. Erica followed on her hands and knees, and enthusiastically wrapped her lips around his head. He laced his fingers in her hair, and she moaned as he pushed deeper into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie sat awkwardly against the headboard. The heat between her thighs was impossible to deny. She bit her knuckle and stared, trying to resist the urge to pinch her nipples or shove a hand down her pants. It was confusing. She was just here to make sure Max didn’t get out of line. Being used for someone else’s pleasure was Erica’s fantasy, not hers. So why was she so turned on?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie,” Max said, snapping her out of a haze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh? Nothing. What?” She crossed her arms over her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay,” he grinned, still thrusting into Erica’s mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s okay?” She was genuinely confused, and distracted by Erica’s quiet moans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can tell this is turning you on. Why don’t you touch yourself?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um, no, I mean…” She found it difficult to answer, distracted by the sight of Erica’s lips finally reaching the base of his shaft. He groaned and held her there for a long moment until she started choking. Eyes watering, she quickly turned around on her hands and knees so he could fuck her from behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on—ah!” He gasped as Erica slipped him inside. “You masturbate for me all the time. Why is this different?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… I mean, it’s…” Rylie stammered, unable to take her eyes off Erica’s face as Max started fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie,” Erica whimpered, “please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she groaned, unable to resist any longer. Erica and Max watched hungrily as she peeled her clothes off. She squeezed her breasts, nipples puckering eagerly with the long-denied stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Watch this, Erica,” Max murmured. “She’s so fucking hot when she gets off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica could only moan in agreement as Rylie leaned back and spread her legs. Her lips were already puffy and sensitive, and she gasped as she spread her wetness with her fingers. Max grinned, the way he always did when she started rubbing circles around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did it turn you on, watching us all day?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie groaned, unable to deny it, but reluctant to say so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew it!” He laughed. “On the balcony, I thought for sure you were gonna rub one out while they watched us fuck!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I almost did,” she breathed, picking up the pace. “It turned me on so much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Back at your apartment, I could tell you were shocked when I made her suck my cock, but you never looked away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t,” she admitted, then tried to make an excuse. “I had to make sure you didn’t overdo it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s not why, though,” he laughed. “Come on!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was hotter than I thought,” she conceded, “watching the two of you.” She groaned as she pushed two fingers inside, while continuing to rub her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then on the plane, when I fucked her into your lap, I thought you were either gonna kiss her or make her eat you out!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica let out a squeal, and looked up at Rylie with startled longing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Max, shut the fuck up,” Rylie moaned, feeling the pressure building. Erica was staring, grasping at the blanket as Max started fucking her harder, slamming into her from behind. Rylie’s insides were starting to clench around her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica came first. She slapped the bed and screamed, burying her face in the blanket, shaking uncontrollably. Max kept his grip on her hips, holding her up as he fucked her, relentlessly working toward his climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie grunted as all her muscles seemed to contract at once. She felt a hot gush around her fingers as waves of pleasure radiated from her core. This orgasm had been building all day, and the release was nearly overwhelming. Her entire body seemed to be pulsing, clenching, thrumming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sight of Rylie cumming pushed Max over the edge. He groaned and shoved Erica down onto her stomach with one final thrust, collapsing on top of her. She moaned happily as he came inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie kept her palm clamped over her clit, legs shaking and head swimming with confusing thoughts about both Max and Erica.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 P.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like everything else in the hotel room, the shower was absurdly large. The tiled space could easily accommodate multiple people. There were several rainfall shower heads mounted to the ceiling, and a surprising array of pleasant-smelling body washes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus, this feels amazing,” Erica purred, standing under one of the shower heads and letting the water cascade down her back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right?” Rylie grinned. “A girl could get used to this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie had been pleasantly surprised when Erica followed her, giggling, into the steamy spray. There was little trace remaining of her shy, uptight roommate. This new Erica was reveling in her newly claimed sexuality, and after letting Rylie watch her get fucked repeatedly, sharing a shower was apparently no big deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um…” Rylie started to ask something and then changed her mind. “Just to be clear, are you still doing okay with all this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m more than okay!” Erica laughed, “Oh my god, this is, like, &lt;em&gt;revelatory&lt;/em&gt;. I’ll need to process a bit at some point, but, yeah, it’s everything I wanted. Thank you so much for setting this up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good, good.” Rylie rolled her neck. She meant to ask about the way Erica looked at her on the bed, and on the plane. But she wasn’t quite sure of her own feelings. It was complicated because Max was involved. Or was it? Maybe she was overthinking it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before she could work out what to say, a now-familiar beeping sound announced Max as he strolled erection-first into the bathroom. Erica squealed excitedly as he joined them in the shower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie quickly rinsed off as Max turned Erica around, pushed her up against the wall, and shoved his cock between her legs. She gasped and arched her back, angling to meet him as he started fucking her hard and fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retreating to dry her hair in the next room, still confusingly aroused, Rylie turned up the TV to cover the sound of Erica’s moans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Midnight&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, Max decided it was time to head to the club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Never show up early, ladies. Like the bard said, the party don’t start ’till we walk in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s a line from a Kesha song, you dork.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What can I say, I love the classics. Let’s get dressed!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After they changed into their dresses, Max tossed his keys to Rylie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wanna drive?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The Mustang?” She grinned. “Hell yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The car was stupidly fun to drive. The motor growled like a beast waiting to be let off the leash. At a red light, a car pulled up alongside, low-slung, with neon lights underneath, revving a challenge. Max and Erica laughed from the back seat as she gunned it, effortlessly leaping ahead of the other car when the light turned green. She was having so much fun, she barely noticed Max’s watch was beeping again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Max!” Erica giggled. “My dress!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just pull it up and sit in my lap, babe,” he replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glancing in the rearview, she caught a glimpse of Erica straddling Max, with her dress hitched up over her hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You guys better be quick,” Rylie laughed. “We’re almost there!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just—ah—park in the back,” Max groaned, slightly muffled by Erica’s cleavage. “We’ll use the VIP entrance.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she pulled into a small parking lot, an attendant with a clipboard gestured for her to stop and roll down the window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Name?” He asked, sounding bored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, Max?” Rylie said, trying to sound like someone who used VIP entrances all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not on the list,” he replied after a quick scan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie was surprised to hear Max’s window rolling down. Erica squealed as the attendant looked in, but Max kept a firm grip on her hips and didn’t let her move away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve got a standing invite,” he groaned, encouraging Erica to keep moving. “Text Stevie and—ah—tell him Max flew in for the night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The attendant barely raised an eyebrow at the sight of them fucking in the back seat. Rylie wondered what kind of things he saw regularly in this job to leave him so nonplussed. He pulled out his phone and started typing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica, after the initial moment of surprise, seemed to decide she didn’t mind an audience and resumed bouncing enthusiastically on Max’s cock. Her moans of pleasure did get a bit more performative, Rylie couldn’t help but notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” the attendant finally replied, ignoring Erica. “He says you’re on the list. You can park over there.” He walked away, casually gesturing to a space between two other expensive cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you,” Erica gasped as Rylie parked. “Are you—oh!—gonna cum soon?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Max growled. “You want it in your mouth or your pussy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie turned around in her seat to watch, curious what Erica would decide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” Erica seemed unsure. “I—ah!—You…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Choose quick!” Max groaned, his eyes screwed shut as he tried to hold back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My mouth,” Erica squealed. She jumped off him just as his cock started throbbing, and wrapped her lips tightly around his head. She moaned happily as she swallowed, stroking his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie unconsciously squeezed her breasts at the sight. Max’s eyes were screwed shut, and he rocked in place, unaware of anything beyond the pleasure of cumming in the heat of Erica’s mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he collapsed. Erica quickly opened the car door and climbed out, wiping her chin and shimmying her dress back down over her hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Max, hurry up,” she laughed. “I wanna dance!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1 A.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the next hour, Erica commanded the dance floor. Rylie was genuinely impressed. Her dancing was uninhibited, as if she was celebrating a new perspective on life. People seemed to orbit her, sometimes swinging closer, sometimes peeling off, burned by flying too close to the sun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie stayed close, at times dancing with Erica, or moving back when she seemed to vibe with someone. Mostly men would cruise by, hoping to get close to Erica. Occasionally, she would let them. Their hands would roam over her hips, or wrap around her back, trying to pull her in, but they seemed unable to keep ahold of her, and she would move on to a new partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several women came in as well. One moved in time with the beat, standing behind Erica, hands exploring her sides. Another joined her from the front, their legs twined together as they moved in time. Rylie felt her heart beating faster as the women caressed Erica’s body, grinding with her to the pounding beat. But when one leaned in as if to kiss her, Erica slipped away, finding Max in the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max seemed to instinctively understand that any attempt to constrain Erica or keep her to himself would backfire. He enthusiastically danced nearby, matching her energy, with an effortless confidence that came from knowing he would claim her again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As if sensing Rylie’s thoughts, Max glanced down at his watch, and showed it to Erica, who allowed him to lead her from the dance floor. On the way, he caught Rylie’s eye and gestured toward the bathrooms. With a shared sense of excitement, they moved through the crowd together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica didn’t hesitate to pull Max into an open stall in the women’s room. Rylie took a spot at the counter near other women checking their makeup and gossiping. A few eyebrows were raised when they went in the stall together, but it was clearly a common enough occurrence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A moment later, there was a thump against the door, followed by the sound of Erica moaning. With every passing moment, she got louder, and more of the girls started laughing, or openly staring at the stall door, thumping against the flimsy frame so hard it looked like it might crash open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, Rylie was struck by the change in her roommate. If you had told her the day before that Erica would be getting loudly fucked in a public restroom at a club, she would have laughed. It was completely out of character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” Erica screamed as the thumping got faster. “Fuck me harder!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie wished she had followed them into the stall. It was a dumb thought, there’d be no room for her, but she wanted to see the look on Erica’s face. She imagined a gleam of excitement in her eyes, genuine lust mixed with the thrill of performing in public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max let out a loud groan, there was one last final slam against the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few moments later, the stall opened and Erica walked out, adjusting her dress. She was blushing, but looked pleased with herself. Several of the women applauded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max followed in her wake, tossing off a casual wink at the catcalls he received as they returned to the dance floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2 A.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, after more drinking and dancing, Max escorted Rylie and Erica back out the VIP entrance. The night air felt cool compared to the packed club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was so much fun!” Erica said, spinning giddily as they crossed the parking lot. “Why are we leaving?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s last call in a few minutes,” Max explained. “The club’ll clear out after that, and I’m a big believer in leaving a party before it winds down.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were a few steps from the exit when Max’s timer went off. They all stopped for a moment and looked at each other, then Erica ran the last few steps to the car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, we can do it in the back seat again!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie nodded and opened the driver’s door, but stopped to look when Erica squealed. She was bent over, starting to climb into the car, but Max had grabbed her hips from behind, holding her in the open door. He started lifting her dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Max!” She laughed and swatted at him, but he kept going, pulling it up to expose the fact that she had no panties on. “Here in the parking lot?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I said every hour on the hour, babe. I’m not waiting to feel your hot little pussy around my cock again.” He quickly unbuttoned his pants. Rylie couldn’t tell if she was imagining that his cock looked even more swollen than earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, but—OH!” Erica barked in surprise as Max filled her with one eager thrust. “Oh fuck, we’re outside! Uh! Anyone—ah!—could see!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There’s no one to see except a bartender having a smoke,” Max groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god!” Erica moaned. “Is he watching? Ah! Is he watching you fuck me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie glanced around. There was indeed a dude in a tight black shirt smoking near the door. It was a small parking lot, and they were only a couple car lengths away. He could clearly see them from where he was standing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, he’s watching,” Max growled. “He’s into it, too. After we finish, I bet he’s gonna go jerk off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica slapped the seat and moaned at the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie glanced in the direction of the bartender, who, despite Max’s description, seemed only mildly curious. She climbed into the driver’s seat, closed the door, and adjusted the rearview mirror so she could see the back seat. Erica’s tits were threatening to fall out of her top with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, Rylie hitched up her own dress, pushed her panties to one side and ran a finger through the wetness coating her lips. She watched Erica moaning and swaying, gripping the edge of the seat. Max was barely visible, urgently fucking her through the open door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie slipped one finger inside as Erica’s top finally lost the battle, and her breasts spilled out. Her lips were parted, eyes wide with lust, but unfocused. Rylie imagined climbing into the back seat with her. She couldn’t tell if she wanted to kiss Erica, suck on her nipples, or push her out of the way and take her place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max groaned loudly and gave her ass a slap, making Erica cry out in surprise. Rylie pushed another finger inside. She remembered being on the plane as Max fucked Erica into her lap. Imagined that she had spread her legs, and made Erica go down on her. She rubbed her clit, imagining it was Erica’s tongue, with Max grinning and thrusting harder, as if he was using Erica to fuck Rylie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m gonna cum,” Max groaned. “I’m gonna flood your fucking pussy…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Erica cried out. “Oh fuck! Yes!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip and fucked herself in time with Max’s thrusts until he grunted, pushing deep inside and holding there. Erica moaned long and low, whimpering as Max came deep inside. Rylie felt her insides clenching around her fingers and imagined it was her bent over in the back seat instead of Erica.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3 A.M.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Rylie, the next hour passed in a haze of sexual tension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica cuddled with her on the bed, idly flipping channels on the television. Once they’d returned to the hotel room, she and Rylie had both shed their club clothes, and put on a pair of soft hotel bathrobes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica didn’t seem anxious anymore. Somewhere in the course of the day, she’d given herself over fully to the experience. The waiting, the not knowing what Max was going to do to her next, it was all part of it. She fairly radiated satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max lounged in an armchair, scrolling on his phone. The only sign that he wasn’t completely chill was the constant nervous tapping of his foot. His twelve hours were nearly up. He had one more turn with Erica, and Rylie figured he was trying to think of a way to make it count.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie’s head was still swimming with confused arousal. She was extremely aware of the heat of Erica’s body, snuggled against hers. Spending the entire day watching the two of them fuck had left her flooded with lust. She still wasn’t sure if it was mostly aimed at Max or Erica.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Max’s timer went off, he stood up, stretched, and quickly undressed. Standing at the foot of the bed, his cock jutted upward, swollen with need. Erica quickly shucked her robe and crawled, nude, towards him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you want to do, Max?” She purred seductively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lay on your back, babe, I want to watch your face while I fuck you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She giggled and lay down, spreading her legs invitingly. Max stepped forward, and rubbed the head of his cock between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie got to her knees so she could see better. Instinctively, she held her robe closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They all watched him push slowly inside, drawing a moan from Erica as her lips parted around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” he exhaled. “Your pussy is so hot!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Erica gasped, as he lifted her ankles to his shoulders, and slipped deeper inside. “Yes! Your cock fills me up so good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie reached inside her robe, squeezing her breast and feeling the nipple tighten under her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, Max started moving his hips. Erica laid her head back, eyes closed. Her hands moved restlessly over the blanket, gripping it every time he pushed inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How about it, Rylie,” Max asked, “wanna touch yourself again? It turns me on to watch you rub your clit while I fuck your friend in front of you.” Erica moaned at this, and opened her eyes to see what Rylie would do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking in Erica’s lust-filled eyes, Rylie licked her lips. She slowly opened her robe and let it fall down. Max and Erica watched as she caressed her body, sliding her hands over her breasts and down her hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if, um,” She hesitated, then spoke quickly, before she lost her nerve. “I want to do more than just touch myself?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you want to do, Ry?” Erica asked, breathlessly, breasts bouncing in time with Max’s movements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to join in!” Rylie felt her face flush, but there was no stopping now. “I got &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; turned on, watching you all day.” She looked back and forth between Erica and Max, still not entirely sure who she meant. “But I can’t just watch anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, yes,” Erica exhaled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yeah,” Max growled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie dropped to her hands and knees and crawled forward. Erica moaned as their lips met. The upside-down kiss was filled with heat. Erica sucked on her bottom lip, and Rylie pushed her tongue between her lips. Then Max thrust forward energetically, shoving Erica back and breaking the kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She made a disappointed sound followed by a surprised gasp as Rylie started kissing down her neck. She crawled forward, over Erica’s body, lips dancing toward her breasts. Eagerly, she wrapped her lips around Erica’s nipple, flicking her tongue against the stiff bud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica moaned and squirmed as Max continued fucking her, and Rylie released one nipple to move to the other. Her breasts were hanging in Erica’s face, who reached up to cup and squeeze them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie shivered as Erica trapped her nipples between her fingers, rolling and pulling. She released Erica’s with a wet pop and glanced up at Max. He looked like he couldn’t believe his luck. He continued thrusting into Erica, but his eyes were locked on Rylie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica gasped as Rylie continued crawling forward, kissing down Erica’s body. She shivered with delight as Rylie’s lips brushed over her stomach, inching ever lower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie was tingling with excitement as she moved closer and closer to where Max’s cock was disappearing between Erica’s lips. She found herself panting with lust at the sight of Erica creaming around his shaft. Unable to draw it out any longer, she lunged forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica squealed as Rylie ran her tongue over her clit and along Max’s cock. The angle was awkward. She had to turn her head to keep from getting jostled out of the way as Max continued fucking Erica. He tried to lean back a bit, to change the angle and make it easier for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie eagerly lapped up the cream around the base of his cock, then teased her tongue over and around Erica’s lips, wanting more. Max groaned, and Erica squealed when Rylie’s tongue flicked against her clit. They quickly found a groove, with Rylie excitedly licking them both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then it was Rylie’s turn to gasp, as she felt Erica’s fingers exploring her pussy. She groaned, and wrapped her hand around the base of Max’s cock, slick in her grasp as he plunged in and out. When Erica slipped a couple of fingers inside, Rylie pulled Max out on the backstroke, and guided him between her lips instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” Max exclaimed as he unexpectedly found himself in the heat of her mouth. He didn’t slow down or calm his thrusting. If anything, he seemed to pick up the pace, trying to push deeper. Rylie moaned, feeling Erica’s fingers twisting inside, and tried to relax her throat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max shouted in triumph as he grabbed a handful of Rylie’s hair and pushed into her throat. She swallowed, trying not to gag, wanting to take him all the way. Erica lifted her head and wrapped her lips around Rylie’s clit, sucking as her fingers curled. Stars flared at the edges of her vision. All day, she’d been watching them fuck each other, and now they were both fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gasping and sputtering, Rylie was finally forced to push Max away, guiding him back into Erica, who cried out at suddenly being filled again. He frantically resumed fucking her, Rylie gasping at the sight of Erica’s pussy swallowing his throbbing cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She finally realized what she wanted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Max,” she panted. “Will you fuck me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” he grunted. “You know I’ve always wanted to!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, but you can’t cum inside me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where do you want me to cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want you to fuck me until you’re about to explode, then &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; Erica’s mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Erica squealed from between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, they changed positions, so Rylie was lying on her back with her legs spread. Max wasted no time, immediately burying his throbbing cock inside her. His thickness spread her open and filled her completely. She cried out at the overwhelming sensation. As he started fucking her, she felt her walls squeezing and gripping him tightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy fuck, Rylie,” Max moaned. “I don’t think I’m gonna last long!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait!” She begged, rubbing her clit. “Let me cum first!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica was kneeling to one side, watching with awe in her eyes. She had one hand between her thighs and the other was roughly tugging on her nipple. Rylie made eye contact with her, and she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Erica, you’re so sexy,” Rylie gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie!” Erica rocked in place, shamelessly masturbating for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pressure in her core was growing quickly. Max’s cock seemed to stimulate everywhere at once. Waves of sensation rippled from her pussy, tingling along her spine, and sparking at the edge of her vision. Her clit thrummed under her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she moaned, feeling the pressure build. “Max, keep fucking me! I’m gonna cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max dug his fingers into her thighs, and thrust with increased fervor. Her core tensed, and she felt a gush of release as her pussy clenched around his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Erica,” he grunted, trying to hold back. “Come here, I need you!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah!” She nearly threw herself forward, lying on her side, and resting her head on Rylie’s pelvis. Max thrust furiously, and Rylie felt his cock twitch, then begin throbbing. Erica opened her lips as Max pulled out of Rylie and buried himself in her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cumming!” He grunted, holding her head in place as he continued thrusting, fucking her mouth. “I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie’s own orgasm was still rippling as she watched Max use Erica for his pleasure. She moaned happily, swallowing and squirming, with a hand clamped between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy fuck,” Rylie gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a long moment, Max shuddered and pulled out of Erica’s mouth with a wet slurp. He staggered backwards to collapse into the armchair. His erection was finally beginning to soften.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erica shifted around until she could lay her head on Rylie’s shoulder. She hummed to herself in a satisfied way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie laughed, and pulled Erica closer, hugging her tightly. She giggled and threw a leg over Rylie’s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Erica, I…” Rylie trailed off. There was something important to say, but wasn’t sure how. Had she crossed a line? Was Erica okay? Did she feel the same attraction Rylie could no longer deny?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shhh,” she responded. “Everything’s fine, Ry. Relax.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about Max?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The fuckboy?” Erica laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I heard that,” Max protested groggily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You love it,” Erica teased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just,” Rylie worried, “I think I…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We can talk about it later.” Erica’s lips met hers in a soft kiss. “Because of you, I’m not going anywhere, remember?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” Rylie blinked, then slowly grinned as the tension bled away, replaced by a warm glow in her chest as Erica snuggled closer. “Yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Go Ask Your Girlfriend: and other erotic short stories</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/go-ask-your-girlfriend-ebook/"/>
		<published>2024-09-23T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-09-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/go-ask-your-girlfriend-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="first time" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="phone sex" />
    <category term="nudes" />
    <category term="sexting" />
    <category term="coworker" />
    <category term="quickie sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="facial" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="fingering" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/go-ask-your-girlfriend-ebook-TN1ylEed6--512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Go Ask Your Girlfriend!&lt;/em&gt;, author Ruby Pink brings you four steamy short stories about women who know what they want. “Meet Me in the Supply Closet” is about an illicit encounter in the office that isn’t what it first appears to be. “Whoops, Wrong Number” tells the story of a woman whose unintentionally seductive text turns into a memorable exchange. “Rainy Day at the Shop” is about two bored employees finding a way to entertain them selves on a slow day. And in the titular “Go Ask Your Girlfriend,” Heather agrees to teach Jimmy a few things about women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruby Pink loves reading erotica but was frustrated to find so many featuring shallow women with no agency. She took up the pen to bring us steamy shorts about real women who aren’t just props in male fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DHTBV91S"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>We Have to Be Quiet</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/we-have-to-be-quiet/"/>
		<published>2024-09-12T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-09-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/we-have-to-be-quiet/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="true" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="swallow" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/we-have-to-be-quiet-T_3jf6Bmwo-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It was four in the morning, and I was incredibly turned on. The room was dimly illuminated by starlight and the glowing green numbers on the alarm clock. I could hear rain spattering the window and the soft snores of a half-dozen of our friends. His hand was on my hip, and I could feel his warm breath on the back of my neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few hours ago, our group was ordering a final round at the bar. He and I had flirted before, but for some reason, tonight the spark ignited into a bonfire. We couldn’t take our eyes off each other. We sat side-by-side in a booth, perhaps a little closer than we needed to. I pressed my leg against his. He whispered jokes in my ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The party migrated to the studio apartment he shared with his roommate. Although their place was tiny, it was a conveniently close to the bar. Despite the short walk, we all got a bit wet in the rain. He loaned me a dry t-shirt, and when I peeled off my wet top in the bathroom, I left my bra hanging on the towel bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We sat together on his bed, smoked some weed and listened to some music. The vibe grew more chill. Everyone found a spot to settle on the floor or the little couch they’d managed to squeeze between two beds, dressers, and desks. I leaned against him as his roommate put on a movie, too distracted by the way he caressed my arm to pay much attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One by one, everyone else dozed off. When he finally turned off the TV, the room was plunged into darkness. We both shuffled out of our jeans, and climbed under his blanket by touch. There’s not much space on a twin bed, but we didn’t mind. He lay behind me, with one warm hand on my hip. His breath on the back of my neck sent shivers down my spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very slowly, he slid his hand down my thigh and back up. I leaned back against him invitingly. He started kissing my neck, and I’m not sure if I’ve ever been more aroused. When he lightly nibbled my earlobe, I squirmed, and his bed let out a warning creak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have to be quiet,” he breathed in my ear. I could only inhale shakily in reply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moved his other arm awkwardly, below my head and over my shoulder, to cup my breast. My nipple tightened under his palm, and I wished I had thought to take my shirt off, too. I slowly shifted against him, gratified to feel a growing firmness against my rear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reached behind me to grab his ass, though he needed no encouragement, and we could get no closer. His fingers teased along the waistband of my panties, and when he slipped under, I let out a breath I hadn’t realized I’d been holding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As quietly as I could, I moved my leg over his, spreading my thighs as he reached lower. His fingertips brushed over my trimmed hair, and my heart pounded with anticipation. When he discovered how wet I was, he squeezed my breast eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stifled a gasp as he pushed a long finger inside. We squirmed together as slowly as we could, trying to avoid the bed making any noise. His rapidly hardening cock throbbed, nestled between my cheeks. I turned my head, desperate to find his mouth. The angle wasn’t quite right to kiss, but we tried.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rolled my hips as he added another finger. He thrust against me a bit too enthusiastically, and the bed frame creaked. We froze momentarily as someone made a noise in their sleep, but his fingers never stopped working their magic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reached between our bodies and pushed my hand into his boxers. He let out a shuddering breath as I wrapped my fingers around him, squeezing and pulling. His shaft was swollen, and when I teased my fingertips along the sensitive ridge of his head, he shuddered and bit my shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way his fingers curled put pressure on my clit, which thrummed at his touch. I wanted badly to hump against his hand, to satisfy the growing need in my core. Instead, I bit my lip to avoid making any sound and rocked my hips as much as I dared. From the way he throbbed in my hand, I could tell he was struggling to hold back, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, I couldn’t take it anymore. As slowly as I could manage, I rolled over to face him. Our lips met with passion, subdued only by the need to avoid making noise. He pulled his fingers out and reached around to squeeze my ass as I wrapped both hands around his cock. I bit his lower lip as he thrust into my grip. He twitched, and I felt precum lubricate my palm. I eagerly rubbed it into his skin. His breathing was ragged when I finally broke our kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let me push him slowly onto his back, and I climbed on top, wincing with every creak of the mattress. I raised my shirt and shifted forward. He wasted no time taking my breasts in hand and wrapping his lips around my nipple. I shivered and bit my tongue to avoid crying out as his tongue swirled, sending sparks through my nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He squirmed below me as I shifted my weight. I was barely able to stifle a gasp as his tip prodded me. He lifted his hips to grind against me, excited by the contact. There was a growing need inside me, but I didn’t know if I could give into it without waking everyone in the room. With my breast in his mouth and his cock mashing against me, I could only rock in place, trying not to moan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All I wanted to do was shift our underwear out of the way and let him bury himself inside. God, it would feel so good. Just the thought sent a series of fluttering sensations through me. He thrust harder, as if hoping he could somehow tear through the thin fabric separating us. The mattress creaked ominously, and he squeezed my breasts hard enough to make me gasp. I rocked against him, shivering with desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, he released my nipple. He looked up at me, pleading, begging for more. He was getting close, I could tell. I held a finger to my lips. He nodded. Slowly, I scooted down between his legs. He watched with wide eyes as I tugged down his boxers to free his erection. I had soaked right through my underwear and his. He bit his lip as I ran my tongue up his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I wrapped my lips around his head, he pulled the pillow over his face to avoid making any noise. In the heat of my mouth, he twitched against my tongue. The only thing in the world I wanted at that moment was to make him cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sucked hard, gripping the base of his shaft. With my other hand, I cupped his balls and teased my fingernail against the sensitive skin below. His legs stiffened, and his head swelled in my mouth. I barely managed not to moan as he lifted his hips to thrust deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt him tap my shoulder and realized he was trying to warn me. Happily, I swirled my tongue faster, moving my hands, willing him to do it. His balls tightened, and I felt his shaft pulse right before his cum started filling my mouth. I was unable to avoid letting out a satisfied moan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I milked the final spurts from his throbbing cock, he shuddered and pulled away from my lips, overwhelmed. I swallowed, savoring how hard I’d made him cum, and slowly crawled back up into his arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As my heart rate slowed, and I calmed down enough to think about anything besides the heat of our bodies, I whispered in his ear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My apartment next time.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>The Queen of Marketing</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/queen-of-marketing/"/>
		<published>2024-09-09T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-09-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/queen-of-marketing/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="femdom" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="humiliation" />
    <category term="toe sucking" />
    <category term="step on cock" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="coworkers" />
    <category term="cfnm" />
    <category term="nylons" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/queen-of-marketing-1uVW4aEZit-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Christy was livid. She paced back and forth in her office, replaying the events of the meeting in her mind. Fucking James. He’d always been an insufferable prick, but now he was putting her team at risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pausing by the window, she tried to allow the familiar view of downtown to calm her. Dark clouds rolled overhead. Neon signs and streetlights reflected in the wet streets. Cars slowly crossed the bridge. She could be heading home, too, if it weren’t for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, Frank, the CEO, asked the department heads to prepare a twenty percent budget cut across the board. At first, she’d been concerned, but her plan was solid. A reduction to the Marketing team’s ad spend, some cost-cutting, and a few layoffs. Going into the meeting today, she’d felt confident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One by one, they’d gone around the table and somberly delivered proposals. Sales. Human Resources. Operations. No one wanted to let people go, but they all recognized the necessity. When Frank called on Marketing, she’d proudly done her duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then he turned to James and asked for the Engineering team’s plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can’t do it, Frank,” he said shamelessly. “I’m already short-staffed and underfunded. Engineering’s a finely tuned engine. I can’t just start cutting, it’ll fall apart.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The room fell silent. The other department heads looked shocked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“James, come on,” Frank sighed. “No one’s happy about it, but this is serious.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I get it.” He raised his hands helplessly. “But this is a &lt;em&gt;product&lt;/em&gt; company. No devs, no product.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Be realistic, man. What’s your proposal?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take it from Marketing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All eyes turned to Christy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carl, the VP of Sales—a thick-necked man in an ill-fitting suit—stifled a laugh. James grinned at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is this a joke to you?” She frowned. Carl had the decency to look chastened, but James just crossed his arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No joke,” he said. “Your department’s always been overfunded. Find some more fat to trim.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We already cut twenty percent, which puts our metrics at risk. Your team has the largest budget of the company by far!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Engineering has the largest budget for a reason. I need staff to build all the new features you put in ads without consulting me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our campaigns are drawn up months in advance! You decline every meeting invite, then have the nerve to say you weren’t consulted?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, &lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt; we go. The ‘Queen of Marketing’ assumes everyone should be at her beck and call!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My title,” Christy growled, “is vice president. It shouldn’t be hard to remember, it’s the same as yours.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not the same!” James scoffed. “I’m the VP of &lt;em&gt;Engineering&lt;/em&gt;. Without my team, the company folds. Without &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; team…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a budget crisis, you can’t just refuse to…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If &lt;em&gt;your highness&lt;/em&gt; would ever care to descend from the seventeenth floor, you’d see my devs struggling with outdated equipment, facing ridiculous demands…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s &lt;em&gt;enough&lt;/em&gt;!” Frank threw up his hands in frustration. “I can’t listen to this anymore.” He pinched the bridge of his nose. “It’s been a long day, and I’m exhausted. You two, stay. Everybody else, go home.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James and Christy glared at each other as the other department heads filed out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You will work together,” Frank said, raising a hand to cut off their objections, “and bring me a budget for &lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt; your teams that meets the overall reduction goal. I don’t care if it takes all night. Have it on my desk in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine,” James snarled. “I’ll be in my office. It’s on the third floor, in case your highness has forgotten where the &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; work gets done.” He stormed out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Frank, you can’t be serious,” she protested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know James can be difficult. But we need him.” He clapped her on the shoulder. “I also know you have a real knack for problem-solving. I trust you’ll find a way to resolve this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An hour later, she was glaring out the window in her office. Typical. Succeeding as a woman meant having to do your job twice as well as the men, and for a reward, you got to do their jobs, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How the hell was she going to get James to do his part? There was no reasoning with someone so convinced of his superiority. He’d never admit he was wrong because he couldn’t handle the humiliation. He’d dig in until someone forced him to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her eyes flicked to the garment bag hanging on the coat rack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone with more confidence and power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She unzipped the bag, and ran a fingernail over the black leather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone who could show him how pathetic he really was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come in,” James called when she knocked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She stepped in, closing the door behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s with the long coat?” He sneered. “You ready to head home? Gonna give up and admit I was right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hardly,” she responded, looking around his office disapprovingly. It was decorated like a dorm room. Shelves of tech gear of all sorts. Posters and printouts of comics plastered on the walls, peppered with nerdy stickers. Everything about the space was designed to make non-geeks feel out of place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In that case, welcome to where the magic happens.” His office chair was one of those ridiculous gamer chairs, red leather with cupholders and a headrest. “Have a seat,” he added, gesturing to an ugly couch that looked like he’d dragged it in off the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You humiliated me today, you know.” She said it calmly, hands in her coat pockets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, if the Queen can’t hack it in the boardroom, that’s just another reason to cut your team.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm,” she nodded slowly. “I thought you’d say something like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turned to his windows, facing the warren of cubicles that filled the rest of the floor. Despite the hour, there were still several devs out there. As she walked through, they were all playing video games or browsing social media. No one looked up as she closed the blinds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James looked confused when she locked the door, but before he could say something snarky, she opened her coat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His jaw dropped as he took in what she was wearing. Glossy black heels. Thigh-highs and garters paired with a mesh thong. Long black gloves that ended above the elbow. Her black leather corset left her breasts exposed, including a metal bar pierced through each nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You see, James, I know your type.” Ignoring his dumbfounded expression, she calmly draped her coat over a trolley filled with monitors. “A &lt;em&gt;small&lt;/em&gt; man who gets off on lording his knowledge over others.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sauntered around his desk, allowing her hips to sway, punctuating her words. He swiveled to face her, eyes wide as she stood over him. “You play your petty games and throw your childish tantrums because you believe you are better than your peers.” It was hard to say if he was more shocked by her outfit, or the way she carried herself while wearing it. “You assume the rules don’t apply to you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I—I, uh, that is…” He abruptly stood up and backed away from her, desperate to regain control of the situation, but unable to think straight. She followed him around the desk until he collapsed onto the couch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You think you are special,” she sneered, putting her foot against his crotch. “But when push comes to shove,” she pressed down hard, as if grinding out a cigarette butt, “you’ll collapse at my feet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, fuck!” He whimpered pathetically, too overwhelmed to resist. “Your heel… That hurts!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want me to stop?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Shit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you say?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She relaxed the pressure just a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you speak, you’ll address me properly. Use my title.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Vice president!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm,” she considered. “No, not here. In this context, I think you know what you should call me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Q—Queen?” He looked afraid to say it, fearing a trap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes.” She took her foot away. “That’s fitting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, um, what do you want?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She narrowed her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Queen! What do you want, um, Queen?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Better.” She turned her back and walked to his office chair. She grimaced as she sat down. It was stupidly uncomfortable, but claiming his throne was a message so clear even he would understand. “Start by taking off your clothes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked surprised. Before he could get the wrong idea, she gestured dismissively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t get excited, I have no interest in your pathetic body or flaccid prick. You simply haven’t earned the right to wear clothes around me yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yet? Uh, Queen?” He quickly removed his tie, dropped his clothes in the corner, and stood awkwardly in front of her, covering himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes. From now on, anytime I’m forced to be in your presence, unless other people are around, you will remain nude. Now, stop trying to cover yourself and kneel.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He swallowed nervously, and lowered himself to his knees. His cock twitched nervously, still soft, but threatening to grow. She refrained from smiling at just how quickly he’d surrendered total control to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her heart was pounding. He had no way of knowing, but this was the first time she’d ever acted on this fantasy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had a ritual. Before every department head meeting, she locked her office door and changed into this outfit. Then she masturbated while imagining the men kneeling and worshipping her. It gave her a secret, and more than once a man had backed down from a conflict, unable to face the odd confidence in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not James, of course. He’d always been oblivious. But now here he was, groveling before her for real! The rush of power left her practically breathless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You may remove my heels,” she announced, as though she were bestowing a great privilege upon him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He slipped them off and moved as though to toss them aside as carelessly as he’d discarded his clothing. But seeing her expression, he set them to one side with more reverence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good. Open your mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He hesitated a moment before parting his lips. Slowly, deliberately, she raised her nylon-covered foot. He looked pathetic as she rubbed it against his face, before finally pushing her toes into his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, &lt;em&gt;suck&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He frowned, but wrapped his lips around her big toe. It was awkward around the nylon, but she pushed deeper. He gagged a little, but swirled his tongue dutifully. His obedience caused a surge of heat between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fucking hell, she loved telling him what to do. Not wanting to get too worked up too quickly, she withdrew her toes. He scowled and looked away, flushed with humiliation as he wiped the drool from his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before he could react, she leaned forward and slapped him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wipe that scowl off your face! I’m doing you a favor. By rights, I should &lt;em&gt;destroy&lt;/em&gt; you. Do you realize how easily I could convince Frank to finally cut your worthless ass loose and hire a real man to replace you? After a few calls to my network, you’d be toxic. No one would hire you again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He rubbed his cheek, trying to determine if her threat was genuine. She allowed him to see the steel in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ve &lt;em&gt;badly&lt;/em&gt; misread the situation here. You saw me as a weak-willed little woman to push around. Now, you understand the truth. You continue to have a role here only because I choose to allow it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She saw the final spark of defiance die inside him. It sent a thrill down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think there’s something you should say, don’t you, James?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he stammered. “Th—Thank you, Queen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm. I’ll say this, you’re a quick learner.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, suddenly eager to please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she purred, leaning back and spreading her thighs. “You may continue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sight of him kissing his way up her legs was deeply arousing. She hissed with pleasure as she pulled on the bars in her nipples. His lips reached the top of her thigh-highs, brushing against her bare skin. Eagerly, she pulled her thong to one side, and spread her lips for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He paused at the sight of her bare pussy, dripping with excitement. He glanced up at her, and she nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it,” she commanded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He closed his eyes and lowered his face between her thighs. She bit her lip as he ran his tongue along the length of her. Timidly, he explored, barely dipping between her lips. He traced her folds and contours, hesitantly prodding, either unable or unwilling to commit fully. She growled with frustration as he circled her opening again and again without ever entering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t waste my time,” she warned, grabbing a fistful of his hair and mashing his face more firmly against her. He yelped in surprise, but finally, she felt him push inward. “Yes, like that,” she murmured, “deeper.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heart pounding, she rested her feet on his back, startled by how turned on she was. He wasn’t particularly skilled, but the power dynamic itself made her insides clench. She tugged harder on his hair, demanding more. He let out surprised little moans every time she squeezed around his tongue. She rubbed his nose against her clit, using his face like a toy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t stop,” she groaned, “don’t you dare stop.” He gasped wetly for breath, but she continued fucking his face. He grabbed her thighs, and she swatted his hands away. So many times, she’d imagined the sneering men in her life groveling at her feet, begging for the privilege of servicing her. Now it was happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt an orgasm approaching. It was absurd. She hated him. Found everything about his personality repugnant. But the way he submitted to her, allowed her to use him for her pleasure, left her quivering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her core clenched, and he sputtered as she gushed in his mouth. She kept her grip on his hair, forcing him to swallow. She groaned loudly enough to wonder if his staff could hear. He continued to work his tongue until she finally had to push him away when it became too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He rocked back, gasping for breath. She squeezed her thighs shut around her hand, pressing against her clit as aftershocks rippled through her core. He stared at her, awestruck, her wetness glistening on his chin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was so overwhelmed by the situation that it took her a long moment to realize he was frantically stroking his cock. Clearly, she wasn’t the only one turned on by his submission. His cockhead was swollen, and so dark red it was nearly purple. He stared wantonly at her as he masturbated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What. The fuck. Do you think? You’re doing.” She sat up and glared at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He startled, glancing down at his swollen prick, as if he hadn’t realized he was touching it. Quickly, he let go, and looked up at her with the same expression as a dog caught digging through the trash. His cock still throbbed desperately. As she watched, a large drop of precum leaked from the tip and fell to the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did I give you permission to touch yourself?” She got to her feet, adjusting her underwear back into place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, Queen!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then why are you rubbing your sad excuse for a cock at me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, Queen, I… I just… I didn’t think…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right, you didn’t think. You never do.” She glowered at him, hands on her hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked absurd. The hangdog expression on his face was completely at odds with the eager twitching of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not here for your sexual gratification, you fucking worm! You are &lt;em&gt;beneath&lt;/em&gt; me. Unworthy of me. If you so much as have a wet dream about me, you’d better wake up and beg forgiveness!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Queen!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you’re unable to control yourself in the future, you’ll need to be restrained. Is that clear?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Queen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She put her foot on his shoulder and forcefully pushed him backward until he lay on his back on the rough carpet. It looked uncomfortable, but his erection still jutted hopefully upward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think you’ve forgotten that I have a job to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked up at her, utterly bewildered. Her domination was so complete that he’d forgotten the reason she’d come to his office in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The budget, James.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Right… Queen?” A reminder of their professional roles while lying nude on the floor was clearly confusing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How much can Engineering cut?” As she asked, she put her foot on his cock. It throbbed eagerly, mistaking the stimulation as sexual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… I can’t… We need—ah!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He cried out as she pressed down hard. It twitched once, and another squirt of precum drooled out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fifteen—oh god!—Fifteen percent, Queen?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s a good start, James, but I think you can do better.” She ground her heel mercilessly against the base of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Twenty! Twenty percent, Queen!” He groaned and squirmed, clawing at the carpet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s good, James, I’m glad we could reach… Oh, for fuck’s sake!” As soon as she removed her foot, his cock started spraying cum all over his stomach. He whimpered and writhed as he climaxed uncontrollably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You really are fucking worthless, aren’t you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” he panted. “Yes, Queen,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shaking her head, she stepped into her heels, and put on her coat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Clean yourself up. I expect your budget proposal before you go home tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Truth or Dare: A Threesome Erotic Romance</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/truth-or-dare-ebook/"/>
		<published>2024-09-07T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-09-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/truth-or-dare-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="pussy eating" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="spanking" />
    <category term="ffm" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="roommates" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/truth-or-dare-Ud5eTuKD_g-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;When the party ended, the only ones left were Julie, her roommate Alice, and their friend Dan. The room was flooded with romantic tension, but she could tell nothing was going to happen unless she got involved. When Julie suggests a game of Truth or Dare, will Dan and Alice follow her lead to a night the three of them will never forget?&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DGDM1C4V"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed: Only One Bed: The Complete Box Set</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/only-one-bed-box-set/"/>
		<published>2024-09-01T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-09-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/only-one-bed-box-set/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="vacation sex" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-bundle-5TgLN8PZgC-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Emma couldn’t believe it. The tropical vacation she’d been looking forward to all year was here! After three years apart, she was reunited with her friends Zoya and Liam… Plus Liam’s handsome surfer cousin, Nolan. But now a problem with the reservations will force the four of them to share a room with just one bed. Will this be a disaster… or the start of the best vacation ever?&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DFVHNRVQ"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 4: Best Vacation Ever!: Only One Bed, Book 4</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/4-best-vacation-ever/"/>
		<published>2024-08-25T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/4-best-vacation-ever/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="vacation sex" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-4-TSicI4GwBP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Emma never would have guessed that being forced to share a room with only one bed on a tropical vacation with her friends would lead to her hooking up with all three. Now, together with hunky surfer Nolan and his cousin Liam, Emma is waiting to find out what her best friend Zoya has planned for their last night together to make this the best vacation ever!&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DF6PJBCF"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 3: Let’s Trade!: Only One Bed, Book 3</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/3-lets-trade/"/>
		<published>2024-08-17T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/3-lets-trade/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="vacation sex" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-3--i5hAcsPGk-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Emma’s tropical vacation with her friends hasn’t exactly gone according to plan, but she can’t complain. Forced to share a room with only one bed led her to make a passionate connection with hunky surfer Nolan, and her best friend Zoya hooked up with Nolan’s cousin Liam. Things were going really well until she discovers Liam fantasizing about her in the shower. She expected the Zoya would be upset, but she only laughed and suggested they trade guys. Will Emma be able to follow Zoya’s lead to make this the best vacation ever?&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CTHRTWYW"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Are Those My Underwear?</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/are-those-my-underwear/"/>
		<published>2024-08-16T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/are-those-my-underwear/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="facesitting" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="panty sniffing" />
    <category term="panty thief" />
    <category term="payback" />
    <category term="control" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/are-those-my-underwear-vsx1ybfhSn-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Woah, what the &lt;em&gt;fuck&lt;/em&gt;, dude?” Rachel stood in the doorway to her room, towel-drying her hair and unable to believe what she saw. Her roommate’s boyfriend was reclining on her bed, pants around his ankles, rubbing his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, do you mind?” Norm responded shamelessly, without stopping. “I’m mid-stroke, here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do I mind?” She sputtered, genuinely at a loss for words. “Are those my fucking underwear?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he moaned, holding them to his nose and inhaling deeply. “They smell great.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What the fuck are you doing here? Where’s Laurel?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She picked up a shift at the bar. Left me here high and horny, so I figured I’d squeeze one out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not asking why you’re here in the apartment,” she said through gritted teeth. “You’re &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; fucking here. I mean, why the &lt;em&gt;fuck&lt;/em&gt; are you jerking off in my room?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Duh, that’s where your dirty laundry is. Hey, can you stop swearing so much? It’s a real turn-off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For fuck’s sake, Norm!” She threw her hair towel on the floor and stomped her foot. “I told Laurel you were a loser, but this is a new low.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t say new,” he chuckled, oblivious to her anger. “I do this all the time! It’s just that, usually, I finish before you get out of the shower.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Will you fucking &lt;em&gt;stop&lt;/em&gt; rubbing yourself in front of me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can’t do it, man.” He took another whiff and sighed. “Sorry you had to see this, but I’m building up to a monster climax. If you just leave for a few minutes, I can finish and get out of your way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re not ‘in my way!’ You’re jerking off in my fucking bed!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t be dramatic, I’m not &lt;em&gt;in&lt;/em&gt; your bed, I’m &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; your bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, is this why all my goddamn underwear keep disappearing? You’ve been taking them to jerk off with?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah, your panties smell &lt;em&gt;unreal&lt;/em&gt;. That scent gets me so hard. And when I put them around my cock like this?” He sighed as he wrapped the satin fabric around his head and continued stroking. “It feels amazing, especially the silky ones.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking gross! And why mine? You’re dating Laurel, use hers!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, hers are all cheap cotton. The elastic chafes. Plus, they don’t smell as good as yours.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop fucking talking about how good I smell!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jeez, learn to take a compliment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that why you steal them? Do you keep them stashed away somewhere to sniff?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, I just throw them out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You… You fucking what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“After I cum in your panties, I toss ’em.” He sighed, switched hands, and kept stroking. “I mean, I thought about putting them back in your laundry basket, but I figured you’d notice the spunk, get pissed, and start yelling at me, like you are now. Seemed easier for everyone to just put your panties in the garbage.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, first, &lt;em&gt;stop&lt;/em&gt; saying that fucking word.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, panties?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” she shuddered. “I hate it. And second, those underwear cost money!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Eh, you can afford it. You got that hot-shot advertising job.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m a part-time intern!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Same diff.” He shrugged. “But fine, I guess now that you know, in the future I can just put them back in the dirty laundry when I’m done.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re missing the goddamn point here, Norm!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, maybe you can explain it later? You’re kinda killing my boner.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m killing your boner? Are you fucking serious?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. Can you step out and give me, like, fifteen minutes, tops?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fifteen…!” Rachel took a deep breath before she did something she’d have a hard time explaining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fucking guy was unbelievable. He was always here, eating all their food, smoking all their weed, and scratching himself on the couch. She couldn’t understand what Laurel saw in him. Well, no. Clearly, what she saw in him was surprisingly girthy and currently wrapped in Rachel’s favorite black satin hipsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What made things worse was the increasingly hard-to-deny undercurrent of arousal beneath her anger. Her heart was pounding, and she was undeniably livid, but some part of her limbic system was responding inappropriately to the intensity of the situation. She crossed her arms over the thin fabric of her nightshirt, not wanting him to see how hard her nipples had become.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was so stupid. She hated him and the fact that he genuinely seemed not to understand why she’d be upset. How could he not get that what he was doing was a violation? She wanted to scream and throw things at him. He looked at her with that dumb expression, as if &lt;em&gt;she’d&lt;/em&gt; somehow intruded on &lt;em&gt;him&lt;/em&gt;. Asking her to step out? Outrageous! She wanted to shut him up. She wanted to cover his mouth until he couldn’t breathe, to see his eyes widen in alarm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wanted to &lt;em&gt;smother&lt;/em&gt; him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had an idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Norm, how many pairs of my underwear have you thrown out over the two years you and Laurel have been dating?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jeez, can this really not wait? I guess like twenty or twenty-five?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Twenty-fucking-five?” The number was shockingly high. That meant twenty-five times, he’d snuck into her room. Twenty-five times, he jerked off with her underwear. Twenty-five times, he threw them out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Give or take,” he shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her cheeks burned with humiliation. She’d noticed, of course, but it had happened slowly enough, she’d chalked it up to the landlord’s cheap laundry machines eating them. Just one of those things, like how socks disappear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell,” she frowned, doing the math, “that’s, like, five hundred bucks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Woah, panties are expensive!” He chortled. “I can get a six-pack of boxers for twenty!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, they’re not cheap!” She laughed mirthlessly. “Especially because there’s only one brand that fits my hips right.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That sucks, man.” He was clearly losing interest, and hoping she’d leave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, it does.” She waited a beat. “So, how are you gonna pay me back?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Twenty-five pairs of underwear. Twenty bucks each. That’s five hundred dollars you owe me, asshole.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Woah, I mean, let’s not…” His hand paused on his cock. “I mean, that was just an estimate, it’s probably less, and, uh, I don’t have much cash flow right now…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because you’re a loser with no job who hangs out here all day?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not my fault! The economy’s terrible, and no one’s…” He laughed. “Oh! You’re joking! Man, you had me going there, Rachel. Five hundred bucks! You’re funny.” He raised her underwear to his face again and inhaled deeply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, since you don’t have any money to pay me back with…” She abruptly pulled her shirt off over her head and stood before him, fully nude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I appreciate the thought,” he frowned, “but I don’t really need any help? I was already on my way to a killer orgasm before you came in. And not to be rude, but you’re not exactly my type.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not your type? You’re literally huffing my underwear!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing personal,” he shrugged. “Your tits are okay, and I guess I wouldn’t mind looking at them while I jerk off, but that full bush you’re rocking is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking… I’m not stripping for your benefit, dumbass! You owe me a lot of goddamn money.” She climbed onto the bed. “And if you can’t pay, you’ll have to work off your debt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How?” He looked genuinely confused as she moved closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, since you like smelling my underwear so much, I’m going to sit on your face.” With that, she grabbed the headboard and swung her leg over to straddle his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have you never heard of trimming…” He started saying, but the rest was muffled as she covered his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There we go,” she grinned, looking down at his shocked eyes. “Finally, you stop talking!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmph!” He shook his head and grabbed at her hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up and eat me. The only reason Laurel keeps you around is because you make her cum. Well, you better get me off just as good, if you’re gonna cover this debt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Aaarrmmph!” He slapped her ass with obvious frustration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, spicy!” Rachel laughed and rocked in place, grinding her vulva against his closed mouth. “I don’t mind a spanking, but that’s not gonna make me cum. And if you don’t get started, I’m worried you might pass out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Buhmmmph!” He protested, brows furrowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I know you use your cock to make Laurel cum,” she nodded. “But I’m not interested in your dick. You wanna sniff my underwear? Here you go! Straight to the source! Have all you can take.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stopped struggling, seeming to consider his position for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, Norm. If you think I smell good, why don’t you see what I &lt;em&gt;taste&lt;/em&gt; like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tentatively, he parted his lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s it,” She shivered as he took his first, cautious licks, easing between her folds. “Just like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He lifted his chin, exploring her with more confidence. As he spread her open, his eyes opened wide with surprise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you taste me now, don’t you?” She laughed, giddy with the rush of power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted in agreement, and began licking deeper and faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Keep going, there’s more cream in there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he licked with more enthusiasm, her arousal grew quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she gasped. “Put that annoying tongue of yours to good use. Get my juices flowing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grabbed her hips, more confidently this time. She gasped as he pulled her closer. She’d already been inappropriately turned on, and now that she’d taken charge of the situation, her libido was in overdrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Deeper, now, fuck me with your tongue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled her hips, grinding against his face. The sight of her wetness glistening on his nose and cheeks made her insides clench.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is what you wanted, right? A face full of my pussy? My honey in your mouth, my scent in your nose?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His eyes rolled back in his head, and he moaned in agreement. She leaned forward, shifting the pressure, using his dumb face to stimulate herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck, it feels good when you move your head like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He enthusiastically shook his head from side to side, rubbing his nose against her clit. She moaned, feeling the pressure building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Keep going, keep going, keep—ah!—going!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He made urgent little noises, staring up at her with hungry eyes. She groaned and bucked her hips against his face. He let go of her hip and she felt a rhythmic movement behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you touching yourself again, you—uh—little creep? Can’t even keep your hand off your—ah!—dick when you’ve got a mouthful of pussy. Well, remember, you—oh!—got a job to do. Don’t—ah!—lose focus. I’m getting close!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d never spoken like this before. Never &lt;em&gt;demanded&lt;/em&gt; what she needed. It made her feel powerful. The words poured out of her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is all you’re fucking good for. You’re gonna work off—ah—what you owe me. I’m gonna ride your face—oh!—and drown you in my cum every night. You’re mine now, asshole. And if Laurel—ah!—doesn’t like it, that’s too fucking bad!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gripped the headboard tighter. Guys had gone down on her before, but she’d never really allowed herself to enjoy it. She was always holding back, afraid of overdoing it somehow. Now, she didn’t care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Faster… Fucking—ah!—faster! I’m gonna flood your fucking mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She ruthlessly fucked herself against his face, unconcerned with whether he could breathe, or even if she hurt him. This was about her needs now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, here I cum,” she moaned. “Open wide, swallow what I give you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squealed as her insides clenched rapidly in a sudden and overwhelming release. He sputtered and choked as she gushed in his mouth. Ignoring his reaction, she continued to rub her sensitive pussy against his tongue and mouth and nose. Wave after wave of pleasure rolled through her system, leaving her breathless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, he tensed, and his eyes rolled back in his head. Something hot and wet splattered against her lower back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Gross, you just came all over my ass, you creep!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He could only moan in response, eyes still rolled back with pleasure. Even through his orgasm, he never stopped working his tongue between her lips, lapping up her juices. Her annoyance receded as her arousal began to climb again. Now that she was on the plateau, it wouldn’t take much…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was a good start.” She looked down at him and growled. “Maybe worth ten bucks off your debt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tried to protest, but she ground her pelvis tightly against his mouth to drown him out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up. Keep going, I want to see if I can do it agai—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bedroom door opened. They’d been too distracted, and hadn’t heard Laurel come home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rachel, have you seen…” She stopped abruptly and squealed in shock. “What the fuck? Why are you…? Is that cum? What the &lt;em&gt;fuck&lt;/em&gt;, you guys!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked up at her with panic in his eyes. She didn’t move. He tried to say something, squirming below her, but she kept him pinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Laurel!” She called cheerily over her shoulder. “Sit down, I have to tell you what your loser boyfriend has been up to, and how he’s going to make it up to me.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Relieving the Tension</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/relieving-the-tension/"/>
		<published>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/relieving-the-tension/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="straight sex" />
    <category term="coworkers" />
    <category term="sexual tension" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/relieving-the-tension-GHaOLxrfqk-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“We have to do something about this sexual tension,” I said, stretching my back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” His eyes snapped guiltily to my face. He’d been staring at my chest. “Sorry, what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our presentation is tomorrow, and I can’t think straight around you right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh?” He regarded me curiously. I suspected this was the first time he’d ever been propositioned by a woman. He was attractive enough, and good at his job, but clearly uncomfortable spending so much time alone with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company had flown us out a few days before the big client meeting so we could meet our contacts face-to-face and build rapport. We had separate hotel rooms, but my seniority meant I got a larger suite, which we’d set up as our base of operations. He slept in his room, but otherwise, for three straight days, we’d spent every hour together refining our pitch deck. We really only left the room for dinner and drinks with the clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure what started the tension growing. Perhaps it was a subliminal thing. The entire time we were working from the sofa, my bed was in sight. Or maybe it was our physical proximity. Sitting so close together, it was impossible to avoid little moments of contact. My hand would brush against his, reaching for a pen. His leg would press against mine as he showed me something on his screen. I even became familiar with his scent…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong. He was perfectly respectful, aside from some difficulty keeping his eyes out of my cleavage. But after three days, I found myself wishing he’d be &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; respectful. My career has always been my priority, which doesn’t leave much room for chasing physical attraction. But the smoldering heat between us was difficult to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I knew he desired me. At one point, I had to plug my phone in, and unintentionally gave him a view down my shirt. When I looked up, he quickly turned away, and his face turned bright red.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, I had to be certain, so this morning, I’d answered the door in my workout gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on in and get started. I just need a quick rinse.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He did his best not to stare at my nipples poking through my sports bra, or ogle the way my tights hugged my ass. Even so, I swayed my hips as I disappeared into the bathroom, confident he was watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After my shower, I casually walked out wrapped in a towel. He looked up from his laptop, wide-eyed and flustered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, I forgot these,” I said, grabbing the lacy panties and bra I’d left on the bed. By the time I reappeared fully dressed (with my blouse unbuttoned a bit lower than I would at the office), he seemed quite distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, here we were, the evening before our big presentation, and the tension was palpable. We’d had drinks with the client and came back to my room to make some last-minute changes to the pitch deck. But he could barely keep his eyes off me, and I was having trouble not losing myself in fantasies of pushing him down on the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can’t think straight around me?” His expression said he wasn’t quite allowing himself to believe me. “Because of sexual tension?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right. And I think you feel the same way.” I scooted closer to him, until our thighs were touching, and draped my arm over the back of the sofa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he swallowed. “I suppose that’s true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If we don’t do something,” I said, tracing my finger down the buttons on his shirt, “we’ll be distracted tomorrow. We’ll mess up the pitch, and lose out on the deal. I don’t want that. Do you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No. No, but, uh, what do you have in mind?” He shifted nervously, his erection starting to swell to life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think,” I whispered, “we should get undressed…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes?” He shivered with anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Move over to the bed…” I slid my hand up his thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll suck your &lt;em&gt;cock&lt;/em&gt;…” I purred, squeezing him through his slacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ahhh!” His shaft throbbed under my touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ll lick my clit…” I squeezed my thighs together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then I’m going to get on top and ride you until we both &lt;em&gt;cum&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock twitched urgently, and he stood up quickly, fumbling with his belt. I smiled and sauntered toward the bed, unzipping my skirt and letting it fall to the floor, quickly followed by my blouse. He trailed after, shedding his clothes. I pulled his arms around me and encouraged him to kiss my neck. He fumbled with my bra, but at last the straps slid down my arms, and I tossed it toward my bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He lowered his head to my chest, and eagerly licked my nipples. I inhaled at the sensation, and pulled him closer. He awkwardly shuffled out of his underwear, and I felt his erection bumping against my hip as I pulled him back up into a kiss. His hands explored my body, making my skin tingle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I pushed him back onto the bed. He shuffled higher, cock swaying as he went. I crawled after him, making eye contact and licking my lips. He watched, enthralled, as I licked up the full length before taking him into my mouth. When I began to swirl my tongue around the tip, he gasped, and I tasted his precum. I moaned eagerly and started bobbing my head, taking him deeper. He put a hand on my shoulder, encouraging me as he began to lift his hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wave of lust crashed over me, making my toes curl. His heat filled my mouth, and I wanted more. He cried out as I sucked harder. His thrusting grew more urgent, and he squeezed my shoulder. My insides clenched as I finally swallowed him, taking him into my throat. He groaned loudly as my lips met the base of his shaft. I held him there as long as I could, until my eyes watered, only backing off when I was about to choke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I gazed up at him, gasping for breath, a string of drool stretching between my lips and the tip of his twitching cock. He growled hungrily and rolled me over onto my back. I lifted my hips to allow him to remove my underwear, then spread my legs wide for him. I felt the weight of his gaze on my pussy, and reveled in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gave me a crooked smile, and then lowered himself between my thighs. He spread me open with two fingers and lapped between my lips, eager to taste me. I arched my back and gasped as he explored every fold, until his tongue pushed deep inside. He looked up at me over my mound, nose pressed against my clit, eyes full of hunger. I could only squeal and grasp the sheets as he devoured me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, I couldn’t take any more. I needed him. I pushed him away and rolled shakily to my knees. He grinned and lay down on his back, ready for me. His cock, still glistening with my saliva, throbbed and twitched against his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, I climbed on top, hands on his shoulders, and sighed as I slipped along the length of his shaft. He seemed as hard as iron against my soft, swollen lips, which parted eagerly for him. I allowed myself to savor the feeling, grinding and sliding against him, letting the anticipation build.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and reached for my breasts. I leaned into his grasp, encouraging him to massage and squeeze. My nipples tightened under his touch, and I squeezed my thighs around him. He was lifting his hips now, humping against me, pulling back further, desperate to bury himself in my heat. I shivered as my body seemed to contract, waves of sensation rolling between my breasts and my clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I rocked back, reached down to position him, and allowed him to thrust inside. He cried out, and squeezed my tits hard, making me gasp and clench around his cock. I dug my fingernails into his shoulders and rolled my hips, changing the pressure. He stared up at me with eyes full of lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, I started rocking back and forth, savoring the way he filled me. He panted and rolled my nipples between his fingers. I moaned long and low, gradually increasing the pace. He was firm and unyielding, deep inside, and my pussy grasped and pulled, alternately trying to bring him deeper and push him out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we moved faster, the room filled with the sound of his prick thrusting into my cunt. I shuddered and bucked, tossing my hair and yelping uncontrollably. He grunted and growled, muttering curses under his breath. He stiffened, legs going rigid, about to cum…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I slapped him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His eyes opened wide in shock, but his legs relaxed. Barely able to form words, I tried to tell him, not yet, that I needed more. I don’t know if he understood. He couldn’t answer because I had shoved my fingers in his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt my climax building, as if I was climbing a hill. Rocking back and forth on his swollen cock, the pressure built slowly. I felt myself grow tighter around him, every sensation amplified. He was buried deep inside, and I could feel every inch. My vision dimmed, my entire world narrowing to the feeling of him inside me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rode him hard and fast, fucking him until I saw colors. My thighs squeezed, my nails dug deeper. He groaned in protest, and I leaned against his hands on my tits as my orgasm crashed around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A gush of hot wetness around the base of his cock. Clenching and throbbing that seemed to start in my chest and roll down my spine around his shaft. Someone was crying out, embarrassingly loud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted around my fingers, and shook his head, trying to speak. Still savoring the lingering contractions, I pulled my hand away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m gonna cum! Oh fuck, I’m gonna cum so hard,” he blurted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, do it,” I growled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He went rigid again, and I felt his cock twitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, I jumped off and spun around, taking him into my mouth. He tasted strongly of my pussy. Immediately, he exploded, pumping his spunk against my tongue, mixing our flavors together. I looked up and met his eyes, letting him watch as I squeezed and sucked, milking out every last drop. His body rocked with each diminishing spurt, until at last, he lay still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of swallowing, I opened my mouth, letting his cum run out, pooling at the base of his shaft. He gasped at the sight, and I wrapped my lips around the tip for one last spurt, which I did swallow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally spent, he collapsed, panting for breath, as I lay my head on his hip and absent-mindedly ran my fingers through the sticky mess we’d made. I felt utterly and completely satiated. With the tension released, I could finally think straight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm,” I agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shower, maybe room service. Get some sleep, then the presentation tomorrow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh, I meant between us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” I said. To be honest, it hadn’t occurred to me until that very moment that there might be anything between us beyond the immediate need. “Well, we seem to make a good team. You take direction well. I suppose it depends on how good a job we do with the presentation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” He nodded to himself. “Right, the presentation. Then we’ll see.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see,” I agreed, smiling to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 2: Taking it Further: Only One Bed, Book 2</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/2-taking-it-further/"/>
		<published>2024-08-11T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/2-taking-it-further/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="vacation sex" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-2-zUfUX_gZYR-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;When Emma found out that she and her three friends would have to share a room with just one bed, she was convinced it would ruin their tropical vacation. However, the close quarters had unexpected benefits, and she surprised herself by fooling around with hunky surfer Nolan. That passionate moment was memorable, but despite her best friend Zoya’s encouragement, Emma isn’t sure if she should take things further. Will she push Nolan away, or take things further and make this the best vacation ever?&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DCTZTJZD"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Go Ask Your Girlfriend!</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/go-ask-your-girlfriend/"/>
		<published>2024-08-10T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/go-ask-your-girlfriend/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="first time" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="instruction" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="missionary" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/go-ask-your-girlfriend-f6d9U2mE_e-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Thank you so much, Heather,” Jimmy’s mom apologized as they stood on the porch. “I know it’s a bit unusual, but obviously, at Jimmy’s age, we couldn’t call any of his old sitters.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry,” Heather reassured her. “I’m happy to keep an eye on him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ve had these tickets for months, but Jack was talking about canceling! When Karen mentioned you were home for the summer, it seemed like a perfect fit. I remembered Jimmy and your younger brother were friends, and how you used to drive them to the mall after you got your driver’s license. You were always so responsible…” She trailed off as the shouting from inside got louder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is bullshit!” Jimmy stomped down the stairs after his father. “I graduated last week. I don’t need a babysitter!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“After the shit you pulled…” Jimmy’s dad pinched his nose and turned to face his son. “Trust is &lt;em&gt;earned&lt;/em&gt;, kiddo. And you’ve lost ours, at least for now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh!” Jimmy threw his hands in the air and stormed off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry about that, Heather,” Jimmy’s dad sighed. “He’ll calm down. Here’s some money for delivery. Make yourself at home. We’ll be back around eleven.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take your time,” she smiled, tucking the cash into her hoodie pocket and waving as they climbed in the car. She closed the front door and followed the sound of banging cabinets to the kitchen, where Jimmy was rummaging for snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Trust is earned,” he muttered in a mocking tone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up, Jimmy,” Heather said, trying to keep the amusement from her voice. She’d only been at university for two years, but these teenage dramatics already seemed like the distant past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Heather.” He scowled while devouring a granola bar. “He’s &lt;em&gt;totally&lt;/em&gt; overreacting, you know. It was just a party! No reason to treat me like a child.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“From what I heard, that party got shut down by the cops. I’m not surprised he’s pissed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How’d &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; hear about it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A few guys from my dorm told me. They came back to town that weekend for a game, heard about a party, and decided to crash it. They were like, ‘you should have seen these high school kids going buck wild!’ I mean, damn, Jimmy,” she teased, “I can’t believe the shy kid I knew from photography class threw a rager!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It wasn’t that wild,” he grinned, trying to play it cool, but clearly pleased by her reaction. “A couple of broken windows. Someone puked in the pool. The cops only showed up because the music was too loud.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sure,” she laughed. “Look, man, I get this is weird, but I’m just here to make sure you don’t burn the place down or whatever. I’ll order some pizza and watch a movie. You can hang with me or do your own thing. No big deal, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, okay,” he sighed. “Not your fault my dad’s a dick.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of hours later, they were sitting together on the couch, with the remains of a pizza on the coffee table. Jimmy seemed noticeably more relaxed after eating. Heather was only half paying attention to the movie. Her phone kept buzzing with messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who are you talking to?” Jimmy asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A guy from school.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anyone I know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” she chuckled. “You don’t know him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you guys dating?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dating?” She raised an eyebrow. “No, we just hang out sometimes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool,” he nodded. “Cool, cool, cool.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes passed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So,” Jimmy asked with studied casualness, “what are you guys talking about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why do you want to know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, it’s gotta be more interesting than this weird French chick flick.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey,” she protested, “I like this movie!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ve seen it before?” He looked baffled. “Why’d you put it on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It makes me happy. I like watching them fall in love.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy rolled his eyes, but returned to the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long, her phone buzzed again. She read the message, laughed, and typed out a reply. When she looked up, Jimmy was watching her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“C’mon, tell me what you sent. This movie is boring and I hate subtitles.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s about to get to the best part.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sure they’ll kiss under a rainbow or some shit. What’d you send?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You really want to know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, tell me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine. I said I’d give him a blow job next time I see him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Uh… Cool.” Obviously flustered, he turned away. She tried not to laugh at how red he turned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next scene was her favorite. The leading man realized he’d been an idiot and confessed his love for the heroine. She admitted to herself that she loved him as well, and they fell into a passionate embrace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music swelled, and Heather smiled, imagining herself in the heroine’s place, pressing her body against his, feeling his lips on hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The leading man’s shirt fell to the floor, and the heroine traced her fingers over his bare chest. He removed her bra, and she gasped as he kissed her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy kept glancing in Heather’s direction. She crossed her legs, suddenly aware of both how short her skirt was and how long the scene was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heroine moaned as the leading man lowered her onto the bed. She arched her back as he moved lower, until only his tousled hair was visible between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy shifted awkwardly, and pulled a pillow into his lap. Heather bit her lip. She didn’t remember the movie being this explicit, and now she felt a little guilty for making that blowjob comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The leading man moved behind the heroine as she rolled onto her hands and knees. He thrust forward, and she cried out, gripping the sheets as they started moving together. Her breasts swayed, erect nipples dragging against the silk sheet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather shivered, imagining the sensation, and crossed her arms over her chest. Jimmy met her eyes for a moment, and quickly looked away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heroine climaxed, calling the leading man’s name as he moaned and collapsed on top of her. They rolled into a loving kiss as the credits rolled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” Jimmy said calmly. “That movie was pretty good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They both dissolved into laughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh man,” she said, wiping tears from her eyes. “That was a lot steamier than I remembered.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I see why you like it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; why I like it!” She threw a pillow at him, which knocked away the one in his lap. “Looks like you did, though.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I, uh…” He trailed off as he followed her gaze to the rather obvious erection tenting his shorts. “Ack!” He grabbed for one of the pillows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At ease, Jimbo.” She winked. “No need to salute.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry! Sorry.” His face had turned bright red with embarrassment. She felt bad for him, honestly. Teenage boys popped a boner if you looked at them funny, and she’d just made him sit next to her through a seriously hot sex scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it had affected her, too, because she couldn’t help noticing Jimmy had really grown into himself. Last time she’d seen him, he was all elbows and knees, gangly as a colt. Now his shoulders were broader, and he seemed to have filled in a bit. She found herself imagining moving closer, reaching into his shorts to wrap her hand around…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you, um…” She shook her head, banishing the thought. “Do you need to go take care of that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!” He answered a bit too loudly, then took a breath. “I mean, no, I just need a minute.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suit yourself.” She smiled, hoping he’d see that she wasn’t teasing him. “If it were me, I wouldn’t be able to think straight until I took matters in my own hands, if you know what I mean.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s fine, it’ll go…” He stopped mid-sentence and looked at her curiously. “What &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; you mean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, tickling my fancy?” Jimmy still looked confused. “Beating around the bush? Buttering my muffin?” She grinned and waggled her eyebrows. “Rubbin’ my nubbin? Flicking the bean?” His expression made her laugh. “C’mon, &lt;em&gt;masturbating&lt;/em&gt;, man!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girls masturbate?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yeah?” It was her turn to look confused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” He hesitated for a long moment. “How?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jeez, man,” she hesitated. “Ask your girlfriend.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh, don’t really have a girlfriend.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, whatever you want to call it,” she rolled her eyes. “The girl you’re fooling around with.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked awkward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” she realized. “Nobody? Not even at your big party?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not even, like, a handy in the pool?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He cleared his throat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, shit, I’m sorry about that. But come on, didn’t they cover this kinda stuff in health class?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They were more focused on trying to scare us about pregnancy and diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right. But you’ve got the internet. You’ve never watched a girl masturbate in porn?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought all that stuff was fake.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re not wrong,” she conceded. “Well, don’t stress. You’re a good-looking guy who’s heading off to university soon. I’m sure you’ll meet a girl you like, and you can ask her stuff like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh!” Jimmy groaned. “That’s &lt;em&gt;exactly&lt;/em&gt; what I’m worried about! I’m gonna look like an idiot. I didn’t even know girls masturbated!” He turned abruptly to face her, accidentally flinging the pillow to the floor. “You gotta help me, Heather!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? Help you, &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt;?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Teach me about girls so I don’t humiliate myself!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather blushed. Jimmy’s erection was twitching shamelessly in his shorts, but his expression was guileless and hopeful. Once again, her mind drifted easily into imagining Jimmy gasping in her cleavage as she stroked his shaft…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um…” She blinked, trying to clear her mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, please! I really need your help. College girls aren’t gonna want to fool around with a virgin!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, wait, wait, slow down.” She stood up and pointed at him. “I am &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; hooking up with you. You get that, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that’s fine! Just show me some stuff so I don’t get laughed at.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just show you some stuff.” She considered. “Like, how a girl masturbates?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anything, Heather, please!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turned away from him. This was crazy. She should tell him to go take a cold shower. Then she could step outside and catch her breath until the embers of arousal in her core cooled down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand… He wasn’t wrong. He’d go off to college and meet some girl who liked him, and rub her the wrong way. Literally! Plus, if she showed him a few things, it wasn’t just helping him, it was like doing a favor to all the women he hooked up with in the future. She’d be paying it forward! Hell, it was practically her duty to her fellow women to show this poor clueless boy what was what.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” She nodded to herself and glanced at the clock. His parents wouldn’t be home for another couple hours. “Okay,” she repeated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just, like, give me a second.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached under her skirt, and shimmied her panties down. She heard Jimmy take a deep breath as she dropped them on the coffee table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, pay attention,” she said as she turned around to face him again. “No touching.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded as she sat down, facing him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And you can’t tell anyone.” He nodded eagerly, but she continued. “I’m serious! You can’t go tell your dumb friends, and you &lt;em&gt;definitely&lt;/em&gt; can’t tell my brother!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course not! I wouldn’t!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, then.” She leaned back on the arm of the couch and spread her legs for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, wow,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Quick anatomy lesson. These are my lips. If I spread them open like this, you can see the opening of my pussy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re wet…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. You’re not the only one who got turned on by the movie. When girls get aroused, they get wet, to make it easier for a guy’s cock or a girl’s fingers to slip inside. Don’t ever try to push anything inside a girl if she’s not wet, it’ll just hurt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, staring intently. His cock throbbed, and he absent-mindedly rubbed it through his shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, this is important, look here. Up at the top, where my lips come together? They make a kind of hood to cover this—ah—this little bud here. Do you see it? That’s my clitoris. When I get very turned on, it gets a bit swollen and pokes out. It’s &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; sensitive. You know how it feels good to rub your cock, like you’re doing right now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy looked guilty and moved his hand away, but nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay, I don’t mind, but listen… A girl’s clit is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; like your cock. If you try to rub her clit like you touch yourself, it’s too much. You’ll piss her off. You’ve gotta build up to that, make sure she’s ready first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I, uh,” Jimmy licked his lips, “know if a girl’s ready?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Honestly, you let her tell you or show you. Girls like it when you take your time. Don’t just give her a kiss and jam your hand down her underwear. Talk to her. Ask her how she likes to be touched. Some girls like a lot of kissing. Some will want you to touch their breasts. Others don’t want that at all.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, um…” His hand drifted back to his cock. “What do you like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” she purred, idly caressing her lips. “I like sitting in a guy’s lap, and rubbing against him. Especially if I’m wearing a skirt. Fuck, I love feeling his cock grow, pressing against me. And I like it when a guy touches me like this…” She slowly teased a finger between her lips, just enough to get it wet, and traced a lazy circle around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought you said,” he whispered, “not to start with the clit?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, but I’m already turned on. If I was sitting in your… I mean, a guy’s lap, rubbing against him, I’d be ready for a bit more direct… stimulation…” She trailed off, slowly rubbing herself as she watched him grind his palm against his erection. She wanted to see him. “Why don’t you pull that out? Show me how you touch yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yeah, okay,” he stammered. Quickly, he peeled off his shorts and boxers, then sat back down across from her, leaning on the other arm of the couch. His cock wasn’t bad to look at, she realized, as he wrapped his hand around the base and started slowly stroking the full length of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Once a girl lets you know she’s ready, you can go inside,” she purred, easing her middle finger between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How would she let me know?” His voice was husky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She might show you, by grabbing your hand. Especially if you’re already rubbing her, she might just push your finger inside. Or she might ask. She might say, ‘please, I need your fingers.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather shivered under his gaze. He was entranced. His eyes were locked between her legs, completely absorbed by what she was showing him. She felt almost as though he were worshipping her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to touch me?” She gasped, surprised by her escalation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really?” His eyes met hers, equally surprised. He seemed to be checking that it wasn’t a trap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, really. Here, give me your hand. Start by rubbing over… Mmm, yeah, like that. Slow, gentle pressure. You can kinda let your fingers ease between my lips, but don’t go inside just yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy gawked, one hand wrapped around his cock and the other caressing her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, now come up a little higher… Yes, now to start, don’t rub my clit directly, try rubbing all around it—ah—like that, yeah, every movement stim—oh!—stimulates her more, and then you can start moving closer—uh—and closer, until you—ah!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you like that?” Jimmy asked, earnestly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t ask a girl if she likes it,” Heather groaned. “That’s a turn-off. Just pay attention. Look at me—ah—right now. Listen to my breathing. See how I arch—oh!—my back when you touch me there? Feel me rolling my hips to meet your fingers?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Jimmy gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s how you know—oh, oh, oh!—but you also have to—ah!—know when to back off…” She gently pushed him lower, away from her tingling clit. “Now, I want your fingers. If you turn your hand like this… Yeah, you can slip your first two fingers in. Mmm. Some girls just want one finger. Some want two. Don’t do three or more unless you really know she wants it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ll want to move your fingers in and out… Mmm, yeah, like that. Like having sex… Don’t overdo it. Start slow, but follow her lead. Watch how she—ah—how she responds. See how her body moves with you. If you pay attention, you’ll know…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy groaned, stroking himself faster, matching the pace his fingers were pushing into her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you make a kind of come-hither motion with your fingers—ah!—like that! You’ll feel a spot—ah, ah—that’s good, that spot feels good, and if you—uh!—kinda just strum it—oh!—like a guitar. Oh, that’s good, I just need…” She reached down to rub tight circles around her clit. “Ah!—like that, yeah, you’ll… make… me… Oh! Oh! Cum! I’m cumming…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather clamped her thighs shut around Jimmy’s arm, holding him in place as she clenched around his fingers. She didn’t usually cum this easily. There was something about the situation, about having Jimmy’s complete attention. Her body seemed to bloom for him, like it wanted him to see everything she had to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Jimmy gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she moaned. Somewhat reluctantly, she opened her legs again, and gave him a nudge to pull out. The sensation made her shiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a moment, when she could focus again, she found Jimmy staring curiously at his fingers. They were glistening wet, and a string of her cream stretched between them as he spread them open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go ahead,” she smiled. “Taste it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grinning, Jimmy eagerly licked his fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I taste?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um… it’s like, uh… I have no idea how to describe it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ha! Yeah. It’s hard to find the right words.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, but, um, how…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I know what my pussy tastes like?” Heather laughed as he nodded. “Come on, be honest. Have you never tasted your own cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, I guess I got curious once,” he blushed. “I didn’t really like the taste.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you go. Girls get curious, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a moment, neither of them spoke. The moment stretched, loaded with tension. Jimmy rested on his knees, gripping his throbbing cock, and staring at her with eyes full of lust. She gazed up at him, legs spread, pussy swollen and sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She should tell him they were done. He would respect it, she knew. No doubt, he’d go to his room and cum while thinking of her. She’d go to the bathroom to clean up, then wait for his parents to come home. And, then, to be honest, probably go home to her room and cum while thinking of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, she could let him do it here. She imagined writhing on the couch, rubbing her clit as he knelt over her, gasping and stroking his cock. His cum would arc through the air, falling on her thighs and pussy. She imagined his expression as she eagerly rubbed it into her skin, and then sucked her fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or she could finish what she’d started. Teaching him how to treat a woman. After all, the job wasn’t done. It’d be a bit rude to send him off without showing him how to slide his cock into her dripping wet pussy, to feel him thrust inside…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to keep…” she started to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can we keep…” he said at the same time, and they both stopped. A crooked smile spread across his face as he realized what she was about ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Jimmy, come here,” she gasped, and pulled him down on top of her. He made a surprised sound that was choked off as her tongue pushed between his lips. He awkwardly wrapped his arms around her and settled his weight between her thighs. She moaned as his cock pressed against her, hard as steel against her swollen lips, eager to part around him. She squirmed, trying to position him…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, she pulled back from the kiss, holding a hand against his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You. Cannot. Tell. Anyone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, yeah, no problem,” he agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she gasped. “Okay, let’s do this. If you get a girl good and excited, she’ll be eager for you. Like me right now. I want to feel you inside me so fucking hard…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy leaned forward eagerly, but she kept holding him away just a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If she’s as wet as me, you can just… put yourself against her opening… like this… and then—oh!—Fuck, Jimmy, I was gonna tell you when, but you’re already inside!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned, staring into her eyes, and shifted as if to start fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! No, wait, just—oh—just wait a minute. Give me a minute to adjust. I—ah—love the feeling when a guy first enters me, let me savor it. Oh my god, I can feel you throbbing inside me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she rolled her hips, encouraging him to start moving with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, like that, start slow. Oh, fuck. Don’t just start railing a girl, you—ah!—gotta build up to that, even when she’s as turned on as me. Oh god-damn, yeah, yeah, move with me, I—mmm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled him back into a kiss, moaning into his mouth as he followed her lead and started thrusting into her. Quickly, she escalated the pace. Every thrust, every time he bottomed out, she saw a flare of color out of the corner of her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He broke the kiss, and buried his face in her shoulder, fucking her harder and faster. She wrapped her legs around him, and held on as he moved with increasing urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wanted to tell him more. To get on top and ride him. She wanted him to get behind her. She wanted to show him when to pull her hair. When to push his thumb into her ass. She wanted him to &lt;em&gt;cum&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wanted him to cum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jimmy!” She gasped into his ear. “Are you—ah!—close?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he groaned. “Can I?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Oh, yes! I want you to—ah!—Cum in me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned and went rigid on top of her. She gasped at the feeling of his cock twitching, and the spreading warmth inside. After a long moment, he relaxed, and she ran her fingers through his hair, breathing softly in his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, Jimmy,” she sighed. “I think you’re gonna do alright with the ladies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tried to give her a kiss as he climbed off her, but she squeaked, shoving a hand between her legs as his cum leaked out. He handed her a tissue box, and she wiped up as he watched, fascinated. Mercifully, it had only dripped on the inside of her skirt, not the couch. That would have been hard to explain to his parents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy pulled on his shorts and followed her into the kitchen. She poured them each a glass of water. When she passed his over, his eyes sparkled with a mixture of gratitude and awe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she laughed, “don’t you look like the cat who caught the canary?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kinda feels that way.” He grinned, and took a sip of water. “You know, I was just thinking. Like, you’re home for a few weeks, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And I don’t leave for a few weeks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go on,” she smiled, knowing where he was going with this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, maybe you could show me some more stuff.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t get cocky, kid,” she laughed. “Girls like a bit of confidence, but too much can be off-putting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that a no?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean,” She bit her lip. “I &lt;em&gt;suppose&lt;/em&gt; there’s a bit more I could teach you…”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
</feed>
