<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Ruby Pink Romance</title>
	<subtitle>Classy smut for classy people</subtitle>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/"/>
	<updated>2025-03-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Ruby Pink</name>
		<email>hello@rubypinkromance.com</email>
	</author>
  <icon>https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rubypink.jpg</icon>
	<entry>
		<title>Kara’s Experiences 2: Kara’s Punishment</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/karas-experiences/karas-punishment/"/>
		<published>2025-03-18T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-03-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/karas-experiences/karas-punishment/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="spanking" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
    <category term="submissive" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fingering" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/karas-punishment-K8os0yVcNq-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Fidgeting with her keys, Kara hesitated at the front door of her girlfriend’s apartment. No, scratch that. Victoria always frowned when Kara said, “girlfriend.” She said the word was “used by the patriarchy to demean relationships between women.” But she also resisted any attempt to find a better term to define their relationship, so Kara found herself falling back on the word that most people understood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’d met at a party hosted by the campus LGBT+ community group. Kara had worked up the nerve to walk in, but found herself being a wallflower. Despite an experience the year before that boosted her confidence and resulted in a sexual awakening, she still struggled with social anxiety. Victoria spotted her from the dance floor and beckoned her over, kickstarting a passionate romance. They’d been together ever since.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, there was an extra layer to their relationship beyond simple intimacy. Victoria said she saw a spark in Kara that was at risk of being smothered by “Western society’s restrictive Puritan social norms.” She’d appointed herself Kara’s mentor, determined to broaden her sexual horizons and push her limits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mostly, this took the form of exciting challenges, meant to expand her comfort zone, each building on the last. Bold makeup choices led to shorter skirts, lower-cut tops, and eventually going to class with no underwear. Leaving the lights on when they fooled around turned into filming themselves having sex. And what started with kissing in public ultimately led to Kara going down on her in a movie theater. Each challenge was thrilling and nerve-wracking in equal measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, Victoria was waiting inside, and Kara was nervous because, for the first time, she’d failed a challenge. Victoria had sent her to class with a remote-controlled vibrator and clear instructions not to cum. But Kara couldn’t do it. Victoria’s remote stimulation had become too intense, and she ran out of the lecture hall before she had a very obvious public orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How would Victoria respond? Surely, she’d be disappointed, but then what would happen? Would she comfort Kara and apologize for pushing her too far? That seemed unlikely. Maybe she would shrug and give up on the challenges, leaving Kara forever wondering what could have happened next. Or, worst of all, what if she decided that Kara was just too boring and vanilla to waste any more time on, and broke up with her?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking a deep breath to steady herself, she unlocked the door and slipped inside, hanging her bag on the coat rack and dropping her keys on the table before looking up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria was leaning casually against the kitchen doorframe, sipping a glass of whiskey. Her relaxed pose contrasted with her severe appearance. Hair pulled back in a tight ponytail. Dark lipstick, thigh-high fishnets, and a black mesh thong. All topped with a leather corset that barely contained her breasts. Despite her nervousness, Kara felt a surge of excitement. Victoria only dressed like this when she wanted to take charge in the bedroom. She’d clearly been expecting Kara to come home desperately aroused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So,” Victoria asked calmly, “how’d it go?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t do it,” Kara stammered, twisting her hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I figured,” Victoria nodded, walking over to the couch. “When I saw the app disconnect. But tell me about it. What went wrong?” She sat in the middle, crossed her legs, and draped her arms across the back, pointedly not inviting Kara to sit beside her. She didn’t seem upset, but there was something about her body language that made Kara alert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, at first, it was exciting? I could barely focus on the lecture, but I thought I could hold out. I kept peeking around to make sure no one knew what I was doing. When you put it on that escalating pattern, it was &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; distracting. The intensity would build and build, and when it reset, I was gripping the edge of my seat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria took another slow sip and nodded for Kara to continue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But then it started to be too much. Every time it peaked, it was all I could do not to moan and squirm in my seat. I was so wet, it was soaking through my skirt. I was worried the girl sitting next to me could smell how turned on I was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that when you turned it off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! I didn’t want to give up, even though I was worried about losing control. But then you turned it up again! I didn’t think it could even go any higher. I was starting to breathe heavily and squeeze my thighs together. I was desperate not to lose control. I kept thinking about you saying, ‘Be a good girl, and don’t cum.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And did you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, but I realized I wasn’t going to make it. There were still fifteen minutes of class left! I was so frustrated, I was almost crying.” The words were spilling out of her as she desperately tried to make Victoria understand. “I know if you’d been there… If you had been able to see me, you would have turned it down. You wouldn’t have made me cum in front of everyone. You wanted me to be on the edge, right? So I could come home to you. You can’t have wanted me to lose control. I know you didn’t want to humiliate me in front of the entire class. Because if I had started to cum, I wouldn’t have been able to stop. I would have been moaning and humping my chair. People would have laughed and stared, but I wouldn’t have been able to stop. That &lt;em&gt;can’t&lt;/em&gt; be what you wanted, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm.” Victoria paused for a long moment, considering the idea. “No, I suppose not. Not yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara’s eyes opened wide with surprise. Not yet? How far did Victoria intend to take her?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anyway,” Victoria shrugged, “what did you do then?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When I realized I couldn’t stop it from happening, I grabbed my bag and ran to the bathroom. I barely made it. As soon as I closed the stall door, my orgasm hit. All I could do was brace myself on the wall and try not to make any noise. I came so hard, it was running down my leg and dripping on the floor. When I was finally able to pull the egg out, it was so slippery I almost dropped it, trying to find the off switch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How did you feel?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Incredible! Breathless. Flushed. Nervous?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you think,” Victoria mused, “that your orgasm was more intense because it started in public?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” Kara blushed. “Yes?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, that’s something, I suppose.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara sighed, flooded with relief. She understood!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, you &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; break your word, didn’t you?” Victoria raised an eyebrow. “You promised to be a good girl. To hold yourself back from cumming.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A confusing thrill of anticipation rolled down Kara’s spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And, if a &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; girl would have controlled herself, I suppose that makes you a &lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt; girl, doesn’t it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara slowly nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, if a good girl gets a reward, what do you think a bad girl should get?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A punishment?” Kara could barely breathe the answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Interesting.” Victoria smiled. “To start, why don’t you undress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling weak in the knees, but undeniably curious, Kara dutifully removed her clothes. Victoria watched over the rim of her whiskey glass as Kara folded her things and set them neatly aside. When she finished, Victoria gestured for her to kneel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s better,” she said. “I like the way you look, naked on the floor. Eager to please. You’re excited, aren’t you? Desperate to make it up to me. And you should be, because you derailed my plans for you tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara’s eyes involuntarily flicked toward the bedroom. She blushed, imagining what Victoria would have done if she’d come home as planned, panting with desire and desperate for release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, another time, perhaps,” Victoria shrugged. “Right now, I have a more pressing concern. You’re not the only one who spent the afternoon getting excited, but you’re the only one who’s had any release. That doesn’t seem fair, does it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara shook her head as Victoria spread her legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come see the state you’ve left me in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprised at how much this new dynamic excited her, Kara crawled forward on her hands and knees. As she approached, Victoria ran her fingers through Kara’s hair, grabbing a handful and pulling her closer. The smell of Victoria’s arousal filled her nostrils as she pressed her nose into the damp gusset of her thong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look what you did,” she growled. “It’s hardly fair for you to get off without me and then leave me like this. Go on, lick it. I want you to taste how excited I was for you to come home so I could reward you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara dragged her tongue over the fabric, already clinging to Victoria’s lips. Her juices seeped through, teasing Kara with the taste of her lover’s arousal. She moaned with desperation, to be so close, but still separated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Frustrating, isn’t it?” Victoria groaned. “That’s how I felt, seeing you stroll through the front door, glowing with satisfaction.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry,” Kara murmured from between her thighs. “Let me make it up to you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Since you’re so eager to redeem yourself, I’ll allow you to remove my underwear… with your teeth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Kara bit the waistband and started pulling down. Victoria lifted her hips a bit, but otherwise let Kara struggle. The process was awkward and demeaning, but at last, she knelt between Victoria’s knees with the thong hanging from her lips. Triumphant, she tossed it carelessly aside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well done,” Victoria said, dipping a finger between her labia, glistening with arousal. “Don’t you look pleased with yourself? Like a puppy, desperate for approval.” She laughed. “Come here, puppy, here’s a treat for you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She offered her wet finger, and Kara gratefully wrapped her lips around it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want more? Then go down on me. If you do a good job, I may be generous with your punishment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara didn’t need any more encouragement. Without hesitation, she buried her face between Victoria’s thighs. Her tongue danced between slick lips to lap up her lover’s juices. Victoria let out a long sigh and relaxed as she took another sip of whiskey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s it, puppy. Just like I taught you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A warm glow of pride flared inside when Victoria praised her. Kara moved her head in circles, working her tongue deeper. She worshipped Victoria’s pussy, wanting desperately to make her feel good. When she felt the grip on her hair tighten, she shivered with pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Use your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara slipped two inside, and wrapped her lips around Victoria’s clit. She felt the thighs around her head tense, and curled her fingers in a come-hither motion. Her lover grunted and lifted her hips, grinding against Kara’s face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t. Stop.” Victoria said through clenched teeth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara hummed with satisfaction, working her fingers and tongue in a rhythm. Victoria was squirming and bucking her hips. Slowly, Kara extended her pinky finger. Victoria had spent many hours teaching Kara how to please her, but this was something Kara had discovered all on her own. When Victoria was this turned on, a finger in her ass set her off like a firework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria grunted as Kara’s knuckle bumped against her back door. She tensed as Kara worked her fingertip into the tight opening. And, as always, Victoria gasped as she suddenly unclenched, letting Kara slip it all the way in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara worked harder, thrusting her fingers deeper. The grip on her hair tightened as she flicked her tongue faster. They both moaned as Victoria’s climax approached, her insides clenching and squeezing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara didn’t stop until Victoria suddenly cried out, arching her back. Hot fluid gushed around her fingers, dripping down her arm onto the floor. She held still, letting Victoria’s body react to the steady pressure, until at last, she shuddered and swatted her away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara rocked back on her heels, gasping for breath and wiping her lover’s juices from her chin. Victoria had curled tightly into a ball, shivering as the final waves of pleasure rolled over her. After a minute, she relaxed, then stretched wide and sat up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, puppy,” she chucked, seeing Kara’s triumphant expression. “That was nicely done. Because you worked so hard to please me, I’m feeling generous.” She tapped a finger on her lower lip, thinking. “I’m only going to spank you fifteen times, instead of thirty.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? A spanking?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria laughed at the shocked expression on Kara’s face. “What sort of punishment were you expecting?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know. Not that!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, you thought going down on me was your punishment?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, kinda?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, no. You enjoyed it too much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara cheeks burned and she looked away. She felt foolish. Victoria put a finger under her chin and pulled her gently back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, puppy, have you never been spanked?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! My parents didn’t believe in it!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That explains a lot,” Victoria smirked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Doesn’t it hurt?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It wouldn’t be a good punishment if it didn’t hurt a little,” Victoria shrugged. “But some people find the boundary between pain and pleasure is a bit… hazy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara frowned. Victoria leaned closer, until their lips were nearly touching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you trust me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“…Yes?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have I ever gone too far with you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” Kara conceded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then trust me now. If it’s too much, you can say, hmm… ‘Pineapple,’ and I’ll stop.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” At last, Victoria pulled her into a kiss so full of desire it left her light-headed. “Now, bend over my knee like a &lt;em&gt;good girl&lt;/em&gt;, and accept your punishment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nervously, Kara got into position. It was awkward, being on her hands and knees over Victoria’s legs on the couch. Her heart pounded wildly with anticipation. Victoria grinned wolfishly, caressing her bare bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “One.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara jumped as the first slap impacted her ass, hard enough to leave a stinging impression behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Two.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second fell on her other cheek, just as shocking as the first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Three.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara whimpered as Victoria slapped the first cheek again, intensifying the sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Four.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her soft flesh rippled from the impact. She curled her spine, flinching away from the blows. She wanted to cover her rear to protect herself, but knew she couldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Five.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped from the sharp pain. Ten more? She wouldn’t be able to sit when this was over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria paused for a moment, caressing her ass softly. Kara shivered as cool fingers slipped down the back of her leg, and teased back up her inner thigh. When they met her vulva, she gasped as Victoria dragged one finger teasingly between her lips, slick with arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt humiliated by how wet and ready she was, remembering Victoria saying she might like the confusing mix of pleasure and pain. She wanted to protest, but also desperately wanted her to keep touching her like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Six.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara cried out in shock. She’d known there were more slaps coming, but the tender touch between her thighs had sent a confusing mix of pleasure to soothe the stinging. Now, pain flared back to the forefront.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Seven.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip, choking back a sob as conflicted emotions swirled in her brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Eight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squinting her eyes tight, she saw flares of white sparks behind her eyelids. She gripped the edge of the couch cushion tightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Nine.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” she blurted, clamping a hand over her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Ten.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She swore into her hand, trying not to focus on the burning heat on her bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Victoria’s fingers again teased between her legs and caressed her lips, she gasped with surprise. The gentle touch stood in stark contrast to the harsh spanking. She rocked back against Victoria’s hand, desperate for more, and whimpered when she pulled away too soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Eleven.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara sobbed with frustration at the sudden flare of incandescent pain. A tear rolled down her cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Twelve.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pineapple!&lt;/em&gt; The word was right on her lips. All she had to do was say it, and Victoria would stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Thirteen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But confusingly, some part of her didn’t want it to stop. She buried her face in the couch cushion and groaned, bracing herself for the next blow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slap!&lt;/em&gt; “Fourteen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shouted into the couch cushion, confused by her body’s reaction, and anticipating the final spank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It didn’t come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She growled with frustration. Without intending to, she arched her back, presenting herself, waggling her ass as if begging Victoria to finish the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;SLAP!&lt;/em&gt; “Fifteen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final slap was the hardest of all, falling on stinging, burning, tender flesh. Her body rippled around the blow, and a breath she didn’t realize she’d been holding burst out of her in a shuddering release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good job, puppy, you took your punishment well.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara moaned and squirmed, unable to process the praise. Her body was aflame with a terrible mixture of pain and arousal. She arched her back again, desperate for Victoria’s touch, the gentle caress that had followed each round of spanking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” she gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, what?” Victoria murmured, while running a fingertip up the back of Kara’s thigh, making her shiver with desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, make me cum,” she begged shamelessly, no longer embarrassed by how turned-on she was. “I’m so close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, since you asked so nicely,” Victoria chuckled. Kara didn’t hear her, as a hand moved up her thigh and fingers slipped between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled her hips, urgently rocking back and forth against Victoria’s expert stimulation. She was on fire. Every sensation was bleeding into the others, an overwhelming cocktail of stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cum for me, puppy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara screamed as her body responded immediately to the command. Her insides clenched tightly around thrusting fingers. She rolled her hips against the pressure on her clit, waves of pleasure radiating out from her core. Behind her closed eyes, fireworks of pink and yellow erupted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, the release left her limp and breathless. It took effort to sit up, and curl herself into her lover’s embrace. Victoria held her close, pulling her head onto her shoulder, caressing her back, and whispering, “Good girl” until she stopped shivering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe next time,” Victoria mused, with a smile on her face, “I’ll sneak into your class and sit in the back, so I can see how close you get to the edge.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Kara’s Experiences 1: Kara’s Challenge</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/karas-experiences/karas-challenge/"/>
		<published>2025-02-27T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-02-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/karas-experiences/karas-challenge/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="toys" />
    <category term="public" />
    <category term="school" />
    <category term="skirt" />
    <category term="vibrator" />
    <category term="remote control" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/karas-challenge-h376Vb0WFN-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Kara’s heart pounded as she sat perfectly still in her seat, trying to ignore the vibrator rumbling insistently inside her. The art history lecture hall was dimly lit for a slideshow, but the other students sitting around her would definitely notice if she started squirming. She bit her lip and gripped her pen tighter. She’d given up on taking notes, but hoped that holding the pen made it less obvious the state she was in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before she’d left for classes that morning, her girlfriend Victoria had inspected her outfit, walking in a slow circle, assessing her choices. The polka-dot skirt was one of Victoria’s favorites, and she’d paired it with a simple pink button-up and Converse. “You look nice,” Victoria concluded. Before Kara could breathe a sigh of relief, she added, “but undo two more buttons and give me your panties.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria had a knack for pushing Kara just outside her comfort zone, giving her permission to explore a more sensual side of herself. It started with little challenges like choosing a bolder shade of lipstick, or secretly wearing exciting lingerie under her clothes. Then, between classes, Victoria would summon her to an isolated stairwell for an illicit rendezvous that would leave her breathless and flushed. Today, she was sending her out in a short skirt with no underwear and her top unbuttoned scandalously low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her first class was thrilling. She sat with her group, discussing their project like normal. The guys struggled not to stare down her shirt, which made her nipples harden and her heart beat faster. Of course, they couldn’t tell she wasn’t wearing any underwear, and that secret made her even more excited. She found herself leaning forward, daring them to look, and reveling in their desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that, Victoria met her in the student union building for lunch. When she raised an eyebrow suggestively and asked how class went, Kara blushed. After confirming no one was listening, she confessed everything. How the attention had secretly excited her, how she’d encouraged the boys to peek. Victoria nodded approvingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come with me. I’ve got a present for you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, she threw away her sandwich, took Kara by the hand, and led her to the restroom. In the last stall, Victoria pressed her against the wall and kissed her passionately. Kara melted into her arms, desperate for her touch. One hand slipped into her shirt to rub her nipple. Another traced up her inner thigh, reaching under her skirt. She gasped as Victoria’s nimble fingers danced over her lips, finding her wet and ready. When they finally dipped inside, Kara moaned around Victoria’s tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only when she was panting with desire did Victoria step back, and take the present out of her bag. The object she produced was bright pink and shaped like an egg with a long tail. When Kara looked confused, she explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Since you like having a sexy secret in public, you’ll love this. The big end is a vibrator. Here, spread your legs.” Kara did as she was told, stifling a squeak as Victoria reached under her skirt and pressed it against her slick lips. “That’s right, baby, let me put it in you. Ah! There it goes, and the tail hangs out like that. Now, here’s the clever part.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria pulled out her phone and touched the screen. Kara jumped as the egg suddenly buzzed to life. She clamped her hands between her legs and stared wide-eyed at Victoria as she dragged her finger up and down on her phone, the intensity of the vibration changing to match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you like it? It’s remote-controlled. I can change the pattern and the intensity from anywhere.” She leaned closer, brushing her lips against Kara’s. “Now, you’ll go to your next class…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Class?” Kara shook her head. “No, no, no, I can’t do that in public!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your next class is art history, right? In that dark lecture hall?” When Kara nodded, Victoria smiled. “See? That’s perfect. You’ll sit there in the dark with this vibrating away inside you. I’m going back to the apartment, and I’m going to keep you right on the edge the whole time. No one will be able to tell. And when class is over, you’ll come… home to me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara gasped at the thought. Even when Victoria pushed her boundaries, she’d learned to trust one thing about these challenges. If she did what was asked, and shared all the details of how it made her feel, Victoria would reward her. Her heart beat faster as she imagined falling into bed with her after sitting through an entire class with a vibrator inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One rule,” Victoria breathed, nibbling on her earlobe. “Under no circumstances are you allowed to cum. You save that for &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt;. I want you to ride the edge of this experience and then come home to me. Can you do that? Can you control yourself? Can you be a &lt;em&gt;good girl&lt;/em&gt; for me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was all it took, really. Victoria knew her too well. When she said “Good girl” like that, it sent a shiver straight down Kara’s spine. She nodded helplessly. Victoria kissed her, smiled devilishly, and slipped out. Kara was left breathless and disheveled, with only a few minutes to pull herself together for class. The egg continued gently vibrating the whole time, discreet but impossible to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first half hour of class wasn’t too difficult. She claimed a seat near the back, and avoided making eye contact with anyone she knew. The other seats slowly filled, and when the lights dimmed, she breathed a sigh of relief. At first, she could almost ignore the sensation, but after a bit, it started to change. Victoria must have started playing with the controls. The vibrations grew more insistent, until the rumbling was all she could think about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Licking her lips, Kara glanced around the art history lecture hall, confirming once again that no one was looking at her. Everyone else was lost in their thoughts. Some were paying attention to the slides and diligently taking notes. Some were slouched low, looking at their phones. One guy had actually fallen asleep. His friend nudged him when he started snoring, and he sat up, blinking blearily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No one else seemed to have spent the last half-hour trying to ignore their growing arousal. &lt;em&gt;Slow your breathing&lt;/em&gt;, she told herself. &lt;em&gt;No one knows. They can’t hear the vibrator. Try to look like you’re paying attention to the lecture. Something about… Impressionism?&lt;/em&gt; She squeezed her legs tightly together, resisting the urge to squirm in her seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The egg’s vibration wasn’t as intense as holding a vibrator to her clit, but it simply never stopped. No matter how she shifted her weight, or crossed or uncrossed her legs, the rumbling in her core continued. The stimulation was diffuse but pervasive. She felt it everywhere, and the longer it went on, the more her body responded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria had set it on a pattern that seemed designed to be as distracting as possible. It started as a low and slow rumble, gradually building to a powerfully intense buzzing, before abruptly dropping back to the lowest setting. The cycle repeated until Kara could only grip her desk with white knuckles, trying desperately not to make any noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She imagined Victoria, back at her apartment, manipulating the controls. She would have changed already. When she was in the mood to play with Kara, she always put on a leather corset that barely contained her breasts, and pulled her hair back in a severe ponytail. Would she be in bed already, or sitting on the couch? Probably the couch. Sitting there, legs crossed, casually holding her phone, playing with the intensity, and enjoying the effect she was having from afar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara shot a desperate look at the clock. Class wouldn’t end for another twenty minutes. Could she last that long? As if in response to her thought, the pattern changed to an intense, steady vibration. Oh, God! It was taking all her willpower not to react.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What had started as a pleasant secret had grown to a distracting arousal and continued from there. The pressure had been building, and now she felt an undeniable need for release. She was grateful no one could see the flush across her chest. Her nipples ached to be touched. Her insides squeezed around the egg, rippling with anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Focus on the slides&lt;/em&gt;, she told herself. &lt;em&gt;Don’t think about how desperately you need to cum.&lt;/em&gt; The teacher’s droning voice was explaining Monet’s exile in London, but the intense, all-consuming vibration deep in her core drove away all other thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She released a shuddering breath and slowly rocked forward in her seat, changing the pressure on her clit. Her fingernails dug into the paper of her notebook as she struggled not to give in. Victoria said she had to control herself. She had to be good. Just hold out a bit longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pressure inside continued to build, along with her fear of losing control. Desperate to hold back the tide, she discreetly hiked her skirt high enough to slip her hand under. Spreading her legs just enough to clamp her hand between her thighs, applying a firm, reassuring pressure, she shivered, feeling her lips puffy and wet under her fingers. Her juices were literally dripping down the tail of the vibrator, soaking into the back of her skirt. If this got much worse, she was going to leave an actual puddle on the seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A jolt of electricity crackled up her spine, nearly making her jump, as Victoria turned up the intensity again. She stifled a sob of frustration. It hadn’t already been on the highest setting? Her insides fluttered, rippling around the intense stimulation, desperate for release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; be almost over. She looked desperately at the clock, hoping to see only a minute or two left, but there were still &lt;em&gt;fifteen&lt;/em&gt; minutes to go! Oh, fuck. She gripped her desk tighter as she realized she wasn’t going to make it. Victoria couldn’t see her. She didn’t understand how desperate the situation was. If she were here, surely she would lower the intensity to keep Kara on the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shuddered, feeling an orgasm starting to bubble up. It was too intense. She couldn’t hold it off. Would Victoria make her cum right here in class? There would be no denying what was happening as she cried out and rocked in place, sobbing in frustration as she came uncontrollably in front of everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That can’t have been what Victoria intended. With a shock, she realized the only alternative was to break her promise. What would the consequences be? She’d never failed a challenge before, but as soon as the thought crossed her mind, she knew she had no choice. Frantically, she stuffed her things into her bag and hurried for the exit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She didn’t notice if her classmates protested as she scooted past them, praying they couldn’t smell her arousal. She threw open the door and ran down the hall, bumping into several people on her desperate flight to the bathroom. The egg continued its relentless assault, making it clear that if she stopped for even a second, she would lose control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She just had enough willpower to lock the stall door and throw her bag on the hook before bracing herself on the wall. Standing up, legs spread wide, she gasped as quietly as possible as a relentless climax tore through her. Her knees shook and her vision blurred. She felt hot liquid dripping down her thighs as she thrust her hips. Her insides clenched over and over, waves of pleasure rippling out from her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the sensation receded enough to restore control of her body, she reached under her skirt and yanked the egg out. Once outside her body, the buzzing was embarrassingly loud. Frantically, she felt around the slippery silicone skin for an off switch, finally finding a dimple that shut it down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still breathing heavily, she did her best to clean up, praying no one else heard what she’d just done. Wrapping the pink egg in toilet paper, she hid it in her bag and stepped out to wash her hands. In the mirror, she was flushed, but giddy-looking. She grinned at her reflection, and tried to brush her hair back into control. Despite a lingering sense of shame, she had to admit she felt incredible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, she just had to tell Victoria what she’d done.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Octopus Lover</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/fetish/octopus-lover/"/>
		<published>2025-02-19T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-02-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/fetish/octopus-lover/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="fetish" />
    <category term="octopus" />
    <category term="tentacles" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="first time" />
    <category term="costume" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/octopus-lover-BEXT7z_9Ef-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I can clearly remember the first time I felt aroused. I was eleven years old, watching &lt;em&gt;The Goonies&lt;/em&gt; with my brother and his friends. He was grumpy because Mom said he had to let me watch, and he didn’t want his little sister to embarrass him. He told me to be quiet and sit on the floor in front of the couch, but I felt so cool hanging out with them that I didn’t care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the movie, there’s a scene where one of the girls is attacked by an octopus. It’s barely a minute long. They’re in the water and this enormous octopus sneaks up on them. When it brushes her legs, she slaps one of the boys, assuming he’s doing it. A moment later, the tentacles wrap around her body, trying to pull her under. She thrashes around for a bit until the others save her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, at the time, I didn’t really know what arousal was. I just knew that scene thrilled me in a way I’d never experienced before. It’s funny, I wasn’t worried that she’d be eaten or drown or anything bad like that. I was fascinated by the idea of the tentacles wrapped around her. I couldn’t stop thinking about it. It made me feel funny and a bit squirmy. I could barely focus on the rest of the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was still thinking about it when I went to bed that night. My dreams were full of tentacles snaking up my legs and squeezing my body. I woke up tangled in my sheets with some very confused feelings that I didn’t know what to do with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mom seemed surprised by my sudden fascination with sea life, and particularly octopuses. After all, girls are supposed to like cute animals like bunnies and unicorns. Still, she supported me, taking me to the aquarium as often as possible, and buying me loads of books about the ocean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For my birthday, she got me a large stuffed octopus that never left my bed, even as I got older and other stuffed animals became embarrassing. I slept with him every night, wrapping his tentacles around my body as if it were hugging me. Sometimes, when I was alone, I would sit on him, bouncing in a way that left me feeling squishy and nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my teens, I learned words for what I was experiencing. Other girls at school would talk about “getting horny” or “turned on,” but only in the context of boys. I didn’t understand the appeal, but I knew better than to tell anyone about my octopus fantasies. Instead, I would smile and giggle and play along with my friends, just to fit in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In high school, I tried dating guys, and even a few girls, but nothing really clicked. Kissing was nice, and I liked feeling close to someone, but I never felt any sexual desire for them. We would fool around, and I did all the things my friends said they were doing. It was fine. I enjoyed making my partner feel good. But it didn’t really do anything for me, and after a while, I stopped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even in college, my octopus fantasy never left me. My stuffed friend came with me, of course. When I felt aroused, the images in my head were always of tentacles exploring my body. In my head, my cephalopod companion was a curious and sensitive lover, holding and caressing me in warm water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, it was enough to imagine the dexterous tips of his tentacles stimulating my most sensitive parts. Tracing around my nipples or teasing between my lips to graze my clit. This kind of light stimulation was a common daydream during marine biology classes, enough to leave me pleasantly flushed and distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alone in my bed at night, those tentacles would become more insistent. Multiple arms would slide around my torso, squeezing my breasts, and reaching up my neck. They would wrap around my thighs and spread them open, leaving me breathless and squirming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would gasp at the thought of arms coiling and writhing hungrily around my body, probing my openings. One would push into my mouth, dancing along my tongue. I imagined them moving further up my thighs, caressing my slit, and prodding my entrance. I wanted to feel my lips part around an inquisitive tentacle, swelling thicker as it pushed deeper inside. And just when I thought I couldn’t take any more, one would tease between my cheeks, desperate to find another way into my body. When it finally slipped in the back door, I would moan around a mouthful of tentacle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frustratingly, I didn’t have enough fingers to fully act out that particular fantasy. Eventually, I worked up the nerve to order some accessories. A company selling novelty dildos offered one shaped like a thick purple tentacle. I bought it along with a strap-on harness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On nights when I felt the most need to act out my fantasy, I would wrap the leather straps around the body of my stuffed octopus, and lower myself onto his new appendage. I would hold his soft arms against my body while writhing on top of the deliciously textured dildo. As my stimulation grew, I would slip two fingers into my mouth, moaning and slurping around an imaginary tentacle. Finally, when I was about to cum, I would work a finger up my rear, triggering a nearly overwhelming climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Around this time, there was a guy in my postgrad marine biology program with a crush on me. He was funny, and I liked hanging out with him, but I knew he wanted more. I tried to subtly let him know I wasn’t interested, but he missed my signals entirely, and one day, he asked me out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to explain that I liked being friends, but I wasn’t really interested in &lt;em&gt;anyone&lt;/em&gt; that way. He accepted my rejection, and stayed in my orbit. I knew he was pining, but I figured as long as I had been clear, and wasn’t leading him on, it would be okay. We were still good friends, and I didn’t want to push him away entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For nearly a year, we remained friends. He would hang out with me after classes. We would go out for karaoke and drinks with friends. Sometimes we would study together at my apartment, but never more than that. At the end of the night I would send him home and go to bed with my octopus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then came the Halloween party. A mutual friend of ours was hosting it at her place, and pretty much everyone we knew was going. I didn’t want to wear something over-sexualized, so I ended up going as Velma from Scooby-Doo. Chunky orange sweater, red skirt, and orange knee-high socks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I walked into the party, surrounded by multiple dudes wearing ill-fitting superhero costumes, and women in lingerie and angel wings. Feeling out of place, I got a drink, and wandered around looking for my friend. When I spotted him coming through the front door, my heart skipped a beat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was wearing an octopus costume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know that scene in a rom-com where the guy spots the girl of his dreams, and everything goes slow motion? The noise of the surrounding conversations fade away, and some 80s song starts playing. I know this sounds dumb, but it was like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s no way he bought it at a store, this was clearly hand-made, though he’d put quite a bit of effort into the sewing. It was made from shiny purple fabric, and he had an exaggerated octopus mantle headpiece with big googly eyes. His arms were in two of the tentacles, which extended past his hands like dangling sleeves. Two more stuffed tentacles hung below his arms, and he was wearing leggings made from the same fabric. The fact that the two “leg” tentacles ended in sneakers somehow made the whole thing more endearing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was big and awkward, and I’ve never been more immediately attracted to someone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He caught my eye and made his way over, slowly moving around other people and constantly having to apologize when his tentacles bumped into them. I took a sip of my drink and tried to blink away the confusing thoughts bubbling up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey,” he said when he got close enough, holding his arms up for me to see. “What do you think?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t answer. Did he know? Had he somehow figured out my fantasy? Maybe he’d stumbled across the tentacle dildo at some point? No, there was no way. I was always careful to bury it at the bottom of my underwear drawer. Plus, the expression on his face said he was expecting friendly teasing about his costume, not shock that he’d uncovered my deepest, darkest secret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kinda goofy, I know,” he laughed, waving his arms around. He’d attached string to the dangling tentacles, so that when he raised his arms, the lower ones would lift at the same time. “I got the idea from that stuffed octopus you have on your bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My cheeks burned. I couldn’t hide the shock in my eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, sorry, I didn’t mean to sound like I was making fun of you,” he stammered, misinterpreting my reaction. “I think it’s cool! I didn’t want to make a costume anyone else would have.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still unable to find my words, I nodded. I could feel my chest was flushed, and was grateful that the sweater kept him from noticing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I like your costume,” he grinned. “Velma was always my favorite, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stared at his face, as if seeing him for the first time. Swathed in shiny purple fabric, waving his arms around, grinning self-consciously. I wanted to touch him, to run my hands over his chest. I saw the stubble on his cheek and imagined the way it would feel if I leaned in to kiss him. There was a growing heat in my core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, uh…” He seemed unnerved by my ongoing silence. “Maybe I’ll go, um, grab a beer?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I grabbed his wrist as he turned away. I felt a little thrill at the contact, and pulled him back. He looked at me curiously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you still like me?” I blurted the question, blushing furiously and grateful the music was too loud for anyone else to have heard me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, um,” he grimaced, unsure how to answer. “I mean, I know you’re not, uh…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay,” I insisted, squeezing his hand. “Just tell me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He regarded me cautiously. I stared, wide-eyed, heart pounding in my chest, willing him to admit what we both knew to be true. Finally, he licked his lips nervously, and nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearly overwhelmed by the sudden rush of emotion, I threw myself forward. Our lips met clumsily, but after his initial shock, he relaxed and wrapped his arms around me. The other tentacles followed suit, sending a thrill up my spine. I melted against him as our kiss became more passionate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take me home,” I gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, took me by the hand, and led me through the crowd. A few people had seen us kissing, and started whistling as we made our hasty exist. He shot me an embarrassed grin, but kept moving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn’t live far away, but the walk to my apartment is burned into my memory. He kept ahold of my hand the whole way. We didn’t talk. My heartbeat seemed to drown out all other sounds. I couldn’t keep my eyes off him. It was like a spotlight was shining on him, illuminating new possibilities I had never considered. Seeing him in that goofy costume awakened a passion in me that I’d only felt in my octopus fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nearly dropped my keys unlocking my apartment. As soon as I closed the door, he pulled me back into his arms. Our kiss was more urgent than before. We staggered into the bedroom, and I pushed him down on the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He watched with wide eyes as I undressed, discarding my clothes on the floor. He started pulling his arms from the tentacles, but I gestured for him to stop as I climbed on top of him. I straddled his waist and pulled his hands to my breasts. The arm tentacles reached further, caressing my face. I gasped as I felt the lower arms brushing against my sides. I rolled my hips, unsurprised to feel the firmness of his erection between my thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fumbled below me, until I found his waistband, and tugged the leggings down, just enough to free him. He groaned and squeezed my nipples as I took him in my hand. I angled him upward, positioning his head against my lips, already dripping with need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he gasped as I rubbed him back and forth, coating him in my wetness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” I moaned as I slowly lowered myself onto him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was like nothing I’d ever felt. I mean, I’d had sex before. That part wasn’t new. But this aching &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; deep inside? The incredible feeling he’d awoken in me? I’d never experienced that with another person before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock throbbed and twitched inside as I bounced on him. I leaned against his hands, savoring the way my breasts felt in his grasp. His tentacles caressed my sides and face, and I was amazed at the way it felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My pussy clenched wetly around him. He stared up at me with lust in his eyes. I rubbed my face against his tentacle, desperate for more. I turned to kiss the soft purple fabric, and surprised myself by licking it instead. He moaned at the sight, and, excited by the idea that it might turn him on too, I pulled the tip of the tentacle down to wrap my lips around it. His cock throbbed as he watched me, sending a thrill up my spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t resist. Still sucking on the tip, I reached behind and rubbed my middle finger around my tightly puckered ass. My wetness had spread, and with little effort, I pushed my fingertip inside. I moaned around his tentacle, and worked it deeper. My insides squeezed around his cock and my finger, and he groaned in surprise at the suddenly increased stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! I’m gonna… I’m gonna cum!” He squeezed my breasts tightly, straining his hips upward, trying to bury himself even deeper inside me. I closed my eyes, lost in the sensation. Tentacles squirmed around me, squeezing and grasping, thrusting into my mouth and pussy and ass. I surrendered completely, allowing them to claim my body entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He cried out and went rigid below me. I felt a throbbing and spreading warmth inside. I moaned at the sensation and thrust my finger more urgently in and out of my ass. I let the tentacle tip slip from my mouth as the pressure mounted, and opened my eyes again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was gazing up at me with awe, astonished at what was happening. Was this moment as much a culmination of his fantasies as mine? Had he dreamed of me climbing on top of him, impaling myself on his hard cock, and letting him cum deep inside?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My vision blurred into a haze as I started clenching repeatedly, my body grasping and pulling and pushing around my finger and his cock. Flares of color erupted behind my eyelids and I cried out in pleasure, finally collapsing heavily against his chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wrapped his arms around me tightly, and held me as the waves of my orgasm crashed uncontrollably through me and over him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After some time, my heart rate slowed, and I rolled onto my back. We lay there, side by side, breathing heavily and laughing giddily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” he managed to say. “Where did that come from?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Honestly, I’m as surprised as you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I doubt that,” he chuckled. “Hey, uh, can I take the costume off now? It, uh, got a bit wet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” I stammered reluctantly, “of course.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stood, and wrestled it off his body. It took him a few tries. I sat up and watched, studying my emotions. I was nervous. What if the connection I felt disappeared with the costume?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he stood before me, nude. A shapeless mass of shiny purple fabric lay pooled at his feet, stuffed tentacles splayed awkwardly. One googly eye stared blankly at the ceiling. I frowned at it, feeling nothing at all. It was just a costume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cautiously, I raised my eyes to meet his. He’d spotted the expression on my face and hesitated, unsure if I was about to tell him we’d made a mistake and kick him out. He looked worried, but also, I could tell he’d accept my boundaries if I did. A warm feeling bloomed in my chest, and he grinned with relief as it reached my face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I held out my hand and invited him back to bed, eager to feel his arms around me again.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Get Out of the Way!</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/watersports/get-out-of-the-way/"/>
		<published>2025-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-02-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/watersports/get-out-of-the-way/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="watersports" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="pee desperation" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="facial" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/get-out-of-the-way-8ZfMU-nH2_-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Norm!” Rachel called as she knocked on the bathroom door again. “Hurry up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Occupied,” Norm replied calmly through the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, that’s the problem!” She pinched the bridge of her nose and counted to ten. “I know it’s occupied, Norm. But we only have one toilet and I really have to fucking pee!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Almost done,” he responded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sighed, pulled her robe more tightly closed, and stomped off to the kitchen. Fucking Norm was her roommate Laurel’s deadbeat boyfriend, and the bane of her existence. He didn’t pay rent, he didn’t cook, he didn’t have a job. He just hung out in their apartment all day, every day, eating all the snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck, she really had to pee. She’d gone out drinking last night, and woken up with her bladder ready to burst. She danced from foot to foot, waiting to hear the bathroom door open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurel was out all the time, but based on the sounds Rachel heard her make through the walls, Norm had exactly one redeeming quality. Rachel actually had a bit of first-hand experience with Norm’s talent. She’d caught him jerking off with her underwear in her room one day, and in a wild turn of events, ended up sitting on his face until he made her cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thinking about gushing in Norm’s mouth was uncomfortably close to thinking about peeing. She shook her head to clear it and started walking in small, tight circles. How long was he going to take?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurel had actually caught them in the act, and it was hard to say who she was more upset with. After hearing what he’d done, she agreed Norm had crossed a line, but vetoed Rachel’s plan to smother him with her pussy every night for a year as a form of payment. Since then, her underwear stopped mysteriously vanishing, and she and Norm had entered an uneasy truce.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck, she couldn’t hold it much longer. She walked, stiff-legged, down the hall and pounded on the bathroom door again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Occupied.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Norm! I told you, I really have to pee! Hurry up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Almost… done.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something about the way he said it made her pause. With a sinking feeling, she asked, “Norm, what are you doing in there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Edging,” he answered with infuriating calmness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you kidding me? You’re jerking off in there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I’m… edging.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s the fucking difference?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m trying &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to cum… to prolong and… enhance my climax.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God damn it, Norm! Get out of there! I’m trying not to burst!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Me… too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Norm, open this fucking door, or I’ll kick it down!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not locked.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fucking Norm. Of course not. He was probably hoping she’d walk in on him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Norm, I’m not fucking joking. I’m going to count to three, then I’m opening the door. Pull up your damn pants.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can’t… I’m too close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve been… edging all morning…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Two!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If I move… I might lose it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Three!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She threw the door open, revealing Norm sprawled on the toilet seat. His sweatpants were around his ankles, and he was jerking his cock like it owed him money. His head looked swollen and purple, pulsing with his heart beat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Would you STOP stroking it!” She held her robe closed, not liking the way he was looking at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, good idea… Getting too close to the edge.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s not what I meant!” She was so distracted by her need to pee that it took her a moment to notice what he was holding. “Are those my fucking underwear again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he moaned, bringing them to his nose. “You smell so good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought you stopped doing that!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, You were mad—ah—I was throwing them away… after I came in them, so I stopped.” He inhaled deeply, and squeezed his cock. “Now, I just put them back in your dirty laundry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop jerking off with my underwear!” She danced from foot to foot. “And get out of the way!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh… Make up your mind,” he groaned, cock throbbing as he rubbed his thumb over the tip. “You told me to stop—ah—throwing out your panties… and masturbating in your room. What do you want from me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want you to move, quickly!” She let her robe fall open, no longer caring what he might see, and jammed her hand between her legs, frantically trying to hold back the tide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” he groaned, face contorted with a mixture of effort and pleasure. “Told you… too close… to move.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t hold it any longer,” she pleaded, eyes watering. “I’m gonna pee!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here,” he offered, spreading his legs to reveal a small opening to the toilet bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You want me to pee between your legs?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not wasting this—ah—killer orgasm just because you—oh—can’t hold it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Damn it, Norm!” Before she could say anything else, she felt an uncontrollable twinge. There was no longer a choice. She was already starting to pee as she moved forward to straddle him. “Oh, fuck! Fuuuck!” she sobbed in frustration as she lost control of her bladder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She braced herself on the towel bar and stood over him as the golden liquid shot out with surprising force. It jetted against Norm’s thigh as she tried to adjust the angle, aiming for the impossibly small opening between his legs. She overcorrected, and it sprayed directly on his hand and cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So hot!” Norm exclaimed at the unexpected sensation. His cock throbbed and twitched uncontrollably in the stream of urine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sense of relief that flooded her system was overwhelming. She gasped and panted as her bladder released an astonishing amount of fluid. As she finished, she found herself settling her weight onto his legs without meaning to, finally relaxing, until he suddenly stiffened under her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” He cried out. “It’s happening!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She recoiled as hot cum splattered her face. She opened her mouth to protest, but another spurt fell across her lips, and she clamped them shut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Norm’s hand was flying, stroking feverishly between her thighs. His cock was twitching over and over, shooting globs of sticky white spunk to land on her body. They splashed wildly across her breasts, in her hair, on her cheeks, and against her stomach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was shaking, gasping, and groaning. His eyes rolled back in his head. The orgasm lasted a shocking long time. By the end, he was squeezing the last of his cum directly onto her, making a sticky mess in her pubes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh. My. God,” she sputtered, spitting his cum out. “I can’t believe you did that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; did that,” he gasped, still rubbing his cock against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, you came all over me!” She wiped her face in disgust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only after you pissed all over me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I wasn’t trying to!” She got to her feet, and started wiping up his spunk with a towel. “And I certainly didn’t know you get off on that!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t!” he panted. “But, I’d been balanced on the edge for hours, and that extra bit of stimulation was all it took. Wow! That was amazing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m glad you enjoyed yourself,” she snapped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I really did! That was… wow!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m being sarcastic, idiot.” She threw the now-sticky towel on the floor. “Why didn’t you just move? I told you I was going to pee.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why didn’t you just piss in there?” He gestured at the unoccupied shower to his right. “You made a &lt;em&gt;choice&lt;/em&gt; to piss on me when I was that close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? I did not! I couldn’t think straight. You should have moved!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, whatever.” He shrugged, and got to his feet, stepping awkwardly around her into the shower, where he proceeded to turn on the water and peel off his urine-soaked clothes. “I’m gonna rinse off. You should get this mess cleaned up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? Are you fucking kidding me? I’m not cleaning this up. It’s your fault! You clean it up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, I don’t clean up other people’s bodily fluids, that’s disgusting.” He closed his eyes and leaned his head back into the spray. “You’re the one who pissed everywhere, so you’re the one who cleans it up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously?” She sputtered incoherently as he shamelessly started rubbing his still semi-erect cock. “Are you seriously going to jerk off in front of me again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not jerking off in front of you, I’m jerking off, period. You just happen to be here. I think I’ve got another one in me, and I’m gonna see if I can make it five hours this time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You are fucking unbelievable!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, sorry, don’t worry, I don’t need you to piss on me this time. That was interesting, but I don’t think it’s really my thing. Also, your piss smells pretty strong. You should drink more water.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a sudden clatter behind her, and she spun around to find Laurel standing in the hallway. She’d just dropped her keys on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey babe!” Norm called out cheerfully, still stroking his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What the fuck is going on?” Laurel was looking back and forth between Norm in the shower, Rachel’s open robe, and the puddle on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, look, Norm wouldn’t let me use the bathroom…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that cum in your hair?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rachel reached up, and winced as she felt some she’d missed. “Shit, look…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is it in your hair?” Norm laughed. “That’s awesome! I’ve never shot it so far before!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that…” Laurel’s nose crinkled. “Is that piss all over the floor?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry,” Norm answered. “I told Rachel she has to clean it up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look,” Rachel protested, “It’s not what you think. He wouldn’t stop jerking off, and I had to pee &lt;em&gt;so bad&lt;/em&gt;, then he just spread his legs and I couldn’t hold it anymore, and when I peed on him, he came all over me, like a creep!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What the &lt;em&gt;fuck&lt;/em&gt;, you guys,” Laurel yelled. “Again?” She stormed off and slammed her bedroom door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell.” Rachel scowled as Norm continued tugging his cock. “What is &lt;em&gt;wrong&lt;/em&gt; with you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’ll get over it,” he shrugged. “Now, do you mind giving me some privacy?” He raised an eyebrow at her. “Unless you want to join me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get fucked, Norm.” She slammed the bathroom door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait!” he called. “You forgot to clean up!”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Graduation Present</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/cross-dressing/graduation-present/"/>
		<published>2025-02-11T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-02-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/cross-dressing/graduation-present/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="cross-dressing" />
    <category term="bra" />
    <category term="panties" />
    <category term="handjob" />
    <category term="facial" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/graduation-present-sqy2-A3RHU-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Syd, what the fuck am I gonna do?” Ezra groaned. “School’s almost out, and that meathead’s gonna kill me as soon as I step outside.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’m not gonna say I told you so,” Sydney shrugged. “Tiff, you tell him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She warned you, dude.” Tiffany looked up from her phone. “She said if you put that photo in the yearbook, he’d kick your ass.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, but how could I not? It was the perfect shot! The expression on Jack’s face as that goat rammed him in the nuts? Come on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, it was funny,” Kiki agreed, “and it’s what he gets for stealing another school’s mascot. But Syd totally warned you. We all did.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck! This is it. This is how I die. Seconds after the last day of high school, all because you talked me into joining the yearbook club.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Quit your moaning,” Sydney teased, poking him in the shoulder. “You’re being overdramatic. All you have to do is avoid him as we leave school. It’s not like you guys hang out in the same places. He’ll forget all about it. And even if he doesn’t, you’ll be heading to college while he goes to, I dunno, learn how to drive a bulldozer or something.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How am I gonna avoid him? He said he’d be waiting for me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other students shuffled restlessly, picking up their bags and staring at the clock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Sydney considered, “I’ve got an idea, but you’re not gonna like it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Syd, I’ll do anything! Please, save me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bell rang, and everyone streamed for the exit, ignoring the teacher’s requests to slow down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, follow us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ezra let Sydney and the girls lead him into the hall, against the flow of students laughing, cheering, and heading for the front doors. As they waded through the crush, the crowd eventually thinned until they led him to a girl’s bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are we doing here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ll see,” she grinned, pulling him through the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inside, two junior girls at the sink squealed at his presence, and left quickly, laughing and winking. Ezra grinned sheepishly and waved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Sydney said, pushing him toward the far wall. “Take off your clothes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You heard me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is this a prank? You’re gonna make me strip, and then take off with my clothes? Real funny, Syd.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you wanna get your ass kicked?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you trust me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I guess?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then strip. And face the wall.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you don’t catch an eyeful.” She gestured. “Go on. Turn around.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, fine,” he grumbled, turning away and starting to undress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kiki, you’ve got your gym clothes, right? Okay, change into your shorts and give me your leggings and skirt. Tiffany, let me have your bra. And I’ll donate my shirt. I can wear Ezra’s button-up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The girls started laughing when they figured out what she was suggesting. By the time Ezra had stripped down to just his boxers, they had assembled an outfit for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Underwear too, Ez.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can’t wear boxers under leggings, they’ll bunch up weird.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s your plan? Dress me up like a girl?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure. Lucky for you, you’ve got a slim build, so most of this stuff should fit you okay.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is humiliating,” he groused, shucking his boxers and trying awkwardly to pull on Kiki’s leggings while not letting them see his junk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ha!” She laughed as she put on his shirt, tucking it in and rolling the sleeves. “Be glad I’m not making you wear a thong to get the full experience.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I put this on?” He frowned, holding up the bra. Kiki and Tiffany burst out laughing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh come on,” Sydney teased, “you must have taken a girl’s bra off before, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, yeah, but that’s not the same thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure it is,” she laughed, helping him pull the straps up his arms. “In reverse. Hold on, I need to loosen these up. You’ve got broader shoulders than Tiff, but I think it’ll still fit…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oof, it’s tight!” He complained, moving his arms awkwardly. “This is really uncomfortable.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me about it!” Sydney giggled, snapping his bra strap. “Here, let me stuff some toilet paper in the cups to pad them out a bit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe I’m doing this,” he grumbled, pulling her shirt on over his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, careful, you’ll rip it! I like that top. You can’t just tug it on like a cheap t-shirt!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, how do I look?” He asked grumpily, putting his sneakers back on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, you forgot the skirt,” she snorted, pointing to the obvious bulge in the crotch of his leggings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course,” he sighed, stepping into it. She helped him with the zipper, then the girls moved back to look at him critically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I dunno,” Kiki sniffed. “The shoes are all wrong.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And the shirt’s too tight,” Tiffany noted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, it’s his face,” Sydney observed. “We have to do something with his hair, and he needs some makeup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Makeup?” He looked nervous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh please, you’ll wear a bra and a skirt, but you draw the line at makeup?” Sydney laughed. “Just be thankful your hair is long enough to pass. If it were cut short, we’d have to borrow a big hat from the theater department.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiki set about brushing his hair, while Tiffany and Sydney gave him a quick makeover. After a bit of foundation and eyeliner, they all stepped back again to examine their work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, it’s not terrible,” Kiki shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I like how you did his hair,” Tiffany agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Honestly, you’re kinda cute,” Sydney grinned, gesturing at the mirror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh.” He tried to frown, but even he had to admit the transformation was more convincing than he expected. “This might actually work.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course it’ll work,” Sydney said confidently, bumping fists with Kiki. “And if not, we’ll get to watch you get your ass kicked in a skirt, so, you know, win-win.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They left the bathroom and headed for the front doors. Most of the students had already left the building, so there wasn’t much crowd cover as they stepped outside. Sydney motioned for Ezra to walk behind her, with Kiki and Tiffany at her sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack was standing by the flagpole, arms crossed and glowering. He was flanked by three friends, each bigger than the last. When he saw them leave the building, he called out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey Sydney, where’s your loser friend? The longer he makes me wait, the harder I’m gonna beat his ass.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck off, Jack,” she called out cheerily. He glared as they giggled and kept walking, but turned his attention back to the front door, muttering something to his friends. A few minutes later, Ezra laughed with relief as they boarded a bus, sitting as a group in the back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe it worked! He didn’t recognize me at all!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told you,” Sydney beamed. “Now cross your legs, you’re sitting like a dude.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She stifled a laugh as Ezra exaggeratedly crossed his legs, placed his hands on his knees, batted his eyelashes, and smiled at them all demurely. Kiki and Tiffany lost it. Sydney stuck out her tongue at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey,” he asked, looking around for the first time, “where are we going?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To the mall. We can find a dressing room for you to change in, and then you can buy us all fries to thank us for saving your life.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool.” He nodded, then scrunched up his face. He rolled his shoulders a few times, trying to adjust his bra band. “How do you wear one of these all the time? This is so uncomfortable!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Welcome to being a woman,” Kiki observed dryly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right? My mom freaks if I go out without a bra,” Tiffany said, “but sometimes I take it off as soon as I get to school.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, as much as I appreciate the loan,” he grimaced, “I’ll be happy to give this back.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, if the fit’s the problem,” Sydney grinned, “we could get you something in your size? Maybe you’d prefer a different color? Something lacy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ha. Ha.” He turned to look out the window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tiffany and Kiki distracted themselves by looking at something on their phones. Sydney found herself watching Ezra. Every few seconds, he would shift awkwardly in his seat. He uncrossed his legs, stretched, slouched, then sat up and crossed them again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everything okay there, Ez? You look like my dog when it needs to go outside.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh?” He looked startled, then flushed as if caught doing something inappropriate. “No, I’m just a little, um, uncomfortable.” He adjusted his skirt nervously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh?” She leaned closer, sensing something interesting. “Uncomfortable how, exactly?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just, you know, wearing women’s clothing,” he mumbled, still fidgeting with his skirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, it’s something more than that. I can tell.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, it’s just that these clothes are a little, um, snug.” He looked deeply uncomfortable. “In places.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In what places?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just, places, that’s all.” He nervously shot a glance at Tiffany and Kiki, who were still absorbed in whatever they were looking at.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, fine, just keep your voice down.” He leaned closer and whispered conspiratorially. “The, um, leggings are a bit tight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tight?” She grinned, deliberately misunderstanding him. “What, like, they’re cutting off your circulation?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, that’s not, um…” He grimaced, putting his hands over his lap. “They’re a bit tight in the, you know, crotch region.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god! Are you hard right now?” She eagerly tried to lift his skirt to peek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop that!” He hissed, swatting her hand away. “Why are you being weird?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you &lt;em&gt;into&lt;/em&gt; this?” she whispered with delight. “Is wearing our clothes turning you on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! No, that’s not it. I told you, they’re just kinda tight, so there’s a bit of, like, pressure. It’s a normal reaction!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure, it’s a normal reaction. If you’re excited by wearing women’s clothing!” She tried again to reach under his skirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not! Shut up!” He looked nervously at the other girls again. “Stop it!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before she could get past his blocking, the bus stopped at the mall. Ezra got quickly to his feet, and exited the bus, closely followed by Sydney and the girls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they walked through the mall, she stared openly, hoping to catch a peek of the erection tenting his skirt, but he kept his bag in front of him, blocking her view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they got to the clothing store, Kiki and Tiffany wandered off to do a bit of a shopping, while Sydney led Ezra to the dressing rooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you doing?” he whispered when she followed him in, shutting the door behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, &lt;em&gt;now&lt;/em&gt; you can show me,” she grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not showing you!” He continued holding his bag protectively in front of himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why not? Tiff and Kiki aren’t here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s not why! This is weird. Why are you being like this? You’ve never shown any interest in me before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ve never dressed like a girl and popped a hard-on in front of me before.” She bit her lip. “And, I wasn’t lying, you look cute like this. I think I’m kinda into it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does that make you a lesbian?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does dressing this way make you a girl?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then, I guess not,” she grinned. “Come on, put your bag down.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh. Fine.” Despite his protests, he allowed her to take his bag and set it on the bench. He crossed his arms awkwardly. “Now what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Show me what you’re hiding under that skirt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sighing dramatically, he slowly raised the front of his skirt for her. His erection was pressed against his stomach, held in place by the leggings. She could see the shape of his shaft and the ridge of his head. As she stared, it twitched, straining against the fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“See? I told you, it’s just a natural reaction to how tight this is.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing to do with the clothes?” She scoffed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nope.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re telling me,” she murmured, stepping closer, “that it doesn’t turn you on at all to be wearing Kiki’s leggings, that touched her the same way they’re touching you now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” he protested nervously. “They’re just tight, is all.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re not even a little aroused,” she breathed, hooking a finger under the neckline of his shirt, and tracing the edge of his bra strap. “To be wearing Tiffany’s bra? Knowing that her little tits were in there right before you put it on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“N-no,” he breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look in the mirror,” she purred, nudging his chin and meeting his gaze in the reflection. “You’re not excited by the sight of yourself? Look how good you look with a bit of lipstick.” She groped his padded chest. “Tell me you don’t like the way you look with breasts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh, I mean,” he stammered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How would you have felt if I’d given you my underwear?” She leaned closer, brushing her lips against his ear. “Would it turn you on to feel your hard cock straining against lace?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” he groaned as she reached down, caressing the length of him through the leggings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Would you like that?” She pushed him against the wall, pressing her body against his. “We can do it now, if you want.” His cock throbbed in her grasp. “Do you want to wear my panties?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” he gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Her heart pounded. “You want that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” he shuddered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me,” she growled, squeezing him tightly. “Tell me what you want.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I—ah!—I want to wear your panties!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good, take off your leggings.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, she stepped back, unbuttoning her shorts and stepping out of them. Ezra stared hungrily at her pink lace underwear. He unzipped his skirt and clumsily peeled off the leggings, kicking them both to one side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They stood breathlessly before each other. His erection jutted forward, bobbing with anticipation. She started unbuttoning her shirt. He watched with wide eyes and followed her lead, pulling his shirt over his head until he stood before her wearing only a bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now you see why I couldn’t loan you mine,” she grinned, letting his shirt slide down her arms to reveal her bare breasts. His breath caught, and his cock twitched at the sight of her small, dark nipples, already puckered tight. She hooked her thumbs in the waistband of her panties and slowly lowered them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here you go,” she said, offering them to him. “Sorry they’re a bit damp. You’re not the only one who’s excited.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He took them from her, speechless, and held them up before him. It looked like he could barely believe what he was doing as he cautiously stepped in and pulled them up. She bit her fingertip as she watched the pink lace rise. It was deeply erotic to see him putting on her underwear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he finally pulled them all the way up, he let out a shaky gasp. The lace couldn’t contain his full erection, which jutted up past the waistband. He stared at himself in the mirror, wearing a bra and panties. He seemed to have forgotten that she was standing next to him, completely naked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look at you,” she purred, stepping behind him and looking at his reflection in the mirror. “How does it feel?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tight,” he gasped, cock straining against the lace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But how do &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; feel?” She slipped her hands over his sides, tracing the waistband.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sexy,” he breathed, barely audible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You are sexy,” she murmured in his ear. “You look so good like this.” Unconsciously, she pressed her pelvis forward, grinding against him from behind. Her nipples dragged down his back, sending little sparks of stimulation through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shivered as she reached around to touch him. As she grazed her hand over the head of his cock, he twitched and a squirt of precum lubricated her palm. She rubbed it against him, savoring the way he moaned for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You look so fucking sexy wearing my panties,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both of their gazes were fixed on his reflection, on the way he looked. She teased her fingertips around the rim of his head. His hands moved restlessly, sliding up his chest and over his bra, squeezing the padded cups as if they were his breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rocked her body against him, squeezing her thighs together. His skin felt hot against hers, and her body was crackling with tension. Unable to resist any longer, she reached into his panties to fully wrap her hand around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” she encouraged him. “Look at yourself. You look so naughty wearing a bra and lace underwear as I stroke your hard fucking cock.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted, and braced himself against the mirror, gasping at his reflection. His cock throbbed in her grasp, and she stroked eagerly up and down the length of his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so sexy like this,” she moaned, squirming against his back. “I want to make you cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His head glistened, smeared with precum, as he thrust enthusiastically into her grip. But his eyes were locked on his own reflection, as if he was fucking himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that’s right,” she encouraged him with a constant stream of filth whispered in his ear. “Keep going. You’re so hard. You must be close. I want you to blow your load all over that sexy bitch in the mirror. She wants it. Look how desperate she is for it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Syd!” He gasped, leaning against the mirror with two hands, repeatedly pumping his thick cock into her grasp. She moaned, feeling a wave of lust roll through her body as he strained, ass clenching against her pelvis. “I’m gonna…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you gonna cum for me?” She whispered urgently in his ear, praying no one would hear and interrupt them. All she wanted right now was to watch him cum, hard, wearing her panties. “Do it,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m cumming,” he moaned, as his entire body went rigid, just before his cock started pulsing in her hand. She squeezed the base as rope after rope of thick white spunk sprayed against the mirror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” she squeaked, her body clenching excitedly at the sight. “Come on, Ezra! Cum all over her!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the first few powerful shots, he shuddered, and the rest of his cum spurted over her fingers. She leaned against him, happily milking the last of his orgasm, until he dropped to his knees on the floor. She followed him down, breathing heavily against his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was awesome,” she grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” he panted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked at their reflections in the mirror. He was rocking gently in place and gasping for breath. One bra strap had slipped off his shoulder, and the tissues had fallen out of that cup. Her arm was wrapped around his waist, hand snaked under the pink lace, still holding his softening cock. She saw herself peeking over his shoulder. His eyes were closed, and…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, Ezra, look!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” He glanced up and opened his eyes wide in surprise. “Oh!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’d collapsed down to where his cum, splattered and dripping down the surface of the mirror, looked like it had been sprayed across his face. For a moment, the illusion was convincing, and she seemed to be looking at a flushed young woman with cum all over her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look at that,” she laughed. “You gave her a facial!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He didn’t answer, but his cock twitched in her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she grinned, coming to a sudden decision. “Get dressed. We’ve got to go.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why?” He struggled to stop looking at his reflection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because,” she answered, standing up and pulling on her shorts. “We’re going underwear shopping.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We are?” He looked unsure as she buttoned up her shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Call it a graduation present,” she said, pulling him up and giving him a kiss on the cheek. “Now, hurry up. I’ll go tell Kiki and Tiff.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” he said, then hesitated. “Wait, Syd, what do you mean tell them?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry, they love shopping!” She giggled as she slipped out the door. “Hurry up!”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Stacy’s Family: an erotic short story collection</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/stacys-family-ebook/"/>
		<published>2025-01-26T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-01-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/stacys-family-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="wife" />
    <category term="handyman" />
    <category term="older man" />
    <category term="younger woman" />
    <category term="schoolgirl uniform" />
    <category term="panties" />
    <category term="stepsister" />
    <category term="stepbrother" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="facial" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/stacys-family-c8y0JctBvH-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Four hot stories about a family with sensual needs. Stacy’s mom is a lonely housewife, trying to catch the handyman’s attention. Stacy’s dad doesn’t know it, but her best friend has a plan to seduce him. Stacy’s sister is at a sleepover where her friend’s brother can’t stop staring at her school uniform. And Stacy herself just learned that her stepbrother has a stepsister fetish. Each story in this collection is hotter than the last, so get ready to meet Stacy’s family!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruby Pink loves reading erotica but was frustrated to find so many featuring shallow women with no agency. She took up the pen to bring us steamy shorts about real women who aren’t just props in male fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DV4PFWDN"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Stacy’s Family 4: Stacy’s Stepbrother</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/4-stacys-stepbrother/"/>
		<published>2025-01-20T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-01-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/4-stacys-stepbrother/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="taboo" />
    <category term="stepsister" />
    <category term="stepbrother" />
    <category term="teasing" />
    <category term="sexual tension" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/stacys-stepbrother--iL6qRSgVF-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Stacy heaved a sigh, pushed back from the dining room table, and stretched. Strewn around her laptop were assorted reference books, sticky notes, and printouts with colorful highlights. She’d spent the last several minutes repeatedly reading the same sentence, unable to make any sense of it. It was ten o’clock, and time to admit she wouldn’t make any more useful progress on her senior project tonight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moving to the living room, she settled on the sofa, pulled up her favorite movie, and tried to switch off her brain. She’d seen it so many times she didn’t need to pay attention. It was just a comforting distraction as she wrapped a warm blanket around her legs and fooled around on her phone. She was finally starting to relax when her stepbrother Hudson vaulted onto the other side of the sofa, nearly spilling his oversized bowl of cereal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatcha watching?” he asked through a mouthful of food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A rom-com,” she answered curtly, annoyed by his intrusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool. Mind if I sit here? Your stuff’s all over the table.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suit yourself,” she said, biting back a reply about how she didn’t have anywhere else to work. She wasn’t really mad at &lt;em&gt;him&lt;/em&gt;. After all, it wasn’t his fault that his dad married her mom last year. Or that when they moved in, she’d had to give up her bedroom for him. She grudgingly admitted it made sense for her and her sister Flora to share a room, since they spent alternate weeks at their dad’s house. Even so, the loss of personal space was aggravating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s this about, then?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Those two,” she said, gesturing at the main characters, “hate each other, but they’re pretending to be in love to make his ex jealous and stop her parents trying to set her up with someone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” he nodded, taking another bite. “Sounds like it’s based on the Shakespeare play we just read in English class.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I guess.” Stacy rolled her eyes. Her biggest problem with Hudson was that he was boring. The most middle-of-the-road boy she’d ever met. Perfectly average in every way. His tastes were predictably mainstream. No hobbies to speak of. No girlfriend. He didn’t drink or party. Even his friends were boring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, he stopped asking questions, so she was able to mostly ignore him. He finished his cereal, but seemed interested enough in the movie to stick around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a while, she found herself getting drowsy. She slouched lower until her head was resting on the back of the couch. The familiar movie lulled her overworked brain into a state of relaxation. She pulled the blanket higher as her eyes drifted shut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she opened them again, the movie had ended, and it was past midnight. She blinked slowly, trying to figure out what woke her up. The house was quiet, but she could hear something out of place. A quiet noise she didn’t quite recognize. Blearily, she looked to her side. Hudson was still there, staring at his phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was something different about his posture, though. He wasn’t scrolling idly through social media or playing a game. Sitting almost unnaturally still, his attention was entirely focused on the screen. She couldn’t make it out, but there was a lot of movement, and the sound was…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh! Holy shit. Was he really watching porn here in the living room? On the couch next to her?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now fully awake, she felt a rush of conflicting emotions. Astonishment. Annoyance. Frustration. Embarrassment. Concern. But all of those were quickly drowned out by one overwhelming reaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without a doubt, this was the most interesting thing Hudson had ever done. Outrageous, sure, but she had so many questions! Why didn’t he just go to his room? Did he watch porn out here all the time, or was this a spur of the moment thing? She supposed she should be upset, but he didn’t seem to be paying any attention to her, and hadn’t done anything overtly creepy. It was almost like he just got distracted and forgot she was there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And what kind of porn was he watching? She strained her ears for any clues, but could only make out the vague sound of a woman performatively moaning. That ruled out gay porn, she supposed, a little disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As slowly as possible, she shifted in his direction, trying to catch a glimpse. Focused on the screen, he didn’t notice her creeping closer, inch by inch, until at last, she could see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The camera framed a young woman on her back, grabbing her knees. The man holding the camera was urgently fucking her. With each thrust, her tits bounced and she cried out. Suddenly, the man groaned and pulled out, spraying cum all over her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hudson closed the video and scrolled through a list of others. She tried not to laugh when she saw he was browsing the stepsister category. It made sense, she supposed. Almost overnight, he’d gone from being an only child to living with two hot girls he wasn’t related to. Who wouldn’t be curious?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He picked a new video, and she couldn’t help but notice the girl had glasses and dark hair like her. Of course, the previous girl was blonde with fake tits, so that might not mean anything. She watched, along with him, as the “step-siblings” wrestled over the TV remote until the guy’s cock slipped implausibly out of his shorts and into her pussy. They pretended to be shocked for about three seconds, then proceeded to fuck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole thing was predictable, except for the framing device that they were meant to be related. She knew it was fake, but even so, she was surprised to find herself getting into it. The hook was enough to keep the encounter excitingly scandalous. She imagined they were fucking like they were afraid of getting caught.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hudson was enjoying it too, judging by the erection tenting his pants. She bit her lip as she watched him slowly rub himself. This was wrong. Sure, he’d crossed the line first by playing porn in front of her, but was she really going to let him keep going while she pretended to be asleep? What if he actually pulled it out? Some part of her wanted to let him, but she knew there was only one way to handle this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” she blurted, leaning closer. “What are you doing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” He startled, almost dropping his phone as he tried to close the video. “Nothing!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t lie,” she laughed, snatching it from his hands and holding it out of reach. “You’re watching porn!” On-screen, the girl who looked like her moaned as the guy rolled her onto her back and started thrusting between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Give it back!” He awkwardly tried to grab his phone without touching her, clearly hoping she wouldn’t notice his hard-on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let’s see what else you’ve been watching,” she grinned, holding him off with one hand and scrolling with the other. “Oh, look, stepsister videos!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, that’s not…” He risked getting a bit closer, pushing her arm out of the way and leaning over to reach for the phone. “Stop that!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stepsister and brother have fun while parents aren’t at home,” she read, scanning the titles. “Fucking my stepsister after she teases me. Sharing a bed and cumming in stepsister. Ooh, here’s a good one, stepsister fucks stepbrother to borrow his car!” She laughed, still swatting his hands away. “Is this what you like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He lunged forward, knocking them both over. She squealed as she fell onto her back, and he landed heavily on top. Triumphantly, he wrestled his phone from her grasp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, what’s your plan, Hudson?” She grinned up at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh?” It took him a moment to realize the position they’d landed in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Gonna act out your fantasy?” She squirmed under his weight, feeling his stiff cock pressing into her leggings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up,” he retorted, and tried to pull away, but she wrapped her legs around his to hold him in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good point, we’ll have to be quiet,” she teased, rolling her hips. “Wouldn’t want anyone to hear you &lt;em&gt;fucking&lt;/em&gt; your &lt;em&gt;stepsister&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Knock it off!” Blushing furiously, he broke free and stormed out of the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, come back, I want to borrow your car!” she called after him, laughing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was still laughing and heckling him the next morning as he made coffee before school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, like, is it &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; stepsisters that do it for you, or do you watch other stuff, too? How do you feel about babysitters? Or nurses?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He glowered, but did not reply as he shook the grounds into the compost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why are you being so mean to him about this?” Flora asked as she walked into the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you kidding?” Stacy crowed. “This is the most interesting thing about him by far! A stepsister fetish when he has two stepsisters? Come on!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You told Flora?” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, &lt;em&gt;immediately&lt;/em&gt;,” she laughed. “This was too juicy not to share.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re not gonna tell my dad, are you?” He looked horrified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not after the way he overreacted to Flora that time,” she frowned. “He’d probably blame me for this, and pack me off to a convent.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flora nodded, Hudson breathed a sigh of relief, and Stacy pounced on him again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about threesomes? Everyone likes threesomes, right? What do you prefer, two guys or two girls? Does everyone in the threesome need to be a step-sibling?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gritted his teeth and rinsed the coffee strainer in the sink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Give him a break,” Flora scowled over a piece of toast. “Everyone watches porn. It’s not a big deal.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But I have so many questions! Like, what about boobs? Do you like big ones like Flora’s, or little ones like mine?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His only response was to grip the edge of the sink in frustration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You don’t wanna answer in front of Flora, huh?” She grinned. “Smart. You can tell me later. No need to hurt her feelings. Let’s talk pubes. Do you prefer shaved or…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hudson turned and doused her with cold water from the sink sprayer. She sputtered in shock and disbelief. Wiping the water from her eyes, she saw his expression change. The anger drained away as his eyes widened in surprise. Following his gaze downward, she realized the water had soaked her top, turning it nearly transparent. Clapping her hands over her chest, she ran from the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she fled, she heard Flora say “Don’t worry about it, she was being a total bitch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacy spent the entire day thinking about how to get back at Hudson. That night, she waited until she heard him getting ready to take a shower. When he stepped out of his room with a towel draped over his shoulder, she followed him down the hall to the bathroom. Just before he could close the door, she blocked it and slipped in after him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you doing?” he asked, backing away as she closed the door behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We need to talk,” she replied cryptically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you followed me into the bathroom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Privately.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever.” He scowled and draped his towel over the shower rod. “You’re just here to give me more shit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not,” she said quietly. “In fact, I want to apologize.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You do?” he regarded her warily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, Flora was right. I shouldn’t have teased you. I just thought it was funny! I’m sorry, I didn’t realize how upset you were until you turned the sprayer on me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right.” He rubbed his neck awkwardly. “I’m sorry, too. I didn’t mean to get your shirt wet like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright.” She leaned against the door, looking pointedly at him, and letting the moment stretch uncomfortably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And, um, I’m also sorry about watching porn on the couch by you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was super weird, dude.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I’m sorry! I thought you were asleep. The girl in the movie was pretty hot, and when it ended I was a little turned on, and I kinda forgot you were there. I swear, I wasn’t trying to be a creep or anything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I figured,” she shrugged. “You’ve never done anything sketchy before. I guess that’s why I was more curious than upset.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, is that all you wanted to talk about? Because I was gonna take a shower.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, um, there was something else.” She fidgeted with her shirt. “In the kitchen, you were kinda staring at me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry! I just got surprised…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And also last night on the couch, when you were on top of me? I could feel you had a hard-on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I swear that was…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you have a crush on me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, you’re into stepsister porn. You got hard watching a girl who looks like me. And then you were staring at my boobs. You can’t blame me for wondering.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, no! Fuck no, I swear!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She scowled at his overreaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t mean it that way,” he grimaced. “Like, you’re attractive and stuff. And yeah, I got turned on, but I promise, I’m not obsessed with you or anything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, you &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; think I’m hot, but you’re not &lt;em&gt;into&lt;/em&gt; me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yes?” He was clearly unsure if that was the correct response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” She considered for a moment. “Then show me your cock.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? How does that follow?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s only fair,” she shrugged. “You basically got to see me topless. This makes us even.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No it doesn’t! Me kinda seeing your nipples through a wet shirt and you wanting to look at my dick aren’t the same thing at all!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever! You watched porn next to me while I was asleep. You owe me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, okay.” He frowned. “Did you follow me in here just to see my junk?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Pretty much.” She bit her thumb. “Plus, if I’m being honest, after it poked me, I got a bit curious about what you’re packing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine. But you have to promise not to tell anyone. Not even Flora!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cross my heart.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With obvious reluctance, he peeled off his shirt and dropped it on the floor. She grinned with anticipation. He sighed, and stepped out of his joggers. Now fully nude, he stood before her, giving her a good look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There. You’ve seen it. Happy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, now get it hard.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? That wasn’t the deal. You just said you wanted to see it!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, &lt;em&gt;obviously&lt;/em&gt;, I meant hard.” She rolled her eyes. “Who wants to see a limp dick?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No way!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s the big deal?” she shrugged. “I already felt it once.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was an accident!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Again,” she said pointedly, “you &lt;em&gt;owe&lt;/em&gt; me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not that simple,” he complained, even as he wrapped his hand around it. “I don’t know if I can do it with you here!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You didn’t have any problems last night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s different! You weren’t watching!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’m definitely watching this time,” she winked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grimaced, closed his eyes, and started squeezing and pulling. She stared, fascinated by the way he manipulated it. However, after a few minutes, he remained stubbornly soft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This isn’t working,” he sighed. “I’m too self-conscious with you here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm,” she considered. “Would it help if I took my top off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” He blinked in shock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, you seemed to enjoy getting a peek at my nipples this morning. Would it help you get hard if I let you see them again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, yeah. That would help.” He hesitated. “Are you sure?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shrugged, pulled her shirt over her head, and removed her bra. He stared as she stood topless before him. She cupped her breasts, gently squeezing them together. Unconsciously, he started pulling on his cock again, which quickly began to swell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, look at him grow,” she giggled. “I’d ask if you like my boobs, but it’s pretty obvious you do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he mumbled, “They’re, uh, they’re…” He trailed off as she pulled on her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They’re sensitive,” she breathed, as they puckered and tightened from the stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can see that.” There was naked hunger in his eyes. If she’d had any doubt that he was secretly into her, it was gone now. She had him exactly where she wanted. Anything she asked, he would do now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Keep going,” she purred. “I want you to get as hard as you were last night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned, taking longer strokes as his cock continued to grow. The head was protruding now, swollen and eager-looking. It twitched and strained, as if trying to get closer to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just like that,” she encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hudson gasped in surprise as she lowered to her knees in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Settle down,” she murmured. “I just want to see it better.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had to admit, Hudson had a pretty nice package. It looked like it would fit nicely in her hand… Or elsewhere. She bit her lip and squeezed her legs together as she considered how aroused he was by her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so hard now,” she said approvingly. “Just from seeing me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, er, no?” he stammered. “I mean, any guy would get turned on in this situation!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, bro,” she grinned. “Just admit you have a stepsister fetish!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t,” he protested weakly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You really do,” she assured him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A drop of precum appeared on the tip. His cock was pointing directly at her face. He pumped faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It turns you on to see me down here, doesn’t it?” Heart pounding, she licked her lips and looked up at him. “To see your stepsister so close to your cock?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh,” he hesitated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why can’t you just admit it? You can barely control yourself with me here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I’m just doing what you…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What would you do if I said I wanted to see you cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was hard to say who was more surprised by that question, her or him. She hadn’t intended to go this far. But now that she was here, she wanted him to admit it so badly. If she just went a bit further, she could &lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; him say it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stacy, I…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if I wanted to help?” She leaned closer, until her lips were nearly touching him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” His cock throbbed excitedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, no. This was a bad idea. This was &lt;em&gt;such&lt;/em&gt; a bad idea. What was she doing? Was she really considering this? She had to stop. How could she salvage the situation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, you wish!” She laughed a little too loudly and gave his balls a flick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ow!” He covered himself and sputtered in confusion. “What the fuck?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you really think I was gonna give you head?” She scoffed as she quickly pulled her shirt back on. No time for the bra. She reached for the doorknob.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But you… I… Fuck!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told you, I just wanted to see it. Now we’re even.” She blew him a kiss and slipped out the door, leaving him holding his dick in frustration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the hall, she shook her head, trying to clear the haze of arousal. What the fuck was that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next day, he avoided her, which suited Stacy fine. She was still struggling to figure out her own feelings, and didn’t need to deal with his at the same time. But that evening, he sat down next to her on the couch again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you want?” She crossed her arms and scowled at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh,” he hesitated, thrown off by her hostility. “I just figured we should talk.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s there to talk about?” She gestured dismissively. “I told you, we’re even.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stacy, come on. That wasn’t just you getting even, admit it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It got a little out of hand,” she conceded. “But it’s your own fault for getting so turned on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My fault!” He lowered his voice and checked to make sure no one was around. “You deliberately got me that turned on!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All I told you to do was get it hard.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You took your shirt off!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only to get you over your little performance issue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You got on your knees and kept egging me on!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I’m not the one with the stepsister fetish.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why are you lying?” He hissed. “I saw it in your eyes. You were just as turned on as I was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was just playing a part,” she sniffed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then why did you run away?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that what this is about?” she asked mockingly. “You’re mad I didn’t stick around longer? Beg you to cum all over my tits? Help you act out your fantasies about me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Argh!” He clenched his fists in frustration. “Why are you being like this? What did I do to piss you off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What did you do?” she snapped. “That’s the whole problem! You didn’t &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; anything.” It all came rushing out of her. “You’re so boring! Just when I thought I’d finally found something interesting about you, you’re too chicken to even talk about it. And then, you sprayed me down like &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; was the weird one! So, yeah, I decided to get even.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“By teasing me? By leading me on? By accusing me of having a fetish?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Because you &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt;!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You do! And you’re too afraid to admit what you want.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And you think that’s you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; it’s me. I saw the way you looked at me last night. If I hadn’t left, you totally would have let me seduce you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t understand! You sound like you’re mad nothing happened, but you’re the one that left.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because you weren’t going to &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; anything unless I &lt;em&gt;told&lt;/em&gt; you to do it. You can’t even admit you have a stepsister fetish!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t have a fetish, I’m just into &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glared at him. He glared back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You said you weren’t,” she hissed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t want to make it weird.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Too late.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, you want me to, what,” he whispered, “admit that you turn me on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For a start,” she dared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, you turn me on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, you’re such a pushover.” She rolled her eyes. “You’re basically letting me bully you into admitting it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, do you want me to push you down and &lt;em&gt;show&lt;/em&gt; you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, at least that wouldn’t be boring!” she snapped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine!” He grabbed her knees and pulled her sideways until she fell onto her back. In one quick movement, he got between her legs, settling his weight against her. Braced on his elbows, he stared defiantly into her eyes. “Feel that?” He pressed his pelvis against her, and once again, she felt his erection pressing through her leggings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you just get hard in the middle of a fight?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This has been really confusing!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a long moment, they stayed like that, staring into each other’s eyes while his cock throbbed against her. She felt flushed. Her heart pounded with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now?” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was gonna ask you,” he admitted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck’s sake,” she groaned. “You’re hopeless. Even now, you can’t say what you want?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, fine.” He swallowed nervously. “You were right. I do want you to go down on me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Say more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t stop thinking about it.” He continued with more enthusiasm when she nodded encouragingly. “About how your tongue would feel on my cock. Last night, I was so close. After you left, when I finished, I imagined cumming in your mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot,” she breathed, rolling her hips. He twitched, and she felt an answering flutter inside. “Sit up and pull down your pants.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, right here?” He sat up, glancing nervously over his shoulder toward the dark hallway. “Someone could come in!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They won’t,” she whispered, rolling onto her hands and knees. “Our parents are asleep, and Flora’s light is off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” he breathed, pushing his pants down far enough to let his cock spring free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacy eagerly wrapped her lips around his tip and swirled her tongue. He was almost as hard as last night. She wrapped her hands around his shaft and started stroking. The low groans he made as she bobbed her head sent a thrill down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe this is happening,” he whispered. “Fuck, your mouth is so hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned happily as he throbbed on her tongue. Already, he was lifting his hips, trying to go deeper. She pushed down on his stomach, wanting him to sit still and let her control the pace. In response, he put his hand on her head and encouraged her to go faster. Normally, she hated that, but it excited her to feel him asserting himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, it was so exciting, she almost got them caught. She’d found her rhythm, and was working to take him into her throat. She was almost there when a door opened in the hallway behind them. He tapped her head and frantically scrambled to pull his pants up. She didn’t want to stop, and swallowed him deeper. He groaned quietly at the sensation, until finally, he grabbed her hair and pulled her off his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sat up, wiping her chin, just as Flora walked in to find them sitting in the dark. She paused on her way to the kitchen, and peered suspiciously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you guys doing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing,” blurted Hudson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We were just talking things over,” Stacy answered calmly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In the dark?” Flora asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ve been talking for a while, and didn’t notice how dark it got.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flora shrugged and walked into the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go to your room,” Stacy whispered to Hudson, “and stay hard for me. I’ll join you soon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded eagerly, and shuffled awkwardly down the hall to his room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes later, Flora came in with a glass of water and sat beside her on the couch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is everything alright?” she asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, we’re good,” Stacy reassured her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool. I don’t like when you two are fighting. It makes me feel like I have to pick a side.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know. It’s okay, we apologized, and worked it out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good. You wanna talk about it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thanks, but I’m all talked out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay. I’m heading to bed. Love you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Love you, too. I’m gonna stay up for a while.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They hugged, and Flora walked away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacy forced herself to count to 100, then calmly walked down the hall to Hudson’s room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His light was off. She opened the door without knocking, and quickly slipped inside. Hudson was sitting on his bed, eyes wide with nervous anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told you to stay hard for me,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I did,” he murmured, reaching into his pants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” she smiled. “Then get undressed, so I can finish what I started.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have to be quiet,” he said as he stripped, carelessly tossing his clothes in the corner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know,” she grinned, pulling off her top. “This used to be my room, remember? I know how thin the walls are.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right, right.” He rubbed himself as she shimmied out of her leggings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God, you’re so sexy,” he breathed as she walked slowly toward him, savoring the way his eyes explored her nude body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lie down,” she purred, giving him a gentle push. He shuffled backwards onto the bed, settling with his head on the pillow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She followed, crawling up to kneel at his side. His cock twitched eagerly against his stomach. She lowered herself, and let him feel her breath on his skin. He shivered as she licked up the length of his shaft. It strained upward, rising to meet her, and she wrapped her lips around his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he groaned as she swirled her tongue around him. “Stacy, that feels so fucking good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wasting no time, she resumed bobbing her head, letting him slip deeper each time. He throbbed in her mouth, and she felt her body answer in kind. This was why she’d run away last night. On some level, she’d known that if she actually wrapped her lips around him, she wouldn’t be able to stop. And then she would have had to confront the fact that she wanted him, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shifted sideways on the bed, reaching out to run a hand up the back of her thigh. His touch sent a shiver of sensation up her spine. She pushed down until she felt resistance when he hit the back of her mouth. He moaned again, and it was all the encouragement she needed. With another swallow, she took him deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stifled a cry of pleasure as he slipped into her throat. His cock pulsed, and his thighs strained as she struggled to hold him there without choking. His hand squeezed her shoulder, and he lifted his hips, wanting more. She slapped his thigh as she pulled back, gasping for breath, then did it again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She couldn’t believe this was happening! It was shocking, how much she turned him on, and how much that turned her on. Her insides clenched excitedly as she let Hudson experience his fantasy. How many times had he dreamed about her lips on his cock?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He groaned quietly, straining upward. Her eyes watered, and she swallowed repeatedly, until at last her lips reached his root. She could feel his pulse against her tongue as he throbbed in the heat of her mouth. “Fuuuck,” he said again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Be quiet&lt;/em&gt;, she thought. &lt;em&gt;If you keep making so much noise, Flora will hear us!&lt;/em&gt; Her heart pounded in her chest. The idea that someone would catch them was terrifyingly exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, it was too much, and she pulled back, sputtering and trying not to gag. His cock throbbed in her grasp, and she eagerly continued licking, flicking her tongue against the tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shifted again, and she jumped as his hand reached up between her thighs to caress her lips. His touch felt delicious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh wow, you’re so wet,” he whispered, excitedly slipping a finger inside. She gasped in surprise, then wrapped her lips more tightly around him. He pushed deeper, then pulled out, eagerly fingering her in time with her stimulation of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was distractingly good. She bobbed her head as he added another finger, curling inside to reach a spot that made her moan. She spread her legs wider, pushing against his hand and rolling her hips to meet him, even as he started breathing heavily and thrusting upward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stacy,” he breathed. “I’m gonna cum…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned encouragingly and sucked harder. His fingers thrust into her dripping pussy, matching the rhythm of his cock in her mouth. She felt almost delirious, head swimming in pleasure. He was going to cum for her! She wanted it. Needed it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” He grunted, moving his hand from her shoulder to the back of her head, pushing her down as he lifted up. His fingers stopped moving, even as his cock started pulsing and twitching. She swallowed eagerly as he pumped his cum into her mouth. After the first few spurts, he relaxed his grip, and she eased back until just the tip was between her lips, milking the last of his climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he shuddered, and she let him slip out. His taste filled her mouth, potent evidence of how much she aroused him. She swallowed the last of it, feeling a wave of satisfaction roll down her spine until she squeezed around his fingers, still nestled inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” he gasped. “That was…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, it was,” she purred, still gently squeezing the base of his cock. It felt so natural in her hand that it took her a moment to realize he wasn’t getting softer. “Hey, you’re still hard,” she purred happily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he moaned, “That happens sometimes, when it’s been a while.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can go again?” she asked eagerly, stroking him with more enthusiasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” he gasped, straining in her hand, “but be careful, it’s sensitive. I won’t last long.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I won’t either,” she grinned, getting up. His fingers slipped out, and he looked up at her in surprise as she moved to straddle him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, are you sure?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just let you cum in my mouth,” she grinned, “and &lt;em&gt;now&lt;/em&gt; you’re asking if I’m sure?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just mean—ah!” He gasped as she rubbed his head between her lips. “Like, a blowjob is one thing, but…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t you want to feel your stepsister’s &lt;em&gt;tight&lt;/em&gt; little pussy wrapped around your cock?” she teased, slowly lowering herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he groaned, squeezing her thighs. “I mean, yes, but shut up about the stepsister thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe once—ah!—it stops being so funny.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look how—ohhh—wet you are! Looks like I’m not the only one with a step-sibling fetish.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop talking,” she purred, finally taking him all the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned happily as she started rocking in place, grinding her pelvis against him. She leaned forward, bracing her hands on his shoulders, and gasping at the pressure it put on her clit. He reached up and took her breasts in his hands, trapping her nipples between his fingers. Little sparks of electricity danced through her system, and she felt the pressure growing rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You feel so good inside me,” she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned, his entire body rigid beneath her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t cum yet,” she purred. “I’m close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled her hips, leaning into his hands and savoring the way he felt. Little waves of pleasure radiated from her core. She dug her fingernails into his shoulders, rocking in place, letting the sensation build and build…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stacy,” he warned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not yet,” she hissed. Her insides clenched around his cock. His hard shaft throbbed, resisting any efforts to pull him deeper or push him out. She squeezed her thighs around his waist, struggling not to cry out. Her clit thrummed, the pressure growing, ready to explode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ahh!” He suddenly released her breasts, letting her collapse on top of him, and pulled her into an intense kiss. His cock throbbed and twitched, warmth spreading as he came inside her. She moaned around his tongue as his climax triggered hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He held her close as she shook uncontrollably around him. She could feel him everywhere. Her lips met his eagerly. He thrust desperately up into her, sending shockwaves of pleasure through her body. It was all she could do to cling to him as they came together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, she found herself gasping for breath, with her head resting on his shoulder. He shuddered as his cock softened and slipped out. She giggled and rolled onto her back, pushing a hand between her thighs to catch his cum. Her body was relaxed and humming with satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stacy, that was…” He stared at her breathlessly. “That was…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Pretty fucking great?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” He looked worried. “I’m sorry I couldn’t hold off any longer. I tried to warn you…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I just wanted you to wait so I could cum, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, it’s okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I came,” she grinned. “You couldn’t tell?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I mean, yeah, I just… um…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you’re worried about cumming in me?” she laughed. “Relax, I’m on the pill.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” he breathed a sigh of relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, what now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re asking me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You had a stepsister fantasy, and you got to make it real. Did you get it all out of your system? Are you gonna be able to control yourself around me now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he hesitated, weighing his answer carefully. “Yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm.” She poked his chest playfully. “Too bad.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? What are you saying?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, nothing,” she smiled. “I’m gonna go clean myself up and go back to my bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He watched, speechless, as she got dressed. Before opening the door, she paused and looked back at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me know if you change your mind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She blew him a kiss and slipped out.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Stop Moving!: and other erotic short stories</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/stop-moving-ebook/"/>
		<published>2025-01-07T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-01-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/stop-moving-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="hypnosis" />
    <category term="mind control" />
    <category term="nude model" />
    <category term="life drawing" />
    <category term="nurse" />
    <category term="medical" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="coworker" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/stop-moving-ebook-WwD9rZJkbL-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stop Moving!&lt;/em&gt; brings you three steamy short stories from author Ruby Pink about women who know what they want. In “Do You Need Assistance?” a nurse helps a cute patient with his fluid sample so she can make it to girl’s night. “Hypnosis is Ridiculous” is about a woman who is skeptical of her friend’s claim that he can hypnotize her. If only it wasn’t so hot in this room! And in the title story, two life models who find themselves in an awkwardly intimate pose need a solution for a rapidly swelling problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruby Pink loves reading erotica but was frustrated to find so many featuring shallow women with no agency. She took up the pen to bring us steamy shorts about real women who aren’t just props in male fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DSJFC389"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Stacy’s Family 3: Stacy’s Sister</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/3-stacys-sister/"/>
		<published>2025-01-06T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2025-01-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/3-stacys-sister/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="uniform" />
    <category term="schoolgirl" />
    <category term="upskirt" />
    <category term="panties" />
    <category term="teasing" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="facial" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/stacys-sister-O0zqCrlAX_-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Thanks for the ride, Tom,” Flora said as they pulled up in front of Lindsey’s house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No problem,” he nodded. “Picking you up from tutoring is on my way home from work. And Flora, I really wish you would call me Dad.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But you’re not my dad.” She grabbed her bag and opened the passenger door. “You’re my step-dad.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine,” he frowned, annoyed as always, but not taking the bait. “There won’t be any boys at this sleepover, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No boys, like I already told you.” She rolled her eyes. “Just Lindsey and Alexis. We’re gonna watch horror movies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, have a good time. Be home by dinner tomorrow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he drove away, she resisted the urge to flip him off. So controlling! She couldn’t wait to move out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Flora!” Lindsey’s cheerful voice calling from the doorway snapped her out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They hugged and made their way into the kitchen. Alexis waved hello, and standing nearby was Lindsey’s big brother, Casey. He lifted his chin in greeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flora couldn’t help but notice how cute he was. Scruffy stubble and hair just long enough to run your hands through. He was wearing athletic shorts with a ringer tee, and his forearms were covered in tattoos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mom and Dad are visiting Grandma,” Lindsey said, “and won’t be home until tomorrow. They left money for food. I &lt;em&gt;tried&lt;/em&gt; to convince Casey to buy us beer, but he got pizza instead.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s good pizza,” he shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh!” Lindsey huffed. “What good is having an older brother if he won’t hook you up? Why don’t you just move out?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you have any idea how expensive rent is?” he scoffed. “Until my boss brings me on full-time at the shop, I can’t afford it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re the worst.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Eat your pizza,” he laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they stood around eating and chatting, Flora became aware of Casey’s eyes on her. She met his gaze. He looked puzzled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gestured at all of their outfits. Lindsey and Alexis were dressed in casual clothes, but Flora was still in her school uniform: White button-up shirt, plaid skirt, matching tie, and knee socks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why are you wearing a Catholic schoolgirl uniform? Are you in a play or something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because she goes to Catholic school, dumbass,” Lindsey answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” He still looked confused. “I thought you all went to school together?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We did last year,” Flora said, “but I transferred to St. Mary’s for senior year.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That all-girls school? Why?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because she was too big a slut!” Lindsey crowed. Casey looked intrigued.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up!” Flora blushed and swatted Lindsey’s arm. “They have a good art program, and it’ll help me get into university.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good art program, but no guys?” Alexis shook her head. “Hard pass.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re into art?” Casey asked. “That’s cool.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flora smiled, but before she could reply, Lindsey interrupted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re into art?” she repeated in a mocking tone. “Is that how you flirt? Awkward!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wasn’t flirting,” he protested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure,” Lindsey scoffed. “Keep it in your pants. Let’s start the movie.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the living room, Flora settled on the sofa with the girls, while Casey flopped into an oversized beanbag off to one side. Lindsey picked the movie, the latest installment of a long-running series about a charismatic serial killer and the detective trying to nail him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flora was feeling restless, and kept shifting position. Crossing her legs, uncrossing them, tucking them up under her, dropping them back down. Sometimes, after a long day at school without enough physical activity, she had a hard time sitting still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexis and Lindsey were giggling about something when Flora realized she was being watched. She looked at Casey, who quickly glanced away. A few minutes later, it happened again, and just like before, he turned away when she noticed him looking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She suppressed a smile. It wasn’t hard to figure out what was going on. From his spot on the beanbag, she was pretty sure he could see up her skirt. Not that she minded the attention from her friend’s cute older brother. She’d noticed him discreetly checking her out a few times in the past, but nothing this overt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deciding to toy with him a bit, she subtly parted her legs a bit wider in his direction. Watching out of the corner of her eye, she was pleased to see him linger a bit longer the next time he looked. Some guys had a fetish for school uniforms, she knew. If she’d thought Casey was one of them, she wouldn’t have changed before coming over the last few times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heart pounding, she hitched her skirt up a bit higher. She wished she was wearing sexier underwear, but judging by the growing lack of subtlety on his part, it wasn’t a problem. He couldn’t stop peeking, and every time he did, she grew a little more excited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, she’d have to do something soon. So far, the others had no idea, but if he kept being so obvious, they were bound to notice. If Lindsey spotted him, she’d react loudly, and give him no end of grief for creeping on her friends. One thing was certain, he would stop looking, and Flora didn’t want that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next time he turned his head, she was waiting, and caught his eye. He winced guiltily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What is it?” She silently mouthed the question, pretending she didn’t know why he was glancing at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shrugged and directed his attention back to the TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was several minutes before he worked up the nerve to peek again. Once more, she met his gaze, questioning with a bit more insistence. He looked nervous, but before he could turn away, she held up a finger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You, come with me, now,” she mouthed, gesturing at him, then herself, then the hall. He nodded. She walked around the corner, out of sight of the couch, and a moment later, he followed, hands clasped awkwardly in front of himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you think you’re doing?” she hissed, poking him in the chest and trying not to laugh. “Your sister’s going to see you!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” he protested quietly. “I wasn’t doing anything!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dude, you were looking straight up my skirt. Admit it, or I’ll yell for your sister.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened her mouth as if to call Lindsey, and he frantically gestured for her to stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, okay, you’re right! I’m sorry, it just kinda happened.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It just kinda happened? Over and over?” She struggled not to grin. “You can’t keep your eyes off me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I mean, the first time it happened by accident, I swear. I shouldn’t have kept looking. I’m sorry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re such a perv,” she whispered triumphantly. “Why were you looking up my skirt anyway? I thought you had a girlfriend?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We broke up. It’s, um, been a while. When I caught a glimpse of your panties, I got kinda excited.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can see that. You clearly have a boner.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shit!” He frantically tried to conceal the erection tenting his shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, if you can’t keep your eyes to yourself, you should at least learn to be more subtle. It’s a good thing Lindsey didn’t notice, she would’ve flipped out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I know, I’m sorry.” He glanced nervously in the direction of the living room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lucky for you, I don’t mind so much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” His eyes snapped back to her in disbelief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, you’re still a pervert,” she whispered, “but it is kinda hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For real?” He relaxed as she nodded, biting her finger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A loud sting of music sounded from the living room, making Lindsey and Alexis squeal in surprise, then erupt in laughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In that case,” he whispered with growing boldness, “would you let me see them?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let you see? That’s so naughty,” she grinned, fidgeting with her hemline. “But I guess it wouldn’t hurt to give you a peek. Since you want to see them so bad.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she raised her skirt to reveal a simple pair of white and blue striped cotton briefs. Despite their plainness, he stared, eyes wide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe we’re doing this,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His erection twitched eagerly inside his shorts. She felt an answering flutter inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Casey, I think you have a schoolgirl fetish.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I don’t,” he murmured distractedly. “I just think you look hot in your uniform.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Duh, that’s what a schoolgirl fetish is,” she teased, turning around and bending over a bit, so he could look at her butt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shrugged and started squeezing his cock through his shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so hard already,” she purred, “just from seeing my panties?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It turns me on,” he agreed, rubbing his palm along the length of his shaft. “Like catching a glimpse of something secret. Something sexy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turned around to face him again, holding her skirt up with one hand and teasing herself with the other. He watched enthusiastically as she ran a finger along her slit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take out your cock for me,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He glanced nervously in the direction of the living room before tugging down his waistband. His erection popped out, jutting eagerly upward. Through his trimmed pubes, she could see a tattoo, though she couldn’t make out the details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s that tattoo?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” he looked embarrassed. “It, uh, says ‘lucky you.’ I got it on a dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dork,” she laughed, though she had to admit she did feel lucky as he wrapped his hand around his cock and started stroking for her. It had been months since she’d had any action, and he looked pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stared hungrily as she rubbed herself with increasing enthusiasm, and it wasn’t long before he noticed the growing wet spot on her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Looks like I’m not the only one who’s turned on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, if they’re getting wet, it’s your fault,” she exhaled. “Staring at me like that, and getting hard, and touching yourself!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A scream erupted from the living room, followed by Alexis and Lindsey squealing in horrified glee. The sudden noise reminded Flora realized that at any moment, someone could walk out to get a drink, or another slice of pizza, or just to see where she and Casey had disappeared to. She wasn’t sure who Lindsey would be more upset with if she caught them in the act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come with me,” she whispered, grabbing him by the shoulder and pushing him into the bathroom. She closed the door and leaned against it, biting her lip. The room was small, dimly lit by streetlight through a frosted glass window. There was just enough space for him to lean against the sink and her to stand by the door without touching. They would still have to be quiet, but at least they wouldn’t be spotted immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock throbbed eagerly, jutting from his waistband. He waited cautiously, unsure if they were continuing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Keep going,” she breathed, lifting her skirt and spreading her legs for him. “I love watching you touch yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She stared as he lowered his shorts and rubbed his thumb over the ridge of his head. Slowly, firmly, he stroked the full length of his shaft. She joined in, rubbing her underwear between her lips. Her wetness soaked through, coating her fingertips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Will you, uh,” he stammered, “take them off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My panties?” She grinned. “You won’t tell your sister, will you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shook his head firmly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, if you promise not to tell, then I’ll take them off for you.” Slowly, she slipped them down, and held them up so he could see the creamy wetness smeared inside. “Here’s what they look like. Does it turn you on to see how wet I am?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” he whispered, tugging his cock excitedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take them.” She offered. He looked like he couldn’t believe this was happening. “Go ahead,” she encouraged, as he raised them to his face. “Do you like the smell of my wet schoolgirl panties?” Her heart was pounding. She was surprised to find herself so excited by his fetish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wrap those around your cock,” she instructed. He eagerly draped them over his shaft, and started stroking. She stared as his head strained against the fabric. “That’s so hot,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was so aroused by the sight of her panties wrapped around his cock that she found her hand moving between her thighs again. As she slipped a finger between her lips, a shiver rolled down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you wanna know a secret?” she whispered. He nodded. “I lied about why I switched schools. Lindsey was right, I was a total slut. My stepdad caught me giving head to three guys from the basketball team. He totally lost it, and made me switch to an all-girls school.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Casey moaned quietly, watching her shiver at the memory of kneeling before three throbbing cocks. She laughed at the realization that her step-dad’s attempt to remove her from temptation had instead put her in Casey’s path. She felt drunk with the intensity of his desire for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You like these tits, too?” she continued enthusiastically, unbuttoning her top so he could see her bra. “I’ve caught you staring down my shirt a couple times, but you’ve never been so obvious before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock twitched as she scooped a breast from the cup. She tweaked her nipple until it stiffened for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t realize I’d be so into this,” she gasped. “It’s so hot, watching you use my panties.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so sexy,” he groaned. “You look so fucking good in that uniform.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you wanna see my pussy?” Without waiting for him to answer, she leaned against the door, opened her legs wide and spread her lips for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He started pulling on his cock even harder. His head was swollen under the fabric, and his shaft looked rock-hard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached for the sensitive bud of her clit, finding it erect and nearly too sensitive to touch. Indirectly, she rubbed circles around it, gasping at the sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he breathed as a bit of precum squirted out, soaking into her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My clit is tingling,” she purred. Eagerly, she plunged one and then two fingers inside her soaking pussy. She rubbed her clit with one hand and fucked herself with the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stared hungrily, and she wondered if he was imagining shoving her hands out of the way and burying his cock in her heat. The thought made her insides clench repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re being so naughty,” she moaned, feeling the pressure build. “Do you want to watch this schoolgirl cum for you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded enthusiastically, thrusting forcefully into his fist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you’re so hard! It turns me on so much to watch you jerk off with my panties. I’m so wet right now,” she gasped. “I’m so close. I’m about to cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squirmed, rolling her hips against her hands as she watched him masturbate for her. The head of his cock throbbed as he built towards a climax. She imagined kneeling in front of him, opening her mouth…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Oh fuck, I’m gonna cum! I’m gonna cum. I can’t be too loud, your sister will hear! I’m gonna, I’m gonna, oh my god! Oh fuck, I’m cumming! Ahhh! Ohhh!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wave of sensation crashed over her. Her pussy squeezed insistently, and wetness dripped from her fingers. Her clit thrummed. Little sparks of electricity seemed to dance up and down her spine. Her chest heaved as she panted for breath. Overwhelmed, her legs gave out, and she collapsed to her knees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she could focus again, she found herself gazing up at his cock. He was stroking frantically, her panties pulling taut over his tip with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so hard,” she whispered, still rocking through the final waves of her climax. “Oh fuck, that’s so hot. Look how wet my panties are. Do you think they could make you cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want you to cum for me. Will you cum in this slutty schoolgirl’s panties?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” he grunted. “Here I cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His entire body went rigid, and his cock started twitching and throbbing. He continued thrusting into his grip, pumping his spunk into the saturated gusset of her panties. She moaned deliriously at the sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the third stroke, his head popped free of the fabric, and a hot spurt of cum shot onto her cheek. She stifled a cry of surprise, staring up at his eyes full of lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again and again, his cum fell on her face. She opened her mouth, catching some on her tongue before finally wrapping her lips around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Flora!” He groaned in surprise, and put a hand on the back of her head, encouraging her to suck and swallow the last of his orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he shuddered and pulled away, leaning heavily against the edge of the sink and gasping for breath. Her underwear hung wetly from his still-twitching shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She saw him through a pink haze of arousal as she wiped the last of his cum from her chin and licked her fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now?” he asked, removing her panties and tucking his cock back into his shorts. He held up the sloppy mess, soaked with her juices and his spunk, unsure what to do with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a brief, lust-crazed moment, she considered putting them back on, imagining the way his warm, sticky cum would feel on her arousal-swollen lips. Shaking her head, she closed his hand around her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can keep those,” she grinned. “Make sure Lindsey doesn’t find them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” he grinned. “Thanks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, you better slip out of here first, so they don’t notice us leaving at the same time. I need to clean up a bit, anyway.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure,” he whispered, “but, um, I meant, what now, like, between us?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know yet,” she admitted with a smile. “I guess you’ll find out if I’m wearing my uniform next time you see me.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Stacy’s Family 2: Stacy’s Dad</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/2-stacys-dad/"/>
		<published>2024-12-31T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-12-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/2-stacys-dad/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="mature" />
    <category term="older man" />
    <category term="younger woman" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="sixty-nine" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/stacys-dad-Ow3f1YezaP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Bella’s heart pounded as she rang the doorbell at her best friend Stacy’s house. This was it. It was finally going to happen! She’d expected to be nervous, but more than anything, she felt anticipation. As Stacy’s dad approached, she quickly adjusted her skirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He answered the door barefoot, wearing jeans and a concert T-shirt from ten years before she was born. As usual, she was struck by his good looks. He had a strong jaw, peppered with stubble. There was more gray than black in his hair, but he still had broad shoulders and a healthy physique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hi, Mr. Johnson!” She smiled brightly, bouncing on her heels when he opened the door. He clearly struggled not to notice the way it made her boobs move under her shirt. She never wore a bra to Stacy’s house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bella?” He looked confused. “Stacy’s not here. She and Flora are at their mom’s this week.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” She frowned, pretending to be disappointed, despite knowing perfectly well where Stacy was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What happened?” He sighed. “Did she get her dates mixed up again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I guess so.” It was a lie, but a plausible one. Stacy was notorious for double-booking or forgetting about previous plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked sympathetic. Before he could say anything, she kept talking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I tried texting, but she didn’t answer. I figured her phone died again.” Another lie, also believable. Stacy lived life in the red zone of her battery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that tracks.” He looked awkward. “Well, I’m sorry you had to come all this way…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I stay?” She blurted the question too loud and fast, and forced herself to take a breath. “It’s just, my mom’s new boyfriend is over. They were drinking when I left, and I kinda don’t want to be there right now.” This was a carefully calculated request. He’d never said anything, but the few times she’d talked about her mom, she’d gotten the distinct impression he didn’t think much of the way she behaved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He hesitated, and she could almost see his thought process. She &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; spend the night here all the time, practically sleeping here more than at home. But this would be the first time Stacy wasn’t here, and he looked vaguely uncomfortable. He glanced over his shoulder into the living room, where she could see he’d just been sitting down in front of the TV with his dinner. He grimaced, looked back at her, and ran his hand through his hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please?” She bounced again, beaming at him. “I promise I won’t be any trouble. I’ll sleep in Stacy’s room, and I’ll leave in the morning. You’ll barely know I’m here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” he sighed, opening the door for her. “Come on in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yay! Thanks, Mr. Johnson!” He stiffened as she threw her arms around his neck and pressed herself against his firm chest, withdrawing before he could react.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah, don’t worry about it.” He cleared his throat and closed the door behind her. “And please, I’ve told you, call me Rich.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, Rich,” she giggled, skipping up the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey Bella?” He called after her, and she peeked back down the stairwell. “Do you need dinner?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, thanks, I already ate.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, make yourself at home. I’m starting a movie if you get bored.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He turned away, and she forced herself to walk calmly down the hall, past the doors to Flora’s room, the bathroom, and Rich’s room. Stacy’s was at the end of the hall. She let herself in, shut the door, dropped her bag, and collapsed on the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It worked! She pulled a pillow over her face to muffle a squeal, and laughed giddily. She was finally here alone with her best friend’s dad! He had no idea that she’d come here purposely while Stacy was away. Or that she’d been harboring a secret crush on him for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d always thought he was vaguely handsome, but her awareness of him as a man really blossomed one summer night, two years ago. She’d stayed over, and had trouble sleeping in the heat. After dozing fitfully, tossing and turning the whole time, she’d woken up tangled in the sheets, with a head full of fading and confusingly erotic dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After visiting the bathroom, she’d noticed that his door wasn’t closed all the way. A dim light spilled into the hall, and she could barely hear a woman’s voice. Curious, she crept closer, and blushed when she realized the woman’s voice was crying out in pleasure. Peeking through the gap in the doorway, she saw the light was coming from a laptop on the bed playing pornography. Stacy’s dad—Rich, she corrected herself—had kicked all the covers off and was lying on his back, completely nude. He had his hand wrapped around his erect cock, slowly and firmly stroking the full length of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bella’s breath had caught in her throat. She’d fooled around with a few guys at school, without much enthusiasm. They had no chill. Inevitably, they would rush to fondle her boobs, then try to push her head down to their twitching erections. If she let them go all the way, after only a few frantic thrusts, they would pull out and splatter sticky cum across her back or chest or face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By contrast, Rich seemed to be in no hurry. His cock was much thicker than any of the boys from school, glistening slightly in the light from the laptop screen. Every few minutes he would groan, just on the edge of her hearing. His thighs and stomach muscles would tense, and he would lift his hips, as if thrusting into an imaginary woman riding him like a cowgirl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bella had watched in awe, and something awakened inside her. Her chest flushed, and a sudden heat bloomed between her legs. She watched his hand work the length of his shaft and imagined following it with her tongue. Every time he lifted his hips, she shivered, wishing she was sitting on top of him. Quietly, she reached into her shirt to pull on her nipples, hardly daring to breathe for fear he would notice her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After what seemed like a very long time, his cock started pumping thick white spunk. She squeezed her thighs together and stared at it dripping over his fingers. A few minutes later, he closed the laptop and walked into his bathroom to clean up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bella returned to Stacy’s room and fell asleep with a hand down her shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that night, she’d studied him like a scientist discovering a new species. What did he like? How did he spend his time? One evening, while he was making dinner, she worked up the nerve to ever-so-casually ask him why he wasn’t dating anybody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That sounds exhausting!” He laughed. “Dating is a young man’s game. I wasn’t much good at it back when Jo and I were together, and I damn sure don’t have the patience for it now. Plus, I like being able to do my own thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacy teased him, calling him a curmudgeon. They all laughed, but the thought of him puttering around an empty house when his kids weren’t there made her feel sad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She became mildly obsessed. Whenever she stayed over, she was painfully aware of his presence. If they were in the same room, she was distracted. She never saw his door open again, though she regularly got up in the middle of the night to check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she thought about some of the things she’d done, she felt a bit ashamed. If given a chance, she would sneak into his room and go through his laundry basket, inhaling the musky smell of his clothes. She even stole one of his gym shirts. His scent faded, but for a time, it was her most treasured possession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once, when he took Stacy and Flora on vacation, they left her the keys and asked her to bring in the mail. She visited every day, and masturbated in his bed. She fantasized about him coming home and smelling her on the sheets, but on the last day she panicked and washed them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For some time, she’d harbored a fantasy about being alone with him. She’d confess her feelings, and, overcome with desire, he would carry her straight to the bedroom. This daydream constantly filled her idle moments. It was a bad idea for so many reasons. It would never happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what if it did? The more she thought about it, the harder it was to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wasn’t in love or anything like that. No fantasies of marriage. Only a growing certainty that they should sleep together. That he could teach her things boys her age had no clue about. That she could rekindle something inside him. One magic night to soothe the sadness she was convinced he was hiding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After her eighteenth birthday, she resolved to &lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; it happen. He had grown to epic stature in her mind, the platonic ideal of a man. She yearned for him. Soon, she’d be heading off to college, starting the next chapter of her life. But she couldn’t move on without experiencing this. Experiencing him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now she was here, lying on Stacy’s bed, finally alone in the house with him! She bit her lip with excitement. All she had to do was get him to stop thinking of her as his daughter’s friend, and start thinking of her as a woman. Soft, warm, and eager for his touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, she peeled off her clothes and changed into a pair of sleep shorts and a lace-topped cami. Inspecting her reflection in the mirror, she tried to imagine how she would look through his eyes. Still too young. She undid her ponytail. Better. She rubbed her thumbs over her nipples until they stiffened, protruding through the thin fabric. Perfect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearly bursting with excitement, she made herself walk slowly down the stairs. Rich looked up as she wandered into the living room. She kept her attention on her phone, carefully not looking to see if his eyes were on her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatcha watching?” She forced her voice to sound casual, even a bit bored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A vampire movie from the 90s. It’s just getting started if you want to watch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, okay.” She dropped onto the couch, across from him. For several minutes, she scrolled her socials. If she acted too eager, he’d suspect something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He finished his food, set his plate aside, and leaned back with a beer in his hand. She studied his body language from the corner of her eye. With his feet up on the coffee table, he looked relaxed, but she could sense his secret tension. Her presence without the usual intermediary of Stacy had left him unsettled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good. She flipped her hair back over her shoulder and set her phone aside. He sipped his beer. To all outward appearances, he was focused on the movie, but she could &lt;em&gt;feel&lt;/em&gt; his attention on her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, like, what’s her deal?” She gestured at the main character, giving him a chance to break the ice a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s the reincarnation of the vampire’s wife, who died tragically hundreds of years ago.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She nodded, and pretended to pay attention. Slowly, she shifted from sitting up to leaning on the arm of the couch, with her legs tucked up beside her. After a bit, she made a show of yawning. Languidly, she stretched, reaching her legs out and “accidentally” touching him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oops, sorry,” she giggled, pulling her legs back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry about it,” he said stiffly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although her heart was pounding, she forced herself to wait patiently. Every time she moved, he glanced at her. She crossed her legs, and his eyes flicked in her direction. Uncrossed them a minute later, and he looked again. Time to escalate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She lay on her side, legs pulled up, head resting on the arm of the couch. She felt his gaze follow the curve of her ass, and quickly look away. It was working!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the TV, the main character stirred in her sleep, as if aware of the vampire’s attention. Her restless movement tugged the thin sheet down, exposing the plunging neckline of her nightgown. She was clearly having erotic dreams, and the vampire struggled to control himself as she panted and arched her back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With deliberate carelessness, Bella draped a leg over the back of the couch. He glanced her way, stiffened in surprise, and fixed his gaze on the TV. She bit her lip to keep from reacting. Her sleep shorts were a bit loose, and she wasn’t wearing any panties. With her legs spread like this, she’d just given him a glimpse of her bare pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She risked a quick look in his direction. He had a white-knuckled grip on the beer bottle, reminding her of the way he held his cock that night. A surge of excitement flooded her system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several times over the next few minutes, he sneaked another peek, each time lingering just a little longer. She wished she could get away with reaching down to spread her lips for him, but that would be too much. If she pushed him too fast, he’d overreact and put a stop to things. At this point, everything she did had to remain deniable. Carelessly sultry, not seductive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he shifted his weight in a way that told her he was about to do something. Her heart pounded. What would he do? Was he going to adjust his position to get a better look at her? Maybe he needed to adjust his rapidly swelling cock? Or perhaps he couldn’t handle the temptation anymore and was about to lose control and climb on top of her? She shivered with anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You, er, seem cold, Bella.” He set aside his beer, grabbed a blanket, and draped it over her legs, being careful not to actually touch her. A cold wave of disappointment crashed over her as he sat back down and fixed his attention on the TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had she been imagining his lingering gaze? Perhaps he didn’t even see anything. Or he did, but he couldn’t stop seeing her as a young girl, awkwardly crashing his movie night. She felt foolish. This was a dumb idea. Why did she think this would work?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He’s a grown man, she reminded herself. No doubt he’s been with plenty of women. He wouldn’t be seduced by a simple glimpse of pussy. She’d behaved like a cat in heat and expected him to fall over with lust. Her cheeks burned. She wanted to run back to Stacy’s bed, cry herself to sleep, and sneak out in the morning before he woke up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was about to leave when she noticed him casually grab a pillow and put it on his lap. His movement was calm, relaxed even. But there was a noticeable tension in his posture. Almost as if he were trying to keep her from noticing something. The more she looked, the more convinced she became that if she reached under that pillow, she’d wrap her hand around a throbbing erection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh! He didn’t cover her up because she was an awkward girl, he’d done it because she was having an effect on him. A primal, undeniable response to the sight of her body. She imagined swatting the pillow aside, climbing onto his lap, and rubbing against the bulge in his jeans. The plan was working! She had to keep going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, I am a little cold,” she said, sitting up and scooting closer to him. “Thanks, Rich.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, um, sure,” he stammered as she leaned against him, resting her head on his shoulder. “No problem.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was so excited, it was difficult to control her breathing. Rich was noticeably tense. She could practically feel his heartbeat pounding. He kept one hand pressed onto the pillow in his lap, carefully holding it in place. She wondered if the pressure from the pillow was making it harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the movie, the main character had finally given into the vampire’s sensual advances. She walked into the moonlit garden, wearing only a thin nightgown. His lips met her neck, and she gasped in shock. Her bosom heaved as he eagerly sucked. When he finally released her, she moaned, with blood trickling from two perfect puncture wounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich shifted awkwardly, reaching under the pillow to adjust himself. Bella did the same, pulling the blanket up so he couldn’t see her sliding a hand into her shorts. She traced her fingers over her lips, sending a wave of sensation through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry,” Rich mumbled, “I don’t remember this being quite so… explicit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay,” Bella purred, “I don’t mind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They watched as the vampire mounted the young woman. He appeared bestial, snarling and growling as he rutted between her thighs. She moaned and writhed below him. It was astonishingly explicit. Had this really come out in theaters?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unconsciously, Rich was pushing the pillow into his lap. Bella stared, imagining his cock straining against the soft padding. His eyes were locked on the screen, but she could tell he was alert to her every movement. She squirmed, rubbing the palm of her hand over her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt his legs tense as he tried to resist thrusting into the pillow. Was he imagining the soft pressure was her ass? She stifled a gasp at the thought of him pulling her urgently into his lap and grinding against her. His breathing was becoming labored. His arm was stiff and unmoving as she leaned into him, inhaling his scent with her head on his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The woman in the movie cried out with pleasure, and Bella released a soft moan. Her insides clenched, and without really intending to, she parted her lips, allowing her middle finger to slip between. She was already slick with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My god, was this really happening? She shivered as she slowly pushed inward. Rich was practically vibrating with tension. Did he know she was touching herself? Was his cock throbbing painfully because she was so close?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vampire’s back arched as he thrust one final time into the young woman writhing beneath him. He shouted triumphantly at the moon, and fell upon her, burying his face in her neck. She cried out as he fed on her again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bella squeezed her thighs around her hand, struggling to control herself. It was all she could do not to throw the stupid pillow away and drop her head onto his lap. She imagined the sound he would make when she wrapped her lips around his cock. He would groan and throb on her tongue as she took him as deep as she could.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She struggled to slow her breathing, as the heat grew inside her. As discreetly as she could, she rocked her hips, thrusting against her palm and letting her finger curl deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the movie had moved on from the explicit scene, Rich’s tension seemed to be growing. Some characters she didn’t recognize were having an intense conversation, but she couldn’t follow it. She &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; he was hard, and it was becoming difficult to restrain herself. Was he also struggling for control? Did he know she was masturbating next to him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She imagined him jumping to his feet and tearing the blanket away. She would be completely exposed. He’d see her hand moving urgently inside her shorts. See her nipples poking through her top, tightly contracted and eager for his touch. Recognize the lust in her eyes, the undeniable hunger she felt for him. How would he react?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As badly as she wanted to find out, she realized she needed to stop. Letting him notice she was aroused during a sex scene in the movie was fine, but losing control wasn’t the plan. She intended to tease him all evening and see how he responded. Slowly work up to some perfect moment when she would confess her feelings, and he could admit he felt the same desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With great difficulty, she forced herself to sit up. Her breathing was shaky as she withdrew her finger, trying not to shiver. She licked her lips and blankly stared at the screen, trying to calm herself down and take things slowly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before she could decide her next move, Rich abruptly stood up, still holding the pillow, and faked an awkward stretch with one arm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, I’m really tired, and I’ve seen this movie before, so I’m gonna head to bed, but you go ahead and finish watching it, good night Bella,” he said all in a rush.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She watched as he awkwardly moved up the stairs, taking the pillow with him. A conflicting set of emotions struggled in her mind. On the one hand, triumph! He was clearly overwhelming aroused and fleeing the scene before he did something he thought he shouldn’t. She’d done that to him!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, dismay. What could she do now? If she followed him to his room, he’d panic. How could she let him know it was okay to act on his desire? Could she somehow draw him back out? Maybe she should take a shower, and leave the door open? Would he peek? No, he wasn’t some horny teenage boy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frustrated, and distractingly aroused, she turned off the TV and went upstairs. Rich’s door was closed. She crept closer, hoping to hear something that might indicate he secretly wanted her to follow, but it was silent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Annoyed, she returned to Stacy’s room and flopped on the bed. She was crackling with sexual energy. For a moment, she considered masturbating, but knew it would be disappointing. She didn’t want to touch &lt;em&gt;herself&lt;/em&gt;, she wanted to touch Rich! She longed to walk in on him stroking his cock like before. To watch the expression on his face as she straddled him. To feel his girth fill her, until she came on top of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She jumped as a sudden clap of thunder shook the house and rain splattered against the window. A summer thunderstorm, relieving pent-up energy in the atmosphere. It must feel good, she sighed, to be able to release tension like that. She wondered if Rich was lying in his bed, just as frustrated as her, resisting the urge to masturbate to his daughter’s best friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thunder boomed and rumbled overhead, as brief flashes of lightning illuminated the room. She huddled under Stacy’s blanket, feeling miserable. She’d always hated storms. As a child, she’d been terrified of thunder, and would run crying to her mom’s bed. It was the only place that felt safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the idea came, it felt too silly to act on. There was no way it would work. The whole point of coming here was to get Rich to see her as a woman, with womanly needs. If she went and told him she was afraid of the thunder, she’d be leaning into his perception of her as a child. He’d never fuck her after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ridiculous. But the more she thought about it, the harder it was to ignore. How else was she going to get past his closed door? Clearly, her attempts on the couch had failed. Whether too subtle or too overt, he’d been unable to move past thinking of her as a girl. Why not use it to her advantage? Once she was in his bed, anything could happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, before she could second-guess herself, she walked to his door. After the next peal of thunder, she knocked timidly on his door. Then, a moment later, knocked a bit more insistently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rich?” She asked, allowing her voice to shake a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bella?” He sounded confused. He walked to the door, opening it a crack. In the dim light, she could see he was only wearing a pair of boxers, and no shirt. “What’s going on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um, I was just wondering if—Ah!” She squealed as another crack of thunder sounded. “I’m sorry, it’s just, I get really freaked out by thunder!” She let her eyes tear up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” he said, trying to keep his pelvis behind the door as he opened it a bit wider, clearly unsure how to respond. “Um, how can I…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know it’s dumb, but can I sleep in here with you? I hate being alone during a storm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, I don’t know if that’s…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before he could finish, with the next rumble of thunder, she stepped forward and buried her face in his shoulder. He jumped, but instinctively wrapped his arms around her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” she whispered, feeling his erection twitch against her hip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um.” He hesitated, but she already knew he wouldn’t say no. “I guess so.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thanks, Rich,” she said, holding the embrace just a moment longer than necessary, before pulling away and quickly climbing under his blankets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He ran his hand through his hair, exhaled heavily, and got into bed beside her. He lay stiffly on his back, staring at the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She faced away from him, mostly so he couldn’t see the excitement in her eyes. Despite there being plenty of room, she scooted close. Not touching, but so near that she imagined she could feel the heat from his skin on hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was it! She was finally here, in bed with him. Her heart pounded with anticipation. He was still hard. She was lying next to the man she’d fantasized about so many times, and he was hard for her!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But he wasn’t moving. In fact, he seemed unnaturally still. Despite his arousal, he was afraid to move, afraid to touch her. How could she show him that she was here for him? That he didn’t need to be afraid? That she was soft and warm and so, so ready for him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wanted so badly to roll over and find him calmly and slowly stroking his cock again. It was all she’d ever wanted. But he would never do that, she knew. He would never take advantage of her. It was sweet, and safe, and part of the reason she adored him, but part of her wished he would do it anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just the idea sent a thrill down her back. She squeezed her breast, and tried not to moan as she imagined it was his large hand on her chest. Slowly, slowly, she slid her palm down her stomach, picturing his body behind hers, his chest pressed against her back as he reached under her waistband.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her breath caught as she touched herself the way she imagined he would, tentatively, but with increasing firmness as she leaned into it. She wanted badly to spread her legs, to let him go further and feel the heat, the wetness waiting for him. A shiver rolled down her spine, so intense she wondered if he could feel it through the mattress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She imagined him rolling her over and laying her head on his chest, to stare in awe as he stroked himself for her. She wanted to wrap her hand around the base, feeling his heartbeat in her grasp. He would make that quiet groan again, and lift his hips, thrusting into the air, desperate for her touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She exhaled softly, and brought her fingers to her mouth. Imagining it was him, she touched her tongue to her fingertips, tentatively exploring. In her mind, he moaned as she kissed the tip, flicking her tongue against the slit. Slowly, she pushed two fingers over her tongue, wishing it was him. She took him deeper, shivering at the thought of him filling her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bella, are you okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” she swallowed, quickly pulling her fingers from her mouth. “Yeah!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s just,” he said softly. “I thought I heard you crying.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” she breathed guiltily. “I’m not.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good, good,” he said hesitantly. Now that he knew she wasn’t crying, would he wonder about the wet sounds he’d heard?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re sweet, Rich.” Quickly, she rolled over to face him. In the dim light, his eyes met hers. Could he see the arousal there? She placed a hand on his shoulder, surprised by her own boldness. “Thank you for taking care of me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course,” he murmured, still unsure of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thunder rolled again, louder than ever. She startled involuntarily, and seeing something encouraging in his eyes, moved closer. She laid her head on his shoulder, and draped her arm across his bare chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He didn’t stop her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, they listened to the sound of heavy rain on the roof. He breathed deeply, slowly, and stared up at the ceiling. She could feel his heart pounding. He was hot to the touch. His arm was stuck awkwardly between them, and she could feel his hand under her hip. She inhaled his scent, dizzy with his closeness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her body was alive, every nerve ending screaming its awareness of his body. She felt his chest hair under her arm, and his stubble against her forehead. Her nipples were so tight, she was sure he could feel them poking his arm. His chest rose and fell with each steady breath. The heat between her thighs grew with each passing second.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, agonizingly slowly, she ran her hand down his torso. With every inch, he grew more tense. She held her breath, the spark of arousal now a blazing fire in her core. She wanted him. Craved him with every fiber of her being. There was no going back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bella,” he gasped as she approached his waist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rich,” she echoed, reaching lower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We can’t…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We can,” she purred, teasing her fingers over his straining shaft. “We really can.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god!” He exhaled shakily as she pressed more firmly. “But… You’re…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A grown woman,” she answered, nuzzling his neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, I’m…” His cock throbbed under her hand, despite his protestations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A man I’ve wanted for a long time,” she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That—oh!—doesn’t make it better!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This will,” she said, reaching into his boxers and wrapping her hand around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” he groaned, as she started stroking his cock the way she’d watched him do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She kissed his neck as he lifted his hips to thrust into her grasp. He took the hint, and finally rolled onto his side to face her, meeting her mouth with hunger. She wrapped both hands around his shaft, squeezing and pulling as he moved with her. His tongue darted into her mouth, and she gasped as he sucked on her bottom lip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He reached one arm under her head, wrapped around her shoulder, pulling her closer. His other hand roughly grasped her chest, palm covering her nipple, which sent sparks of electricity shooting through her system. She moaned happily in his grasp, still amazed by the feel of his thick cock in her hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take off your boxers,” she gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, he obeyed, rolling onto his back and peeling them off. He stared with naked lust as she removed her clothes. His cock twitched eagerly, but before she could lower her head to taste him, he grabbed her and pulled her chest to his face. She moaned, and braced herself on the headboard as he wrapped his lips around her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His tongue lashed in tight circles, and she cried out at the nearly overwhelming sensation. He pulled more and more of her breast into the heat of his mouth, and she felt a clenching in her core. She moaned and ran her fingers through his hair. Just when it was becoming too much, he switched to the other side, cupping the abandoned breast in the palm of his hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rich,” she moaned, “I want to taste you…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to taste you too,” he growled. Before she could say anything, he spun her around until she was lying on top of him, with his head between her thighs and her face over his cock. It throbbed and strained, reaching for her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A bit of creamy precum was already leaking out, and she eagerly licked it up, savoring the strongly masculine taste. She barely had time to part her lips around his head before she felt him begin exploring her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His hands grabbed her ass, spreading her open in a way that felt shocking. She moaned around his cock as his lips met hers, and his tongue began excitedly tracing her folds. He licked up and down the length of her, parting her and pushing inside. She squirmed, bucking her hips, but he held her firmly in place, fingers digging into her cheeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tried to focus on him, one hand braced on the mattress, and the other wrapped firmly around the base of his cock. He twitched against her tongue, and she swirled around his head, amazed at how excited she was to go down on him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But a moment later, he reached deeper with his tongue, making her moan in surprise. His cock popped out of her mouth, slapping wetly against her cheek. She could only pant in astonishment as he licked and sucked and kissed her. When his tongue flicked her clit, she cried out, and desperately pulled his cock back in her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and lifted his hips to meet her. She gagged, pulled back, and tried to do it again. He pushed his tongue further, spreading her open, licking deeper and deeper. She felt his cock against the back of her throat, and tried to let him in, but he was too big.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choking, she pulled him out, and lay her head on his hip, gasping as he sucked hard on her clit, his tongue moving in tiny circles. His hands held her locked in place, grinding her against his face. She felt a growing pressure and cried his name, which seemed to only encourage him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distractedly, she stroked his cock, licking the base and moaning with each pass of his tongue. He twitched and throbbed in her grasp, but never relented in his enthusiastic devouring of her pussy. Deep inside, a rhythmic contraction began, radiating outward, clenching again and again around his tongue, until she cried out with an astonishing flood of relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She went limp, releasing every muscle that she hadn’t realized she’d been tensing. Waves of pleasure washed over her, and he held her tightly through it, until she rolled onto her back, shivering with release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Oh, wow. Oh, Rich!” she panted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She raised her head, and saw with a rush that he was urgently stroking his cock. His face was glistening with her wetness, and he stared at her with naked hunger in his eyes. Unlike the calm, firm strokes she’d seen him use before, he was now fucking his hand. Slick with her saliva, he lifted his hips with each stroke, staring at her, clearly imagining that he was burying himself in her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I get on top of you?” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yes,” he said, straining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shakily, she got to her knees and moved to straddle him. Their eyes locked as she wrapped her hand around him and positioned him at her entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ohhh shit,” she breathed as she slowly lowered herself onto him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He grunted, trying to let her go at her own pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rich, you’re so big,” she moaned in astonishment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He squeezed her thighs, unable to speak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” When she finally took him all the way, she paused, hand on her belly, savoring the way he filled her. “Oh wow.” He twitched inside, triggering a cascade of sensations. “Oh wow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she started to lift herself up, then let herself drop. It was nearly overwhelming. Her clit felt like it was being rubbed from the inside. She ran her hands restlessly up and down her body, gasping in wonder. Gradually, she increased the pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich stared at her in awe as she bounced. He reached for her breasts, and she fell forward onto his hands, grabbing the headboard and rolling her hips against him. He trapped her nipples between his fingers and grunted as he started lifting his hips to meet her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each time he thrust into her, she cried out. All this time, she’d wanted this. From the first time she saw him touching himself, she’d imagined being the woman he was thrusting up into. Now it was happening, and her body was singing. It felt like they were made for each other, his cock perfectly crafted to fill her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rich,” she gasped, feeling the pressure building again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bella,” he groaned. “I’m gonna cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yes! Do it!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where?” he said through strained teeth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Inside!” Her pussy clenched.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I?” He hesitated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, it’s safe,” she gasped, then moaned as his cock immediately started throbbing. “Oh!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His body went rigid below her, and she felt a rhythmic pulsing deep inside. She moaned and laid her head on his chest, savoring the sensation she’d dreamed about for so long. Her insides fluttered, squeezing his girth as a warm feeling radiated through her entire body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he could breathe again, he wrapped his arms around her and pulled her into a warm kiss. They held each other like that until he softened and slipped out. She rolled onto her back, giggling at the sensation of his cum spilling from her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she returned from the bathroom, and snuggled up against him, he pulled the blankets up. The storm had passed on, and the room was bathed in silver moonlight. She sighed happily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bella, are you really scared of thunder?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I used to be,” she nodded. “When I was a little kid.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heh.” He chuckled. “You played me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry.” She shrugged and gave him a quick kiss on the cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And did you really, um…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have a crush on you? Yeah, that part was true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm.” He seemed thoughtful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry, I’m not in love with you or anything. I’m off to college soon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” He managed to avoid sounding relieved, which she was grateful for. “So, this was a one-time thing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t have any plans beyond tonight, if that’s what you’re asking.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not sure what I’m asking,” he laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, you are,” she teased. “You’re wondering if I’m going to come back and fuck you again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, yes,” he grinned. “I just couldn’t think of a tactful way to ask. Now, mind, I’m grateful for tonight, and if you’ve satisfied your curiosity about older men, that’s fair. But, you know, if you wanted to stop by again before you leave town…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she smiled. “I guess you’ll have to watch the weather report.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Stacy’s Family 1: Stacy’s Mom</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/1-stacys-mom/"/>
		<published>2024-12-18T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-12-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/series/stacys-family/1-stacys-mom/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="milf" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="handyman" />
    <category term="wife" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="missionary" />
    <category term="cum on tits" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/stacys-mom-ejaogd4VCh-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Jo moaned as she held the rumbling head of the vibrator to her clit. It was a hot afternoon, and she was lying on her back in the bedroom with her legs spread wide. Sunshine streamed in the open windows, along with a gentle breeze that danced over her bare skin. She could smell fresh-cut grass, the lingering scent of her body wash, and her arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her husband Tom was away on business again. Her girls Stacy and Flora were at their dad’s, and Tom’s son Hudson was on a camping trip with friends. So, she found herself home alone for a week, bored, and so horny she wanted to scream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The magic wand buzzed continuously, sending intense waves of pleasure radiating through her core. She arched her back and cried out in pleasure, hoping Chad could hear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The young handyman had arrived this morning, toolbox in hand, wearing basketball shorts and a threadbare t-shirt with a faded band logo. She met him at the door in yoga pants and a sports bra. As she walked him through the house, pointing out things that needed doing, his eyes explored her body with a lack of subtlety she would have found shocking if it wasn’t exactly what she’d been hoping for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he wasn’t looking, she tweaked her nipples, ensuring they stood proud for him. She’d noted the outline of his package when he reached up to grab something for her, and tried to return the favor, bending over longer than necessary while showing him a squeaky spot on the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the backyard, she’d watched approvingly as he peeled off his shirt to work on the broken patio umbrella. He didn’t seem to mind the attention. At one point, he caught her looking, flipped the sun-bleached hair out of his eyes, and gave her a wink that left her thinking scandalous thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chad came recommended by another mom on the block, and now she could see why. No doubt he earned quite a bit in tips from lonely housewives all over town. She hoped he was interested in more than just the tip today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she rocked her hips repeatedly, thrusting against the vibrator, she resisted the urge to check if he was watching. When she last saw him, he’d been fixing the leaky faucet in the kitchen. She’d told him she was going to take a quick shower, then “carelessly” left the bedroom door cracked open. Was he out there right now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned again, louder this time. It made her feel a bit ridiculous, but she reminded herself that guys his age watched a lot of porn. They were used to a more exaggerated and vocal performance than her generation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She strained her ears for any indication he was watching. Silence. It was probably a good sign that she couldn’t hear him working anymore, but if he was out there, he was staying very quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” she groaned, “I’m so wet!” That, at least, wasn’t an exaggeration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was frustrating. She’d imagined with a guy his age, it would be like ringing a dinner bell, that he would hear her siren call and come running. She hadn’t even considered he might have enough self-control to watch. Time to kick it up a notch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, Chad!” She squirmed, clawing at the sheet. “It feels so good when you lick my clit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A sudden noise from the hallway. Bingo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She risked a quick glance. Chad was just visible peeking through the gap in the doorway, eyes wide. Something about his posture made it clear he was touching himself. A triumphant wave of lust crashed over her, and she moaned again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then she sat up abruptly, pretending to notice him. He startled and ducked out of sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, Chad?” She scrambled to cover her breasts with her arms, not doing a very good job. In the process, she knocked the magic wand off the bed. It landed on the floor with a noisy clatter and continued to vibrate angrily as she reached to switch it off. “What are you doing out there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shit!” She heard him curse as he pulled up his shorts, realizing he’d been caught. He opened the door, covering his eyes as if he hadn’t already seen everything. “Sorry! I’m sorry!” He winced. “I didn’t mean to spy on you. I just heard a noise, and was worried you were, like, hurt or something.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tried not to smile at the outline of his twitching cock, barely contained by the thin fabric of his shorts, straining to be released. She put on her best “shocked, but also a little flattered” expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that, um…” She pointed at his erection. “Is that because of me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, yeah,” he said with a sheepish grin, lowering his hand from his eyes. “After I saw you weren’t, like, in trouble or whatever, I kinda, um, watched you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh. Oh! Oh no! How long were you watching? Did you hear…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he admitted. “I heard you say my name. Like, I was already turned on, but that’s when I started jerking off. I know I shouldn’t have, but you’re &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You think I’m hot?” She allowed herself to smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, yeah!” His confidence grew as he realized he wasn’t in trouble. “You’re a smoke show.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, you know what I was fantasizing about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“About me goin’ down on you.” He grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And how do you feel about that?” She sat up straighter, uncovering her breasts, and raising a curious eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, I do love eatin’ pussy.” He hooked a thumb in his waistband, considering. “But, aren’t you married and stuff?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes.” She bit her lip. “But Tom’s not here to attend to my needs right now. You are. And judging by that throbbing in your shorts, you’ve got some needs as well. Maybe we could help each other?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You won’t tell him?” He looked excited, but still worried.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think this can stay our little secret.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool.” He grinned. “Cool.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He pulled his shirt over his head with one easy motion. She opened her legs, beckoning him to come closer. He lay on his stomach and lowered his face between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped when she felt his hot breath on her skin, and moaned as he plunged his tongue between her lips. He licked the length of her, eagerly spreading her open with his fingers. Wasting no time, he found a rhythm, pushing inside, then dragging up to circle her clit, and back down again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” She let out a shuddering breath she hadn’t realized she’d been holding. It had been too long since someone had properly eaten her out. Richard, her first husband, had been good at it, but Tom was uninterested. Until this moment, she hadn’t realized how much she missed it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was certainly enthusiastic, working his face back and forth with his tongue buried astonishingly deep, nose rubbing her clit. The magic wand had gotten her nicely warmed up, leaving her pleasantly sensitive as he lapped up the wetness that flowed from her like a spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Chad, lick my clit,” she groaned, echoing what she’d cried out before. He said something unintelligible as she grabbed his hair, pulling him upward until his lips found the spot. He flicked his tongue, making her jump, then settled into a steady routine of kissing, sucking, and licking tight little circles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, who taught you that?” She purred, arching her back and tightening her grip on his hair to hold him firmly in place. A warm glow was spreading through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I need your fingers,” she moaned. His weight shifted, and she shuddered as thick fingers filled her. He curled them repeatedly, rocking in and out of her. Her clit thrummed on his tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Like that! Yes! Keep going!” She felt the pressure mounting, and knew the first orgasm would crackle through her like lightning, leaving her ready for more. “You’re making me cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He closed his lips around her clit and sucked. She screamed and squeezed her thighs around his head. He moved with her bucking hips, riding the waves that rolled through her body, until she finally released him. When he pulled out, she covered her sensitive clit with her palm, rocking in place with the aftershocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stood up, wiping his chin on his arm and looking quite pleased with himself. Eagerly, he pulled down his shorts, revealing an impressive cock, already standing at attention. She expected him to climb on top of her, but he walked around the side of the bed to kneel by her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Before I fuck you,” he grinned, “wanna suck on this cock?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She was shocked by how easily he asked for what he wanted. Another generational difference, she thought. He waited patiently, stroking himself just over her face, not quite touching her. She licked her lips as a glistening bead of precum appeared, surprised to realize she wanted to taste it. “Yes,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He smiled and touched himself to her lips. Tentatively, she licked the tip, then traced around the ridge of his head. He braced himself on the headboard to more easily lean over her as she opened her mouth for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He rocked his hips forward, groaning as his swollen head passed her lips. She rolled onto her side to improve the angle, and reached up to wrap a hand around the base of his shaft. He throbbed as she enthusiastically sucked, exploring his masculine flavor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, your mouth is so hot,” he exclaimed, looking down as he pushed deeper. She tried to relax, sensing his eagerness. He bumped against the back of her mouth, pulled back a moment, then pushed in again. She swallowed and squeezed his root, feeling his heartbeat in her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A moment of resistance, as she shifted her head, and he suddenly slipped into her throat. She struggled not to choke as he started thrusting. He twitched against her tongue, and cried out, grabbing the back of her head and pulling her forward so he could fuck her throat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She swallowed repeatedly to avoid gagging as he finally buried himself to the hilt. He moaned, and his cock throbbed as he held her in place. She groaned and squirmed, eyes watering, squeezing her legs together as her insides clenched.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she had to smack his leg until he released her. She choked as he pulled out. For a moment, a long, thick strand of saliva connected his tip to her lips, until she wiped it away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus,” she sputtered. “You really wanted my throat, huh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That felt incredible,” he groaned, still stroking his cock directly over her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me,” she coughed, rolling onto her back and squeezing her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, I couldn’t help myself,” he shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I mean come here and fuck me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He laughed, and climbed between her legs, rubbing the head of his cock between her lips. She pulled him on top of her, wrapping her legs around to lock her heels behind his ass. They both gasped in surprise as he slipped effortlessly inside. Her pussy clenched excitedly, suddenly full. His weight felt delicious against her clit, and she rolled her hips as he rocked into her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They moved easily together. He thrust with increasing urgency, gasping in her ear. She welcomed him, using her legs to pull him back every time he withdrew. He filled her perfectly, stretching her open, stimulating her with his entire length. She hooked her hands over his shoulders, and buried her face in his neck, letting his smell fill her nostrils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her body pulsed with nearly overwhelming sensation. Behind her closed eyes, she saw flares of color with each thrust, like a private fireworks show. He was grunting now, straining with effort as he moved eagerly inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, he pulled back, lifting himself up on his elbows to look at her as they fucked. His expression was awe-struck. She stared back, astonished by his attention. She shivered and clenched around him. He moaned loudly and started fucking her harder and faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her legs came unhooked, and her tits bounced with every thrust. She squealed and grabbed them, trapping her nipples between her fingers. The pressure was rapidly building. Her toes curled, gripping the sheet, as her core clenched tightly, desperately trying to hold him inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” He groaned, hair plastered to his forehead with sweat. “You just got so tight!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” She cried, “You’re making me cum again!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her vision blurred into a haze as he continued to fuck her through the orgasm. Every time his pelvis crushed her, it made her clit tingle. Her nipples seemed to sing as she pulled them, and a warm heat spread as she gushed around his cock. For a few minutes, it was all she could do not to pass out from the overwhelming crush of sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You feel so good,” he blurted. “I’m getting close!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Head swimming, still awash with pleasure, she considered letting him cum inside. She wanted to feel him bury himself deeply, holding there, flooding her until he collapsed, spent, on top of her. She would savor his weight, and the spreading warmth inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But that’s what Tom always did. He never asked, he just claimed her for his own. She loved it, but she wanted something different with Chad. She remembered the way he’d confidently asked her to go down on him. Could she do the same? Could she just &lt;em&gt;ask&lt;/em&gt; for what she wanted?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; she want? She wasn’t sure, only that she wanted him to do something her husband didn’t. Something to set this encounter apart. Thrillingly different from the ordinary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should she tell him to get behind her? She imagined him squeezing her hips so hard he left marks. Maybe pull her hair? Or slap her ass, hard, just before he pulled out and came all over her back? No, that was tempting, but she wouldn’t be able to see him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he groaned. “I’m gonna cum so hard!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was it! She wanted to watch him cum. Wanted him to fuck her until he couldn’t take it anymore, then pull out and cum for her. Cum &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; her. She wanted to see the expression on his face as he painted her. See the way his cock twitched, feel his hot cum on…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My tits,” she gasped eagerly. “Will you cum on my tits?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He quickly pulled out and got to his knees, wrapping his hand around his cock. He thrust wetly into his fist, the head emerging from his grip, pointed directly at her chest, already leaking creamy precum over his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She watched eagerly as he fucked his hand, leaning forward so far she worried he’d fall over. His cock throbbed and twitched in his grasp. He stared hungrily at her tits, nipples tightly pebbled, awaiting his cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He cried out as the first spurt erupted, shooting over her chest to splatter hotly against her collarbone. She shuddered, clit singing below her fingers, as thick ropes of cum fell on her skin. There was an astonishing amount, covering her chest until it collected in the valley between her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last shot landed on her belly, then he collapsed on the bed next to her, panting with exertion. She found herself humming quietly, idly tracing her fingers through his cum. He watched breathlessly as she rubbed it into her breasts, as if she were moisturizing. The comparison made her laugh, and he joined in, giddy with endorphins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A pleasant breeze rolled through the window, cooling her wet skin. Probably, she should get in the shower before his spunk started drying. But her body was still buzzing with arousal, and she knew she wasn’t done yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chad loped into the bathroom to clean up. She reached for the magic wand again. By the time he came back, the powerful vibrations had her well on the way to another orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She considered how he must see her. The sexy older woman he’d caught masturbating. Who’d invited him in for a fuck, and let him shoot his load all over her chest. Who was still masturbating, writhing on the bed, covered in his cum. For a moment, she saw herself through his eyes, and felt a rush of confidence and arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What did he think would happen next? Was he expecting her to say the money was on the counter, and to see himself out? Perhaps he thought she was a lonely housewife, desperate for company, who would invite him to stay for dinner. Or maybe he just wanted to go for round two. She considered what she wanted from him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Chad,” she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” He sounded hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How quickly do you think you can finish the rest of the list I gave you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” Clearly disappointed, and prepared to be dismissed, he shrugged. “Um, probably, like, twenty minutes?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” she purred. “If you can get back here before I switch this off, I’ll let you fuck me again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sweet!” He ran out the door, still pulling his shorts up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned long and low as the pressure started building again, hoping the sound would motivate him. She was already thinking about what to put on the maintenance list the next time her husband left town.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Delivery Night: and other erotic paranormal stories</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/delivery-night-ebook/"/>
		<published>2024-12-15T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-12-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/delivery-night-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="paranormal" />
    <category term="supernatural" />
    <category term="monster sex" />
    <category term="sci-fi" />
    <category term="aliens" />
    <category term="tentacles" />
    <category term="horror" />
    <category term="vampire" />
    <category term="succubus" />
    <category term="ghost" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/delivery-night-ebook-X84Px4HR90-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Delivery Night&lt;/em&gt; brings you three erotic paranormal stories from author Ruby Pink. In “The Moaning Ghost” a ghost hunter attempts to help an apparition with some unresolved earthly desires. “What Happens on Treaty Station” shares the story of an ambassador’s illicit encounters with a reclusive species at an outpost on the edge of human space. And in the title story, “Delivery Night,” a pizza delivery driver discovers why his coworker warned him not to go inside, even if the woman who answers the door invites him in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruby Pink loves reading erotica but was frustrated to find so many featuring shallow women with no agency. She took up the pen to bring us steamy shorts about real women who aren’t just props in male fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DQJS5646"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Do You Need Assistance?</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/medical/do-you-need-assistance/"/>
		<published>2024-12-09T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-12-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/medical/do-you-need-assistance/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="medical" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="encouragement" />
    <category term="no touching" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/do-you-need-assistance-4mWEMPh0c2-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“It’s half-price margarita night at Tito’s,” Sandra said, rummaging in her purse as she walked to the front door. “Are you coming?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know it!” Gabby smiled. “I just have to close up, and I’ll meet y’all there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the girls who worked at the clinic went out for drinks every Friday. It made up for the fact that the job was otherwise boring and repetitive, collecting fluid samples from annoying patients to be sent off for lab work. She’d been looking forward to this all week, and since today’s final appointment hadn’t shown up, she was now eagerly watching the clock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, don’t take too long. You know how Laura gets with some tequila in her. She’ll end up convincing the group to follow her, and we’ll end up at either karaoke or Devil’s Point again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cast my vote for karaoke,” Gabby laughed. “I’m still finding glitter from last time we went to the strip club.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandra walked out, and before the door closed, a young man in a button-up shirt and slacks came running in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m here!” He leaned on the counter, winded. “I made it in time for my appointment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She frowned at the clock. Technically, the clinic was still open for a few minutes, but any sample would take time to collect and delay her departure. She glanced at the list, to see if he was here for something quick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Peter?” She looked up at him to confirm, and caught him peering down the v-neck of her scrub top. He looked away quickly. She mentally cursed, and adjusted herself. This top was too large, and she’d been meaning to replace it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that’s me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here to provide a semen sample?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yes.” He looked momentarily awkward, but collected himself, trying to play it cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, sir,” she said, standing up and putting on her stern face, “but we just closed. I’m going to have to ask you to reschedule.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She walked to the door, holding it open for him. His face fell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, please?” His eyes darted to her name badge. “Gabby, I work across town. The traffic is killer, and my boss will &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; let me leave early to make an appointment without burning a vacation day. Do me a favor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She hesitated, looking at the clock and dreaming of margaritas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I promise, I won’t take long!” He blushed as soon as he said it, realizing he’d just told a pretty young nurse that he was going to cum quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She laughed, despite herself, and he relaxed, sensing he’d won her over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, if you’re quick.” She locked the door and walked back around the desk. “Let’s get you checked in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes later, she’d given him a collection cup and escorted him to the private room. He seemed nervous, but most guys were awkward about semen samples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She puttered around, shutting down the office and getting ready to leave as soon as he was done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time passed, and she realized with a sinking feeling that he was going to be one of those guys who took a while. Honestly, she felt bad for them. The “private room” was basically a restroom just a few steps from the front desk. During the day, patients and nurses were constantly walking back and forth past the door. It would be like trying to jerk off in the middle of an office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was actually getting more privacy than most, since she was the only one here. But, judging by the time, he was still struggling to get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sighed and drummed her fingernails on the desk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, she couldn’t take it anymore, and knocked gently on his door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sir? Are you okay in there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lock clicked, and he opened the door enough to poke his head out with a sheepish expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, sorry, I’m having a little trouble. Do you have any, like, magazines or anything like that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, we don’t. Could you, um, look at something on your phone?” Now it was her turn to blush. Why did she feel so awkward around this guy? She must be picking up on his vibe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t.” He grimaced. “I only have my work phone, and they monitor what we look at.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I see.” She trailed off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, sorry about this. I’ll, um, I’ll just make it work.” He looked mortified, and moved to close the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait,” she blurted, a bit too loudly. She knew if he closed the door, he would doggedly keep going, no matter how long it took. The other girls would finish their margaritas and move on with their night. She really didn’t want to miss out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you need any assistance?” She winced, wishing she hadn’t phrased it like that, but unsure how else to say it. Unsure, honestly, of what exactly she was suggesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Assistance?” He looked confused. “With…” He trailed off, glancing downward momentarily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, with your, um, sample.” Before he could react to her shocking suggestion, she started talking quickly. “I know it’s not easy! It’s awkward to come somewhere like this and do something like that. I bet you’re feeling some pressure, since you told me you’d be quick, and now you’re all in your head about it, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded slowly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, I just thought, maybe, I could, um, offer some help.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shit. This was the dumbest thing she’d ever done. It sounded like she was propositioning him. He was going to report her to her boss, and she was going to get fired, and probably blacklisted as a sex pest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, I’m sorry,” she stammered, “I don’t know what I was…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, please,” he said quietly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Some help would be great.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They regarded each other for a moment, then he opened the door for her. His pants were undone, and he had one hand still wrapped around his semi-hard cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She walked in, painfully aware that she had no plan for what to do next. She leaned against the sink, arms crossed, biting her lower lip as he closed the door. When he turned around, he looked just as uncertain as she felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How can I—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They both started talking, and stopped at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry,” she said, tucking her hair behind her ear. “This is a little awkward, huh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” He leaned against the door. “I’ve, um, never done this before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Neither have I!” She was suddenly worried that he thought she joined every man in his position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I didn’t mean you had! I just, um…” He trailed off, and they both laughed at the absurdity of the situation. He ran his hand through his hair, and grinned sheepishly at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” she said, smiling back. “Let’s try this again. How can I help?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” He looked briefly panicked at having to suggest something. “Well, I don’t want you to feel like you have to do anything you’re uncomfortable with.” She nodded, waiting for him to continue. “Maybe, um, you could take your top off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She immediately relaxed, realizing that she’d been bracing for him to propose something a lot more intimate. “Sure, I can do that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled her top off over her head, hung it from a hook on the wall, and leaned back against the sink. Her bra wasn’t anything sexy, but even so, he stared hungrily. She felt goose pimples shiver down her arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shared a nervous look with her, then returned his gaze to her chest and started slowly stroking his cock. It had softened during their conversation, but quickly swelled back to life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip. It was always fascinating to watch a guy get hard. He rubbed his thumb repeatedly over his head, pointing it directly at her. Beneath his slacks, he was wearing basic grey boxers, tugged down just enough to reveal a neatly trimmed thatch of dark hair crowning his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He met her eyes again, and inhaled shakily, clearly astonished by what was happening. He shifted his grip, cock twitching eagerly. His eyes roamed excitedly over her torso, and she found herself growing warm under his gaze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She barely knew his name, but here she was undressing and letting him jerk off to the sight of her. Some part of her thought she should feel taken advantage of, but the situation felt refreshingly earnest. There was no pretense here, none of the usual unspoken negotiation that happened around men. No need to dance around the guy’s libido. His desire for her was a simple truth. Naked and growing. She was surprised to find she wanted to encourage it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she ran her hands up her sides and cupped her breasts. He stared, eyes wide, as she caressed and squeezed them through her bra. She felt a rush of excitement as she touched herself the way she imagined he would like to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she slipped a hand inside the cup, he let out a gasp and squeezed himself firmly. Her areola puckered, nipple tightening under her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I, um,” he stammered, hardly daring to ask, “can I see?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, she pulled her bra strap down and scooped her breast from the cup. He shuddered and licked his lips, clearly wishing he was tracing his tongue around her stiff nipple. She reached into the other cup and tried not to imagine pulling his head to her chest. Tried not to notice the growing heat between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As his cock swelled and strained in his grasp, a shiver rolled down her spine. It was thrilling, not knowing what would happen next. This wasn’t like when she normally went home with a guy. That was exciting, sure, but you always had some idea of what to expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d come into this room with no plan, only a vague idea to somehow help him finish faster. She hadn’t really had time to consider what that meant. Despite the long-standing clinic jokes about “platinum service,” it was unheard of for a nurse to assist a patient like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yet, here she was, unhooking her bra and hanging it with her top. She wasn’t dispassionately conducting some medical procedure. This wasn’t clinical. She was intimately involved, actively encouraging his desire. He wasn’t just rubbing out a sample, he was getting off for her. She was going to make him climax. He was going to cum because of her!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She touched herself for him, and thrilled at the lust in his eyes. He was enthralled by the way she grasped and firmly pulled her breasts until her nipples seemed to crackle with electricity. He panted with need as she squeezed them together, hand moving along his shaft with increasing urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d never performed for anyone like this before. She found it intoxicating, the way he hungered for her. His cock throbbed in his hand, and she felt an answering flutter inside. She was eager to see him climax. To see his cock twitching and shooting hot, sticky cream…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, she realized he wasn’t holding the sample cup. It was sitting on the toilet tank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you getting close?” She asked, struggling not to sound too eager. “Do you need the cup?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not yet,” he grunted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, um,” she stumbled over her words as she trapped her nipples between her fingers, sending a wave of sensation dancing through her body. “What can I do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Would you—ah!—touch yourself, too?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wave of heat washed over her body as she considered his suggestion. Should she? She’d started out caressing her breasts just because it seemed to excite him. It was impossible to deny she was turned on by the situation, but wouldn’t it be crossing the line to join him? To masturbate with him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, she rationalized, everything she was doing was to help a patient in her care. This was perhaps an unorthodox method, but he had a medical need, and she could help. If it happened to address a growing need of her own, well, that was just a side effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, that was too much,” he stammered, face flushed. “I shouldn’t have said that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, it’s okay,” she reassured him. “I can do that… if it helps.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It would help,” he agreed. “Please.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She slipped a hand into her waistband, savoring his gaze as she slowly reached lower. Parting her legs a bit, she wasn’t surprised to find she was already wet. Bracing herself on the sink with one hand, she closed her eyes and focused on the sensation of her finger slipping between her lips. Gasping, she pressed her palm against her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted, and she opened her eyes to find him watching her intently. It was happening. They were masturbating together! His hand was flying on his cock, and she was curling her finger repeatedly inside. She was touching herself for him. Letting him watch her. The thought made her moan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She realized with a thrill that he would probably cum faster if he could see what she was doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Would you like me to take these off, too?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck yes,” he moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, she pushed her scrub pants and underwear down around her knees, unwilling to take the time to undress fully. She spread her legs, and he groaned as she pushed her finger back inside. Her heart was pounding, watching him watch her. She leaned heavily on the sink, working her finger in a come-hither motion, reaching for that magic spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was panting now, stroking his cock frantically. His head was swollen and smeared with precum. She noticed his slacks had slipped partway down his tensed thighs. His entire body was vibrating with the urgent need to cum, but it still seemed elusive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What could she do? She added another finger, moaning quietly as she began thrusting into herself, matching his pace. Unbidden, she found herself imagining bending over the sink as he stepped forward to bury himself in her, fucking her fast and hard until he groaned, and she felt him twitching inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the look on his face, he was imagining something similar. Her pussy clenched around her fingers as she imagined how good he would feel inside her…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No! What was she doing? She couldn’t get carried away. She didn’t even know this guy, and they were here for a reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cup! She needed to make him cum in the cup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Peter,” she gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned when she said his name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re ready, aren’t you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get the cup, Pete.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blinking away whatever fantasy he was engaged in, he leaned over and grabbed the cup, holding it below the tip of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you gonna cum for me?” She purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m close,” he moaned, staring at the fingers plunging in and out of her pussy. “I’m so close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Me too,” she gasped, surprised to realize it. “I want to cum with you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” he grunted, face screwed up with effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you imagining something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay,” she urged. “Tell me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was thinking about walking over there,” he groaned, “and lifting you up onto that sink…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Keep going,” she breathed, feeling the pressure building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I would grab your tits…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“More,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And shove my cock into your wet… fucking… pussy!” He punctuated each word by thrusting forward, fucking his fist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” She squeezed her legs together as her insides begin to clench rapidly around her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And cum… inside… Aaah! Oh, fuck! I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” she moaned, as the climax rippled through her body. “Cum for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stared, wide-eyed at her, rocking back and forth. She watched, fascinated, as his cum shot into the cup. She ground her palm against her clit, the pressure sending diffuse waves of pleasure through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm,” she moaned happily. “That was so fucking hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he panted, leaning heavily against the door, after milking the last spurt carefully into the cup. “Fuck,” he repeated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shivered as she withdrew her fingers, and giggled at the cream around her knuckles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Peter, I suppose I should have asked this earlier, but you’re not married or anything, are you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, no, no, no,” he said breathlessly, screwing the lid onto the sample cup. “My lesbian friend asked me to be a donor for her and her partner, but I had to get checked first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” she smiled. “In that case, how do you feel about margaritas?”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Hypnosis is Ridiculous</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/mind-control/hypnosis-is-ridiculous/"/>
		<published>2024-11-28T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-11-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/mind-control/hypnosis-is-ridiculous/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="mind control" />
    <category term="hypnosis" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="coworker" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="hair pulling" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/hypnosis-is-ridiculous-jk4lwMRq2D-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Hey, Lauren.” Brad grinned at her from across the snack table. “Did I ever tell you I know hypnosis?” He was prone to outrageous claims like this. Once, he’d spent weeks trying to convince her that he was descended from royalty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think I’d remember if you ever said something like that.” she winked playfully, pouring herself more eggnog. “See, I would have lost all respect for you, since hypnosis is bullshit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lauren had been hiding in the break room, avoiding two groups of coworkers at the office holiday party. Karen was trying to gather people for a Christmas-themed trivia game, and Joey was drunkenly recruiting people to go caroling, of all things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brad didn’t know it, but his timing was perfect. He might be a bit of a dork, but bantering with him was far more entertaining than trivia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, come on,” he protested, laughing off her good-natured ribbing. “I’m serious. I took a course and everything. Even got a certificate!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A certificate! Well, that changes everything. How much did that cost you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” he hesitated, picking up a cookie, “you can’t really put a price on a life-changing ability like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ooh, it was a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt;, huh?” She sucked air between her teeth, playing it up. “That’s too bad, buddy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They paused for a moment as a few coworkers came in to grab drinks. One of them warned Lauren that Karen was looking for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m telling you,” Brad said confidently after the others left, “this is the real deal.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And I’m telling you, you got scammed.” She grinned and sipped her eggnog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lauren,” he said with sudden seriousness. “I’ll bet you a hundred bucks I can hypnotize you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She eyed him over the rim of her cup. He wasn’t kidding! She’d thought he was just goofing around, but maybe he really did get scammed? Now she actually felt a little bad for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, a hundred bucks…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on,” he said, seeing her consider it. “What do you have to lose? You think hypnosis is bullshit, right? It should be easy money.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I dunno. How does this work? Are you gonna try to hypnotize me here in the break room? Make me think I’m a chicken or something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, all this Christmas music is too distracting. We should go somewhere quieter. And don’t worry about the chicken thing, hypnosis can’t make you do anything you don’t want to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The approaching sound of drunken singing made up her mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, quick, before Joey finds us. Let’s go to an empty office so I can win this bet, and you can contribute to my shoe fund.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes later, having successfully evaded the carolers, Lauren shut the door behind her. The office had a nice view of the city, and a miniature Christmas tree with twinkling lights on the windowsill. Brad pulled out the desk chair for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sat down carefully, adjusting the hem of her dress, and tried not to smirk as Brad got into character. He rolled up his sleeves and produced a shiny copper coin hung from a chain. Standing seriously before her, he set the coin swinging like a pendulum. She played along, following it with her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, I want you to focus on the coin. Watch it swing back and forth.” He spoke in a low voice, clearly reciting a memorized script. “Back and forth. You are becoming relaxed. Back and forth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She didn’t feel any different. Maybe a little warm. A bit distracted by a raucous group of people coming down the hall. Something crashed, and they all laughed loudly. “Don’t worry about that noise,” he improvised. “Just focus on the coin.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lauren tried not to laugh. This was going to be the easiest money she’d ever made. She wondered how long he’d keep trying before admitting defeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whew, it’s warm in here,” he murmured, undoing a button on his shirt with one hand while continuing to swing the coin with the other. “Back and forth. You should be feeling very relaxed now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shifted uncomfortably in the chair. He was right, this office was quite warm. She slipped her cardigan off, hanging it over the back of the chair, trying to keep her eyes on the coin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your focus is entirely on the coin. Back and forth. Relaxed. Calm.” He wiped his forehead nervously. “No thoughts, no concerns, no hesitations, just, um,” he trailed off as he fumbled with another shirt button. “Sorry, can you help me out? This is tricky with one hand.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rolling her eyes, she reached up to finish unbuttoning his shirt. He continued to swing the coin in front of her face. Did he really think this was working? She helped him pull his arm from one sleeve, then he moved the coin to his other hand, and let her pull the other sleeve off. Carelessly, he tossed his shirt onto the desk, standing before her in an undershirt. Without stopping the coin’s movement, he fanned himself with his other hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Back and forth. Your relaxation is growing with every passing moment. Back and forth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt a trickle of sweat roll down her back and bit her lip in annoyance. Despite his continued intonation, she did not feel relaxed. She crossed, then uncrossed her legs. If he took much longer, she was going to sweat through her dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, it’s so warm in here!” He grinned sheepishly. “It doesn’t, um, normally take this long. I’m sure the heat is making it hard to concentrate. Just try to focus on the coin.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was ridiculous. She wondered if he’d picked this office on purpose, to trick her into giving up and losing the bet. That wasn’t going to happen. He’d never let her hear the end of it. She had to stick it out. But if he took much longer, she was going to end up sweaty and disheveled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hold on,” she said. “I can’t concentrate like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh? Are you ready to give up and admit I know hypnosis?” He asked eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not even,” she laughed as she stood up and turned partly away from him, trying to watch the coin over her shoulder. “Unzip me?” Sensing his hesitation, she rolled her eyes. “Don’t get any funny ideas. It’s just that if you take any longer, I’m going to sweat through everything, and this outfit is dry-clean only.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, he unzipped her dress, which she slipped off with great relief. After laying it carefully over the back of the chair, she sat down again, wearing just her bra and thong. It was still too warm, but now she could focus on winning the bet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brad was staring. She crossed her arms and gave him a pointed look. He cleared his throat and tore his eyes from her chest, still swinging the coin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry! Sorry. Um, back and forth. Back and forth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He seemed so flustered, she almost felt bad. She resolved to play along and help him get his confidence back, so that later, he wouldn’t accuse her of distracting him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You are feeling very relaxed. Very calm. You are not bothered at all by how stupidly hot it is in this office.” He untucked his undershirt, and quickly flapped the hem, trying to fan himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sighed and tried to keep her focus on the coin. It was like a sauna in here. She glanced at the window and briefly considered leaning against the cool glass for relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Back and forth…” He hesitated, wiping his forehead again. “Okay, I wouldn’t ask this, except you took your dress off, so, um, would it be okay if I did the same?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seems only fair,” she conceded. “I suppose you need help again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If that’s okay,” he said, kicking his shoes off. “If I stop swinging the coin, we’ll have to start over again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She stood up to help pull his undershirt over his head, one arm at a time. He had a nice chest, she noted idly, resisting a sudden urge to run her hands over his torso. She blinked the thought away. Where did that come from?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He kept swinging the coin in front of her face as she sat down. Leaning forward, she unbuckled his belt and started lowering his slacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dude!” She jerked back at the unexpected sight of his cock swinging free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shit!” He awkwardly attempted to tug his slacks back up with one hand. “Sorry! I forgot I came to the party commando.” He hesitated. “But, do I really have to put my pants back on? I mean, you’ve already seen it. And, seriously, it’s &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; hot in here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He continued swinging the coin as she frowned at him. Some part of her knew she should be upset. But he looked so awkward, she couldn’t bring herself to be mad. Plus, she had to admit he wasn’t bad to look at. Surprisingly hung. He kept trimmed and looked clean. It twitched hopefully as she regarded it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever, forget about it,” she said, swatting his hand away, and letting his slacks fall to the floor. “It’s just a penis. Nothing to worry about.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool.” He stood confidently before her, swinging the coin. “Then, keep focusing. Back and forth. You are deeply relaxed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hypnosis was bullshit, but she had to admit, he’d finally managed to capture her full attention. She bit her lip. His cock was slowly swelling to life, lifting toward her, and swaying in time with the coin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Back and forth. God, it’s so hot in here,” he exclaimed again. “Are you sure you’re not too warm? I mean, now that I’m undressed, I feel way better. Wouldn’t you be more comfortable if you took your bra and underwear off? It seems silly for me to be naked, while you have to keep those on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was feeling flushed. Her bra itched, and she struggled to think of a reason to keep it on. He was already naked. She was nearly naked. And nothing inappropriate was going to happen, it was just practical to strip down in this heat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine,” she sighed. “I guess if you’ve already gone that far, there’s no reason for me to be uncomfortable.” She unhooked her bra and let it slip down her arms, feeling immediate relief. The air felt good on her bare skin. She exhaled in satisfaction and lay it on top of her dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you go,” he grinned as she stood up and pulled down her thong. “Feels better, huh? Now you can focus. That money is as good as yours.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right!” She laughed and gave him a wink. “I told you hypnosis is bullshit. I don’t feel any different at all.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She didn’t feel hypnotized, but she was struggling to focus on the coin instead of his cock. It was now fully erect, and bobbed back and forth in time with the coin. She wondered how it would feel in her hand. To her surprise, she found herself starting to reach for him, and quickly grabbed the edge of the seat instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you sure about that?” He raised an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Absolutely sure. I’m wide awake and in full control.” She resolved not to let him see how distracted she was. He’d try to claim it was the hypnosis, but it was only natural to want to look. How often did you get to see a coworker nude, let alone with their rather appealing erection swaying in front of your face? No one could blame her for being curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Back and forth. You’re becoming entranced.” His voice dropped back into that practiced rhythm. “Back and forth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squeezed her legs together and tried to focus on the bet. If she proved him wrong, she’d get a hundred bucks to put towards those new shoes she wanted. All she had to do was concentrate, and stop getting distracted by the thought of running her tongue up his shaft like a popsicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Follow the movement. Back and forth. You feel deeply relaxed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck, what was she doing? This was inappropriate! She shouldn’t be salivating over Brad’s dick like this. No matter how enticing it looked, or how good it would feel to touch…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re getting very aroused.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” She looked up at him, blushing furiously. “How did you… I mean, no I’m not!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You haven’t been watching the coin at all.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I, just,” she gestured at his cock. “It’s distracting!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can see that. Your nipples are hard.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That doesn’t mean anything!” She protested, resisting the suddenly overwhelming urge to squeeze her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And you’re squirming.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I am?” Shit. She hadn’t realized quite how obvious she was being. Now that she considered it, that familiar heat between her thighs had been building for some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay,” Brad reassured her. “Obviously, I’m turned on, too. I’ve been trying not to take advantage of your hypnotized state, but, uh, it’s difficult when you lick your lips and lean closer like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She hadn’t realized how far forward she was bending. With some effort, she forced herself to lean back in the chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look, forget about the coin,” he said, dropping it on the floor. “Hypnosis works with any focal point. And you’ve been fixated on my cock ever since we got undressed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? No, dude. I didn’t get hypnotized by your dick. Don’t be ridiculous.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, it’s perfectly natural! You wanted to win the bet so bad, you slipped into a state of hyper-focus.” His cock twitched. “And now you can’t stop staring.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can stop!” She wrenched her eyes away, and triumphantly stuck her tongue out at him. “See? Just admit that you never hypnotized me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t do that. You’re definitely in a trance. Look at you, with your tongue out, leaning forward again without realizing it. It’s obvious that you’re thinking about wrapping your lips around me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not!” She absolutely was. She wanted to lick up that little bead of precum that had appeared at the tip. To swirl her tongue around his head, and swallow him. With some difficulty, she closed her mouth and pulled away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you even realize you’ve got a hand between your legs? Do you know how long you’ve been playing with yourself?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t,” she protested, “I wasn’t…” But it was true. Without even realizing she was doing it, her fingers had begun caressing her lips. She was sensitive, hungry for stimulation, and slick with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you wet?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! I mean, fuck, yes,” she swore as she slipped a finger inside, “but this is stupid. Hypnosis is bullshit. I’m probably just ovulating, is all. I always get horny this time of the month, and you were swinging your cock in front of my face. Of course I got turned on! If we hadn’t picked such a warm office, and started undressing, nothing would have happened.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I have to tell you,” he said with some reluctance, “it’s not actually very warm in here. That was part of the hypnosis. I didn’t expect it to go this far.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s ridiculous. It’s like a sauna in here. The thermostat must be broken.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lauren, I’m sorry that I’m such a gifted hypnotist.” He wrapped his hand around his shaft and started stroking. “I’m trying to do the right thing, but it’s hard with you touching yourself like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Gifted, my ass,” she groaned, squeezing her breast. “You got swindled with a fake hypnosis class, and spent thirty minutes waving that stupid coin in front of me.” Unable to stop herself, she added another finger, curling inward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How can you be so sure?” He gasped, flicking his thumb over his head. “Look at you spreading your legs so I can see you fingering yourself. You can’t help it. You got hypnotized by my cock, and now you’re uncontrollably aroused.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nooo,” she protested, “I’m not! I just—Fuck, I’m so wet—It’s not hypnosis, it’s just dumb luck. Right place, right time. If it wasn’t you, I’d have gone home early, and I’d be rubbing one out in bed right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t believe you,” he panted, stepping closer, masturbating directly in front of her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t care,” she moaned. “I just… Oh fuck, I just need…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you’re not hypnotized,” he shivered, feeling her hot breath on his skin, “then why are you opening your mouth for me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, shut up.” Her fingers worked urgently, wetness dripping from her knuckles. With her mouth open wide, she leaned forward, unable to stop herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned as she wrapped her lips around him as last. He was hot and firm, and she moaned as his cock throbbed on her tongue. The pressure in her core was building, squeezing around her fingers. He leaned forward, bracing himself on the back of the chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lauren,” he gasped in surprise as she angled her head to let him go deeper. “Oh fuck!” She braced her hand on his pelvis as he pushed eagerly into her throat. She struggled to relax her jaw, resisting the instinct to gag. “Fuck!” He thrust forward, unable to resist the urge to bury himself. She saw flares of color at the edge of her vision, and a warm gush around her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she pushed him away, choking as he pulled out. He staggered back against the wall, hand in a fist around the base of his cock. She sank back in the chair, gasping for breath. He stared, eyes wide, as she rubbed tight circles around her clit with one hand, still fingering herself with the other. She watched hungrily as he started slowly stroking the length of his shaft for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know that, uh,” he panted, struggling to control himself. “I know you want to win the bet. I know you think hypnosis is fake.” She shook her head, wanting him to stop talking. “But, come on. Just admit it! Admit that you’re absurdly turned on, and it’s because you were put in a trance by my cock.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me,” she groaned. “I’ve never seen a dude work so hard to avoid getting laid.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Laid?” His cock throbbed eagerly in his hand. “Lauren, look, I like you, and fucking hell do I want to go further, but you’re in a trance. It wouldn’t be right.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not in a goddamn trance,” she growled. “I’m just horny, and I need a cock inside me, and you’re lucky enough to be here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know,” he hesitated. “I don’t want to risk our friendship.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s risking our friendship is if you don’t bend me over this desk right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before he could answer, she got out of the chair and shoved everything on the desk to one side. Then she bent over the edge, and wiggled her ass at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he mumbled, stepping up behind her. She shivered in anticipation as he rubbed the head of his cock between her lips. “Alright.” She laid her cheek on the cool surface and grabbed the far side of the desktop. They both moaned as he pushed inside, burying himself in one stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt deliriously good as he filled her. It was like letting out a breath she hadn’t realized she’d been holding. The entire time she’d been watching his cock sway back and forth in front of her eyes, her body had been preparing for this moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grabbed her hips as he started sliding in and out. Every motion sent a ripple of sensation along her spine, leaving her gasping in time with his thrusts. He groaned as she squeezed around him, desperate for more. Her body was crackling with lust. She couldn’t believe how good this felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abandoning any efforts at control, he began moving more urgently. She bit her knuckle to keep from loudly crying out with every thrust. The smaller items on the desk moved rhythmically, inching closer and closer to the edge. A cup of pens clattered loudly to the floor. A desk lamp fell, hanging by the cord, swaying in time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock seemed to swell, and she suddenly needed to shove a hand between her legs, clamping her fingers over her clit. Firm pressure helped to diffuse the nearly overwhelming sensation. She moaned, and reached lower, to brush against his shaft thrusting urgently into her. He was hard and hot and slick with her wetness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned, feeling her touch, and started fucking her even harder. His fingers dug painfully into her hips, and she did cry out then. Her body shook, spasming with pleasure, squeezing around his girth. With a gush, she came, dripping down her thighs and onto the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lauren,” he panted, “I’m close. Where should I cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her cunt clenched excitedly at the thought of letting him finish inside. She moaned happily, knowing that her climax was pushing him closer to the edge. Still holding her clit with one hand, she lifted onto her other elbow to look back at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cum inside me,” she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he gasped, eyes wide with surprise. “Are you sure—ah!—you don’t want me to cum on your tits?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop trying to prove you hypnotized me! I know what I want!” She rubbed her clit, building rapidly towards another orgasm. “Now, pull my hair and fucking cum in me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He reached forward, grabbed her hair in one hand, and pulled gently back, grunting with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Harder!” She groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tightened his grip, jerking her head back. Her mouth hung open, panting as he fucked her over the desk. Waves of pleasure radiated from her core, rippling around his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cumming!” He blurted, as he slammed into her one last time, burying himself deep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck! Yes!” She shuddered as she felt him twitching. “Oh my god!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let go of her hair and leaned against her, making a little surprised sound each time he throbbed inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned happily, finally feeling completely relaxed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After some time, he softened and slipped out. She covered her lips with her fingers, trying to keep his cum from leaking all over the floor. The pressure felt good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stumbled back and collapsed into the desk chair, trying to catch his breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turned around, leaning on the desk with one hand between her legs, and smiled crookedly at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, Brad, that was something.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He laughed breathlessly and gave her a thumbs-up in agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still tingling with aftershocks of pleasure, she picked up a fallen box of tissues and started wiping up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lauren,” he said, climbing to his feet, “that was incredible.” She nodded in agreement. “But seriously, I shouldn’t have let that get out of hand…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you still worried about the bet?” She laughed incredulously. “You lost, man! Your hypnosis didn’t do anything, just like I knew it wouldn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, seriously, I don’t think you…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Brad, forget it.” She stepped into her underwear. “Did you have a good time?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, yeah, but…” He watched her fasten her bra with concern in his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So did I. I’ll make you a deal.” She pulled up her dress and turned around so he could zip her up. “Keep your money, but take me out to dinner soon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded as she gave him a kiss on the cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And no more hypnosis talk, alright? It was a decent pickup line, but you can consider me ‘captivated’ already.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She walked out feeling quite pleased with herself, leaving him looking awestruck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hypnosis! Ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>The Coat Check Room: and other erotic short stories</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/coat-check-room-ebook/"/>
		<published>2024-11-27T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-11-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/coat-check-room-ebook/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="bdsm" />
    <category term="domination" />
    <category term="submission" />
    <category term="femdom" />
    <category term="humiliation" />
    <category term="reluctance" />
    <category term="control" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="coworker" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/coat-check-room-ebook-bjY-MRYX9f-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Coat Check Room&lt;/em&gt; brings you three steamy short stories from author Ruby Pink exploring domination and submission. “The Queen of Marketing” acts out a longtime fantasy by dominating the insufferable head of another department. In “Shower Surprise,” a man is caught in an indiscreet moment by his impatient coworker when he forgets to lock the door to the office shower room. And in the titular “Coat Check Room,” a coat check girl takes great delight in telling her companion about her journey into the world of submissiveness, teasing him mercilessly, until his boss catches them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruby Pink loves reading erotica but was frustrated to find so many featuring shallow women with no agency. She took up the pen to bring us steamy shorts about real women who aren’t just props in male fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DP52V991"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
</feed>
