<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Ruby Pink Romance</title>
	<subtitle>Classy smut for classy people</subtitle>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/"/>
	<updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Ruby Pink</name>
		<email>hello@rubypinkromance.com</email>
	</author>
  <icon>https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rubypink.jpg</icon>
	<entry>
		<title>Relieving the Tension</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/relieving-the-tension/"/>
		<published>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/relieving-the-tension/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="straight sex" />
    <category term="coworkers" />
    <category term="sexual tension" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/relieving-the-tension-GHaOLxrfqk-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“We have to do something about this sexual tension,” I said, stretching my back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” His eyes snapped guiltily to my face. He’d been staring at my chest. “Sorry, what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our presentation is tomorrow, and I can’t think straight around you right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh?” He regarded me curiously. I suspected this was the first time he’d ever been propositioned by a woman. He was attractive enough, and good at his job, but clearly uncomfortable spending so much time alone with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company had flown us out a few days before the big client meeting so we could meet our contacts face-to-face and build rapport. We had separate hotel rooms, but my seniority meant I got a larger suite, which we’d set up as our base of operations. He slept in his room, but otherwise, for three straight days, we’d spent every hour together refining our pitch deck. We really only left the room for dinner and drinks with the clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure what started the tension growing. Perhaps it was a subliminal thing. The entire time we were working from the sofa, my bed was in sight. Or maybe it was our physical proximity. Sitting so close together, it was impossible to avoid little moments of contact. My hand would brush against his, reaching for a pen. His leg would press against mine as he showed me something on his screen. I even became familiar with his scent…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong. He was perfectly respectful, aside from some difficulty keeping his eyes out of my cleavage. But after three days, I found myself wishing he’d be &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; respectful. My career has always been my priority, which doesn’t leave much room for chasing physical attraction. But the smoldering heat between us was difficult to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I knew he desired me. At one point, I had to plug my phone in, and unintentionally gave him a view down my shirt. When I looked up, he quickly turned away, and his face turned bright red.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, I had to be certain, so this morning, I’d answered the door in my workout gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on in and get started. I just need a quick rinse.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He did his best not to stare at my nipples poking through my sports bra, or ogle the way my tights hugged my ass. Even so, I swayed my hips as I disappeared into the bathroom, confident he was watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After my shower, I casually walked out wrapped in a towel. He looked up from his laptop, wide-eyed and flustered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, I forgot these,” I said, grabbing the lacy panties and bra I’d left on the bed. By the time I reappeared fully dressed (with my blouse unbuttoned a bit lower than I would at the office), he seemed quite distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, here we were, the evening before our big presentation, and the tension was palpable. We’d had drinks with the client and came back to my room to make some last-minute changes to the pitch deck. But he could barely keep his eyes off me, and I was having trouble not losing myself in fantasies of pushing him down on the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can’t think straight around me?” His expression said he wasn’t quite allowing himself to believe me. “Because of sexual tension?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right. And I think you feel the same way.” I scooted closer to him, until our thighs were touching, and draped my arm over the back of the sofa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he swallowed. “I suppose that’s true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If we don’t do something,” I said, tracing my finger down the buttons on his shirt, “we’ll be distracted tomorrow. We’ll mess up the pitch, and lose out on the deal. I don’t want that. Do you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No. No, but, uh, what do you have in mind?” He shifted nervously, his erection starting to swell to life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think,” I whispered, “we should get undressed…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes?” He shivered with anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Move over to the bed…” I slid my hand up his thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll suck your &lt;em&gt;cock&lt;/em&gt;…” I purred, squeezing him through his slacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ahhh!” His shaft throbbed under my touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ll lick my clit…” I squeezed my thighs together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then I’m going to get on top and ride you until we both &lt;em&gt;cum&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock twitched urgently, and he stood up quickly, fumbling with his belt. I smiled and sauntered toward the bed, unzipping my skirt and letting it fall to the floor, quickly followed by my blouse. He trailed after, shedding his clothes. I pulled his arms around me and encouraged him to kiss my neck. He fumbled with my bra, but at last the straps slid down my arms, and I tossed it toward my bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He lowered his head to my chest, and eagerly licked my nipples. I inhaled at the sensation, and pulled him closer. He awkwardly shuffled out of his underwear, and I felt his erection bumping against my hip as I pulled him back up into a kiss. His hands explored my body, making my skin tingle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I pushed him back onto the bed. He shuffled higher, cock swaying as he went. I crawled after him, making eye contact and licking my lips. He watched, enthralled, as I licked up the full length before taking him into my mouth. When I began to swirl my tongue around the tip, he gasped, and I tasted his precum. I moaned eagerly and started bobbing my head, taking him deeper. He put a hand on my shoulder, encouraging me as he began to lift his hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wave of lust crashed over me, making my toes curl. His heat filled my mouth, and I wanted more. He cried out as I sucked harder. His thrusting grew more urgent, and he squeezed my shoulder. My insides clenched as I finally swallowed him, taking him into my throat. He groaned loudly as my lips met the base of his shaft. I held him there as long as I could, until my eyes watered, only backing off when I was about to choke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I gazed up at him, gasping for breath, a string of drool stretching between my lips and the tip of his twitching cock. He growled hungrily and rolled me over onto my back. I lifted my hips to allow him to remove my underwear, then spread my legs wide for him. I felt the weight of his gaze on my pussy, and reveled in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gave me a crooked smile, and then lowered himself between my thighs. He spread me open with two fingers and lapped between my lips, eager to taste me. I arched my back and gasped as he explored every fold, until his tongue pushed deep inside. He looked up at me over my mound, nose pressed against my clit, eyes full of hunger. I could only squeal and grasp the sheets as he devoured me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, I couldn’t take any more. I needed him. I pushed him away and rolled shakily to my knees. He grinned and lay down on his back, ready for me. His cock, still glistening with my saliva, throbbed and twitched against his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, I climbed on top, hands on his shoulders, and sighed as I slipped along the length of his shaft. He seemed as hard as iron against my soft, swollen lips, which parted eagerly for him. I allowed myself to savor the feeling, grinding and sliding against him, letting the anticipation build.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and reached for my breasts. I leaned into his grasp, encouraging him to massage and squeeze. My nipples tightened under his touch, and I squeezed my thighs around him. He was lifting his hips now, humping against me, pulling back further, desperate to bury himself in my heat. I shivered as my body seemed to contract, waves of sensation rolling between my breasts and my clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I rocked back, reached down to position him, and allowed him to thrust inside. He cried out, and squeezed my tits hard, making me gasp and clench around his cock. I dug my fingernails into his shoulders and rolled my hips, changing the pressure. He stared up at me with eyes full of lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, I started rocking back and forth, savoring the way he filled me. He panted and rolled my nipples between his fingers. I moaned long and low, gradually increasing the pace. He was firm and unyielding, deep inside, and my pussy grasped and pulled, alternately trying to bring him deeper and push him out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we moved faster, the room filled with the sound of his prick thrusting into my cunt. I shuddered and bucked, tossing my hair and yelping uncontrollably. He grunted and growled, muttering curses under his breath. He stiffened, legs going rigid, about to cum…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I slapped him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His eyes opened wide in shock, but his legs relaxed. Barely able to form words, I tried to tell him, not yet, that I needed more. I don’t know if he understood. He couldn’t answer because I had shoved my fingers in his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt my climax building, as if I was climbing a hill. Rocking back and forth on his swollen cock, the pressure built slowly. I felt myself grow tighter around him, every sensation amplified. He was buried deep inside, and I could feel every inch. My vision dimmed, my entire world narrowing to the feeling of him inside me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rode him hard and fast, fucking him until I saw colors. My thighs squeezed, my nails dug deeper. He groaned in protest, and I leaned against his hands on my tits as my orgasm crashed around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A gush of hot wetness around the base of his cock. Clenching and throbbing that seemed to start in my chest and roll down my spine around his shaft. Someone was crying out, embarrassingly loud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted around my fingers, and shook his head, trying to speak. Still savoring the lingering contractions, I pulled my hand away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m gonna cum! Oh fuck, I’m gonna cum so hard,” he blurted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, do it,” I growled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He went rigid again, and I felt his cock twitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, I jumped off and spun around, taking him into my mouth. He tasted strongly of my pussy. Immediately, he exploded, pumping his spunk against my tongue, mixing our flavors together. I looked up and met his eyes, letting him watch as I squeezed and sucked, milking out every last drop. His body rocked with each diminishing spurt, until at last, he lay still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of swallowing, I opened my mouth, letting his cum run out, pooling at the base of his shaft. He gasped at the sight, and I wrapped my lips around the tip for one last spurt, which I did swallow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally spent, he collapsed, panting for breath, as I lay my head on his hip and absent-mindedly ran my fingers through the sticky mess we’d made. I felt utterly and completely satiated. With the tension released, I could finally think straight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm,” I agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shower, maybe room service. Get some sleep, then the presentation tomorrow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh, I meant between us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” I said. To be honest, it hadn’t occurred to me until that very moment that there might be anything between us beyond the immediate need. “Well, we seem to make a good team. You take direction well. I suppose it depends on how good a job we do with the presentation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” He nodded to himself. “Right, the presentation. Then we’ll see.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see,” I agreed, smiling to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 2: Taking it Further: Only One Bed, Book 2</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/2-taking-it-further/"/>
		<published>2024-08-11T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/2-taking-it-further/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="vacation sex" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-2-zUfUX_gZYR-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;When Emma found out that she and her three friends would have to share a room with just one bed, she was convinced it would ruin their tropical vacation. However, the close quarters had unexpected benefits, and she surprised herself by fooling around with hunky surfer Nolan. That passionate moment was memorable, but despite her best friend Zoya’s encouragement, Emma isn’t sure if she should take things further. Will she push Nolan away, or take things further and make this the best vacation ever?&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DCTZTJZD"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Go Ask Your Girlfriend!</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/go-ask-your-girlfriend/"/>
		<published>2024-08-10T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/go-ask-your-girlfriend/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="first time" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="instruction" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="missionary" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/go-ask-your-girlfriend-f6d9U2mE_e-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Thank you so much, Heather,” Jimmy’s mom apologized as they stood on the porch. “I know it’s a bit unusual, but obviously, at Jimmy’s age, we couldn’t call any of his old sitters.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry,” Heather reassured her. “I’m happy to keep an eye on him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ve had these tickets for months, but Jack was talking about canceling! When Karen mentioned you were home for the summer, it seemed like a perfect fit. I remembered Jimmy and your younger brother were friends, and how you used to drive them to the mall after you got your driver’s license. You were always so responsible…” She trailed off as the shouting from inside got louder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is bullshit!” Jimmy stomped down the stairs after his father. “I graduated last week. I don’t need a babysitter!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“After the shit you pulled…” Jimmy’s dad pinched his nose and turned to face his son. “Trust is &lt;em&gt;earned&lt;/em&gt;, kiddo. And you’ve lost ours, at least for now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh!” Jimmy threw his hands in the air and stormed off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry about that, Heather,” Jimmy’s dad sighed. “He’ll calm down. Here’s some money for delivery. Make yourself at home. We’ll be back around eleven.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take your time,” she smiled, tucking the cash into her hoodie pocket and waving as they climbed in the car. She closed the front door and followed the sound of banging cabinets to the kitchen, where Jimmy was rummaging for snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Trust is earned,” he muttered in a mocking tone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up, Jimmy,” Heather said, trying to keep the amusement from her voice. She’d only been at university for two years, but these teenage dramatics already seemed like the distant past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Heather.” He scowled while devouring a granola bar. “He’s &lt;em&gt;totally&lt;/em&gt; overreacting, you know. It was just a party! No reason to treat me like a child.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“From what I heard, that party got shut down by the cops. I’m not surprised he’s pissed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How’d &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; hear about it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A few guys from my dorm told me. They came back to town that weekend for a game, heard about a party, and decided to crash it. They were like, ‘you should have seen these high school kids going buck wild!’ I mean, damn, Jimmy,” she teased, “I can’t believe the shy kid I knew from photography class threw a rager!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It wasn’t that wild,” he grinned, trying to play it cool, but clearly pleased by her reaction. “A couple of broken windows. Someone puked in the pool. The cops only showed up because the music was too loud.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sure,” she laughed. “Look, man, I get this is weird, but I’m just here to make sure you don’t burn the place down or whatever. I’ll order some pizza and watch a movie. You can hang with me or do your own thing. No big deal, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, okay,” he sighed. “Not your fault my dad’s a dick.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of hours later, they were sitting together on the couch, with the remains of a pizza on the coffee table. Jimmy seemed noticeably more relaxed after eating. Heather was only half paying attention to the movie. Her phone kept buzzing with messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who are you talking to?” Jimmy asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A guy from school.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anyone I know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” she chuckled. “You don’t know him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you guys dating?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dating?” She raised an eyebrow. “No, we just hang out sometimes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool,” he nodded. “Cool, cool, cool.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes passed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So,” Jimmy asked with studied casualness, “what are you guys talking about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why do you want to know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, it’s gotta be more interesting than this weird French chick flick.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey,” she protested, “I like this movie!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ve seen it before?” He looked baffled. “Why’d you put it on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It makes me happy. I like watching them fall in love.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy rolled his eyes, but returned to the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long, her phone buzzed again. She read the message, laughed, and typed out a reply. When she looked up, Jimmy was watching her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“C’mon, tell me what you sent. This movie is boring and I hate subtitles.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s about to get to the best part.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sure they’ll kiss under a rainbow or some shit. What’d you send?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You really want to know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, tell me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine. I said I’d give him a blow job next time I see him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Uh… Cool.” Obviously flustered, he turned away. She tried not to laugh at how red he turned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next scene was her favorite. The leading man realized he’d been an idiot and confessed his love for the heroine. She admitted to herself that she loved him as well, and they fell into a passionate embrace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music swelled, and Heather smiled, imagining herself in the heroine’s place, pressing her body against his, feeling his lips on hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The leading man’s shirt fell to the floor, and the heroine traced her fingers over his bare chest. He removed her bra, and she gasped as he kissed her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy kept glancing in Heather’s direction. She crossed her legs, suddenly aware of both how short her skirt was and how long the scene was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heroine moaned as the leading man lowered her onto the bed. She arched her back as he moved lower, until only his tousled hair was visible between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy shifted awkwardly, and pulled a pillow into his lap. Heather bit her lip. She didn’t remember the movie being this explicit, and now she felt a little guilty for making that blowjob comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The leading man moved behind the heroine as she rolled onto her hands and knees. He thrust forward, and she cried out, gripping the sheets as they started moving together. Her breasts swayed, erect nipples dragging against the silk sheet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather shivered, imagining the sensation, and crossed her arms over her chest. Jimmy met her eyes for a moment, and quickly looked away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heroine climaxed, calling the leading man’s name as he moaned and collapsed on top of her. They rolled into a loving kiss as the credits rolled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” Jimmy said calmly. “That movie was pretty good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They both dissolved into laughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh man,” she said, wiping tears from her eyes. “That was a lot steamier than I remembered.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I see why you like it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; why I like it!” She threw a pillow at him, which knocked away the one in his lap. “Looks like you did, though.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I, uh…” He trailed off as he followed her gaze to the rather obvious erection tenting his shorts. “Ack!” He grabbed for one of the pillows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At ease, Jimbo.” She winked. “No need to salute.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry! Sorry.” His face had turned bright red with embarrassment. She felt bad for him, honestly. Teenage boys popped a boner if you looked at them funny, and she’d just made him sit next to her through a seriously hot sex scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it had affected her, too, because she couldn’t help noticing Jimmy had really grown into himself. Last time she’d seen him, he was all elbows and knees, gangly as a colt. Now his shoulders were broader, and he seemed to have filled in a bit. She found herself imagining moving closer, reaching into his shorts to wrap her hand around…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you, um…” She shook her head, banishing the thought. “Do you need to go take care of that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!” He answered a bit too loudly, then took a breath. “I mean, no, I just need a minute.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suit yourself.” She smiled, hoping he’d see that she wasn’t teasing him. “If it were me, I wouldn’t be able to think straight until I took matters in my own hands, if you know what I mean.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s fine, it’ll go…” He stopped mid-sentence and looked at her curiously. “What &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; you mean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, tickling my fancy?” Jimmy still looked confused. “Beating around the bush? Buttering my muffin?” She grinned and waggled her eyebrows. “Rubbin’ my nubbin? Flicking the bean?” His expression made her laugh. “C’mon, &lt;em&gt;masturbating&lt;/em&gt;, man!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girls masturbate?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yeah?” It was her turn to look confused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” He hesitated for a long moment. “How?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jeez, man,” she hesitated. “Ask your girlfriend.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh, don’t really have a girlfriend.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, whatever you want to call it,” she rolled her eyes. “The girl you’re fooling around with.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked awkward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” she realized. “Nobody? Not even at your big party?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not even, like, a handy in the pool?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He cleared his throat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, shit, I’m sorry about that. But come on, didn’t they cover this kinda stuff in health class?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They were more focused on trying to scare us about pregnancy and diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right. But you’ve got the internet. You’ve never watched a girl masturbate in porn?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought all that stuff was fake.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re not wrong,” she conceded. “Well, don’t stress. You’re a good-looking guy who’s heading off to university soon. I’m sure you’ll meet a girl you like, and you can ask her stuff like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh!” Jimmy groaned. “That’s &lt;em&gt;exactly&lt;/em&gt; what I’m worried about! I’m gonna look like an idiot. I didn’t even know girls masturbated!” He turned abruptly to face her, accidentally flinging the pillow to the floor. “You gotta help me, Heather!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? Help you, &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt;?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Teach me about girls so I don’t humiliate myself!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather blushed. Jimmy’s erection was twitching shamelessly in his shorts, but his expression was guileless and hopeful. Once again, her mind drifted easily into imagining Jimmy gasping in her cleavage as she stroked his shaft…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um…” She blinked, trying to clear her mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, please! I really need your help. College girls aren’t gonna want to fool around with a virgin!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, wait, wait, slow down.” She stood up and pointed at him. “I am &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; hooking up with you. You get that, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that’s fine! Just show me some stuff so I don’t get laughed at.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just show you some stuff.” She considered. “Like, how a girl masturbates?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anything, Heather, please!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turned away from him. This was crazy. She should tell him to go take a cold shower. Then she could step outside and catch her breath until the embers of arousal in her core cooled down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand… He wasn’t wrong. He’d go off to college and meet some girl who liked him, and rub her the wrong way. Literally! Plus, if she showed him a few things, it wasn’t just helping him, it was like doing a favor to all the women he hooked up with in the future. She’d be paying it forward! Hell, it was practically her duty to her fellow women to show this poor clueless boy what was what.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” She nodded to herself and glanced at the clock. His parents wouldn’t be home for another couple hours. “Okay,” she repeated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just, like, give me a second.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached under her skirt, and shimmied her panties down. She heard Jimmy take a deep breath as she dropped them on the coffee table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, pay attention,” she said as she turned around to face him again. “No touching.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded as she sat down, facing him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And you can’t tell anyone.” He nodded eagerly, but she continued. “I’m serious! You can’t go tell your dumb friends, and you &lt;em&gt;definitely&lt;/em&gt; can’t tell my brother!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course not! I wouldn’t!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, then.” She leaned back on the arm of the couch and spread her legs for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, wow,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Quick anatomy lesson. These are my lips. If I spread them open like this, you can see the opening of my pussy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re wet…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. You’re not the only one who got turned on by the movie. When girls get aroused, they get wet, to make it easier for a guy’s cock or a girl’s fingers to slip inside. Don’t ever try to push anything inside a girl if she’s not wet, it’ll just hurt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, staring intently. His cock throbbed, and he absent-mindedly rubbed it through his shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, this is important, look here. Up at the top, where my lips come together? They make a kind of hood to cover this—ah—this little bud here. Do you see it? That’s my clitoris. When I get very turned on, it gets a bit swollen and pokes out. It’s &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; sensitive. You know how it feels good to rub your cock, like you’re doing right now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy looked guilty and moved his hand away, but nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay, I don’t mind, but listen… A girl’s clit is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; like your cock. If you try to rub her clit like you touch yourself, it’s too much. You’ll piss her off. You’ve gotta build up to that, make sure she’s ready first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I, uh,” Jimmy licked his lips, “know if a girl’s ready?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Honestly, you let her tell you or show you. Girls like it when you take your time. Don’t just give her a kiss and jam your hand down her underwear. Talk to her. Ask her how she likes to be touched. Some girls like a lot of kissing. Some will want you to touch their breasts. Others don’t want that at all.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, um…” His hand drifted back to his cock. “What do you like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” she purred, idly caressing her lips. “I like sitting in a guy’s lap, and rubbing against him. Especially if I’m wearing a skirt. Fuck, I love feeling his cock grow, pressing against me. And I like it when a guy touches me like this…” She slowly teased a finger between her lips, just enough to get it wet, and traced a lazy circle around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought you said,” he whispered, “not to start with the clit?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, but I’m already turned on. If I was sitting in your… I mean, a guy’s lap, rubbing against him, I’d be ready for a bit more direct… stimulation…” She trailed off, slowly rubbing herself as she watched him grind his palm against his erection. She wanted to see him. “Why don’t you pull that out? Show me how you touch yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yeah, okay,” he stammered. Quickly, he peeled off his shorts and boxers, then sat back down across from her, leaning on the other arm of the couch. His cock wasn’t bad to look at, she realized, as he wrapped his hand around the base and started slowly stroking the full length of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Once a girl lets you know she’s ready, you can go inside,” she purred, easing her middle finger between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How would she let me know?” His voice was husky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She might show you, by grabbing your hand. Especially if you’re already rubbing her, she might just push your finger inside. Or she might ask. She might say, ‘please, I need your fingers.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather shivered under his gaze. He was entranced. His eyes were locked between her legs, completely absorbed by what she was showing him. She felt almost as though he were worshipping her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to touch me?” She gasped, surprised by her escalation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really?” His eyes met hers, equally surprised. He seemed to be checking that it wasn’t a trap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, really. Here, give me your hand. Start by rubbing over… Mmm, yeah, like that. Slow, gentle pressure. You can kinda let your fingers ease between my lips, but don’t go inside just yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy gawked, one hand wrapped around his cock and the other caressing her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, now come up a little higher… Yes, now to start, don’t rub my clit directly, try rubbing all around it—ah—like that, yeah, every movement stim—oh!—stimulates her more, and then you can start moving closer—uh—and closer, until you—ah!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you like that?” Jimmy asked, earnestly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t ask a girl if she likes it,” Heather groaned. “That’s a turn-off. Just pay attention. Look at me—ah—right now. Listen to my breathing. See how I arch—oh!—my back when you touch me there? Feel me rolling my hips to meet your fingers?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Jimmy gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s how you know—oh, oh, oh!—but you also have to—ah!—know when to back off…” She gently pushed him lower, away from her tingling clit. “Now, I want your fingers. If you turn your hand like this… Yeah, you can slip your first two fingers in. Mmm. Some girls just want one finger. Some want two. Don’t do three or more unless you really know she wants it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’ll want to move your fingers in and out… Mmm, yeah, like that. Like having sex… Don’t overdo it. Start slow, but follow her lead. Watch how she—ah—how she responds. See how her body moves with you. If you pay attention, you’ll know…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy groaned, stroking himself faster, matching the pace his fingers were pushing into her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you make a kind of come-hither motion with your fingers—ah!—like that! You’ll feel a spot—ah, ah—that’s good, that spot feels good, and if you—uh!—kinda just strum it—oh!—like a guitar. Oh, that’s good, I just need…” She reached down to rub tight circles around her clit. “Ah!—like that, yeah, you’ll… make… me… Oh! Oh! Cum! I’m cumming…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heather clamped her thighs shut around Jimmy’s arm, holding him in place as she clenched around his fingers. She didn’t usually cum this easily. There was something about the situation, about having Jimmy’s complete attention. Her body seemed to bloom for him, like it wanted him to see everything she had to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Jimmy gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she moaned. Somewhat reluctantly, she opened her legs again, and gave him a nudge to pull out. The sensation made her shiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a moment, when she could focus again, she found Jimmy staring curiously at his fingers. They were glistening wet, and a string of her cream stretched between them as he spread them open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go ahead,” she smiled. “Taste it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grinning, Jimmy eagerly licked his fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I taste?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um… it’s like, uh… I have no idea how to describe it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ha! Yeah. It’s hard to find the right words.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, but, um, how…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do I know what my pussy tastes like?” Heather laughed as he nodded. “Come on, be honest. Have you never tasted your own cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, I guess I got curious once,” he blushed. “I didn’t really like the taste.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you go. Girls get curious, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a moment, neither of them spoke. The moment stretched, loaded with tension. Jimmy rested on his knees, gripping his throbbing cock, and staring at her with eyes full of lust. She gazed up at him, legs spread, pussy swollen and sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She should tell him they were done. He would respect it, she knew. No doubt, he’d go to his room and cum while thinking of her. She’d go to the bathroom to clean up, then wait for his parents to come home. And, then, to be honest, probably go home to her room and cum while thinking of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, she could let him do it here. She imagined writhing on the couch, rubbing her clit as he knelt over her, gasping and stroking his cock. His cum would arc through the air, falling on her thighs and pussy. She imagined his expression as she eagerly rubbed it into her skin, and then sucked her fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or she could finish what she’d started. Teaching him how to treat a woman. After all, the job wasn’t done. It’d be a bit rude to send him off without showing him how to slide his cock into her dripping wet pussy, to feel him thrust inside…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to keep…” she started to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can we keep…” he said at the same time, and they both stopped. A crooked smile spread across his face as he realized what she was about ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Jimmy, come here,” she gasped, and pulled him down on top of her. He made a surprised sound that was choked off as her tongue pushed between his lips. He awkwardly wrapped his arms around her and settled his weight between her thighs. She moaned as his cock pressed against her, hard as steel against her swollen lips, eager to part around him. She squirmed, trying to position him…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, she pulled back from the kiss, holding a hand against his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You. Cannot. Tell. Anyone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, yeah, no problem,” he agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she gasped. “Okay, let’s do this. If you get a girl good and excited, she’ll be eager for you. Like me right now. I want to feel you inside me so fucking hard…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy leaned forward eagerly, but she kept holding him away just a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If she’s as wet as me, you can just… put yourself against her opening… like this… and then—oh!—Fuck, Jimmy, I was gonna tell you when, but you’re already inside!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned, staring into her eyes, and shifted as if to start fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! No, wait, just—oh—just wait a minute. Give me a minute to adjust. I—ah—love the feeling when a guy first enters me, let me savor it. Oh my god, I can feel you throbbing inside me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she rolled her hips, encouraging him to start moving with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, like that, start slow. Oh, fuck. Don’t just start railing a girl, you—ah!—gotta build up to that, even when she’s as turned on as me. Oh god-damn, yeah, yeah, move with me, I—mmm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled him back into a kiss, moaning into his mouth as he followed her lead and started thrusting into her. Quickly, she escalated the pace. Every thrust, every time he bottomed out, she saw a flare of color out of the corner of her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He broke the kiss, and buried his face in her shoulder, fucking her harder and faster. She wrapped her legs around him, and held on as he moved with increasing urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wanted to tell him more. To get on top and ride him. She wanted him to get behind her. She wanted to show him when to pull her hair. When to push his thumb into her ass. She wanted him to &lt;em&gt;cum&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wanted him to cum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jimmy!” She gasped into his ear. “Are you—ah!—close?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he groaned. “Can I?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Oh, yes! I want you to—ah!—Cum in me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned and went rigid on top of her. She gasped at the feeling of his cock twitching, and the spreading warmth inside. After a long moment, he relaxed, and she ran her fingers through his hair, breathing softly in his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, Jimmy,” she sighed. “I think you’re gonna do alright with the ladies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tried to give her a kiss as he climbed off her, but she squeaked, shoving a hand between her legs as his cum leaked out. He handed her a tissue box, and she wiped up as he watched, fascinated. Mercifully, it had only dripped on the inside of her skirt, not the couch. That would have been hard to explain to his parents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy pulled on his shorts and followed her into the kitchen. She poured them each a glass of water. When she passed his over, his eyes sparkled with a mixture of gratitude and awe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she laughed, “don’t you look like the cat who caught the canary?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kinda feels that way.” He grinned, and took a sip of water. “You know, I was just thinking. Like, you’re home for a few weeks, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And I don’t leave for a few weeks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go on,” she smiled, knowing where he was going with this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, maybe you could show me some more stuff.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t get cocky, kid,” she laughed. “Girls like a bit of confidence, but too much can be off-putting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that a no?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean,” She bit her lip. “I &lt;em&gt;suppose&lt;/em&gt; there’s a bit more I could teach you…”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 1: Close Quarters: Only One Bed, Book 1</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/1-close-quarters/"/>
		<published>2024-08-03T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-08-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/only-one-bed/1-close-quarters/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="vacation sex" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-1-h7lrmsTSMe-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Emma couldn’t believe it. The tropical vacation she’d been looking forward to all year was here! After three years apart, she was reunited with her friends Zoya and Liam… Plus Liam’s handsome surfer cousin, Nolan. But now a problem with the reservations will force the four of them to share a room with just one bed. Will this be a disaster… or the start of the best vacation ever?&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0DC4K9MBG"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Can You Teach Me?</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/can-you-teach-me/"/>
		<published>2024-07-28T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-07-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/can-you-teach-me/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="phone sex" />
    <category term="dirty talk" />
    <category term="dancing" />
    <category term="clubbing" />
    <category term="public" />
    <category term="double penetration" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="mmf" />
    <category term="anal" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/can-you-teach-me-9oJNWSdbLe-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Sitting on the couch as a movie she’d barely paid attention to ended, Alice took a deep breath, gathered her courage, and turned to her roommate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Julie, I need to ask you something.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh?” Julie raised an eyebrow and set down her bowl of popcorn. “So serious!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um,” she hesitated, “my boyfriend is going on this work trip, so he’ll be out of town for a few weeks, and…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And he wants to try an open relationship?” Julie nodded knowingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? No, he wants to try phone sex.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Well, that’s no big deal. Kinda old-fashioned now that we have video calls, but you do you. What’s got you worried?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I always thought dirty talk was kinda dumb? Like, I don’t get how it’s sexy. Have you done it before?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My dirty talk game is &lt;em&gt;legendary&lt;/em&gt;. One time in college, I turned a straight girl gay with a single phone call.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really?” Alice looked skeptical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For real. When I hung up, she was a changed woman.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, um… Can you teach me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, but don’t blame me if you want to dump your man when we’re done.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think I’ll be okay.” Alice rolled her eyes. “I’m not some closeted coed looking to experiment, I just want some pointers on how to be sexy on the phone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay!” Julie grinned. “If we’re gonna do this, we need to do it properly, so go to your room and call me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We can’t just talk here on the couch?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! You won’t be able to see him when you talk, and if you’re looking at me, you’ll get self-conscious. Go get comfortable. Oh, and use headphones. You’ll want your hands free.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My earbuds don’t work, I put them through the washing machine. And what do you mean I’ll want my hands free?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Think about talking to your guy. If the mood strikes, you need to be free to touch yourself. You want him to hear how turned on you are, not fumbling with your phone.” Alice looked unconvinced, but Julie stood firm. “If you want me to teach you, take it seriously!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes later, after finding a spare pair of earbuds, they went to their separate rooms. Julie put on her headphones, fluffed her pillows, lay down on the bed, and answered her phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, so do I just start describing things I’m doing?” Alice sounded tense. “Or telling him to do stuff? Should I tell him what I’m wearing? That’s a thing, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice, slow down!” Julie laughed. “If you want this to work, you need to be relaxed and open to the possibility that it might be a good time. You sound like you’re trying to complete a checklist.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m just nervous! What if I say something dumb? What if he says something sexy, and I laugh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you worry about that when you’re with him in person?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then don’t worry about it here. All he really wants is to know you’re into it… Into &lt;em&gt;him&lt;/em&gt;. Forget about the phone or how silly you feel, and think about the way you would feel if you were lying next to him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.” Alice took a couple of deep breaths. “How do we start?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like any conversation. You don’t dive into the deep end. You ease in. Leave space for things to get hot, but don’t expect it to start there. You can try the whole ‘what are you wearing’ thing, but I’ll tell you what’s always worked for me: telling stories.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, like reading erotica?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, like sharing a story about something that happened to you. Maybe the story is about something kinda hot. Maybe, in the course of telling it, it gets you turned on. Maybe when he hears you getting into it, it turns him on, too. Just start slow, and see where it goes from there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if I don’t have any stories like that to tell?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take a real story and spice it up a bit. Hell, you could make something up completely, but it’s usually easier to build from something that really happened. Think about a moment you had with someone. Maybe you almost kissed, but didn’t. What if you had kissed? What would have happened next?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm.” Alice considered this. She sounded more relaxed, but still hesitant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me give you an example. You remember last week, the night I went clubbing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, you came home at three in the morning, climbed into my bed and got a little handsy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Julie grinned, “I get horny when I’m high. And I don’t remember you complaining.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“…Anyway,” Alice demurred. “Yes, I remember.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did I tell you what I got up to at the club?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You were mumbling something in my ear about making out on the dance floor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I did more than make out, but we’ll get there. I was wearing that short silver dress… You know the one I mean? Spaghetti straps, kinda twirly?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I remember last time you wore it out, the guys couldn’t stop staring at your nipples. They’d practically shove me out of the way to dance with you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I don’t like the way it looks with a bra! And I was on the prowl that night. So I was out on the floor, and I ended up dancing near this girl. Short blonde bob, red mini skirt, halter top, and fuck-me heels. She was looking at me, and I was looking at her. And she leaned in and said, ‘I love your dress.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll bet she did.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then the song changed, and suddenly the floor was packed. We were kinda pushed together, not that we minded, and things got steamier. She’s running her hands up and down my sides, getting closer and closer to my chest. There were people behind me, and they were bumping into me, pushing me closer against her. She finally ran her thumbs over my nipples and I leaned in and kissed her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right there on the floor?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We couldn’t have left if we wanted to, it was so crowded. I heard a couple of people behind me cheer, and she gave up trying to be subtle. Her tongue was in my mouth, her hands were on my tits, and her thigh pushed between my legs. The motion of the crowd was literally shoving us together. It was getting hot. I could feel sweat trickling down my spine. I grabbed her ass and squeezed her against me. More people cheered. I think everyone around us was watching.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s intense.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have no idea. I didn’t realize how much it would turn me on to know everyone was watching. The jostling of the crowd around us got more intense. I was fully grinding on her thigh and moaning into her mouth, and I wanted more. Would other people start touching us? I imagined feeling someone’s hand on my ass, pulling up my skirt…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” Alice said huskily. “How far did you go?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, security showed up when she pulled my tits out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She did?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I think she was getting carried away by the moment, just like me. I felt her push my straps off my shoulders, and pull my top down. Then she stopped kissing me and leaned down to suck on my exposed nipples. Everyone around us was cheering. I was fully leaning against some dude behind me, with my fingers tangled in her hair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s so hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was starting to see stars when I heard people protesting as two bouncers shoved their way into the crowd towards us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you get thrown out?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She did. They would have thrown me out, too, but I ducked around the big guy I’d been leaning on. He gave me a wink and stood in their way long enough for me to pull my dress up and disappear into the crowd toward the restroom.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’d you do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I was still panting from how worked up she got me. My dress was clinging to my body and my nipples were hard as fuck. My heart was pounding from a mix of adrenaline and arousal. I ducked into a stall and tried to catch my breath. I peeled off my thong, which was practically soaked, and left it on the floor. All I could think about was how far I would have gone with her if no one had stopped us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice said nothing, but Julie could hear her breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you touching yourself, Alice?” Julie whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh… What? No. Sorry, I was just…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay, that’s the idea. I’m telling you a story to turn you on. Did you squeeze your tits when she squeezed mine?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh… Don’t… What’d you do next?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I knew I couldn’t leave without finding someone to make me cum. I checked my reflection in the mirror. My dress was practically painted to my body. My chest was flushed, and my nipples were begging for more attention. I was buzzing with excitement to walk back out into the club, to find someone who looked at me the way she did.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes…” Alice purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t have to go far. Just outside the restroom, a couple of guys caught my eye. I don’t know if they saw me earlier, but they were definitely watching me now. I gave them a look and strutted back onto the dance floor, near the speakers. They followed, and soon I was dancing between them. We moved with the pounding beat. I felt their hands on my hips, my ass, my tits. The guy behind me was already hard and grinding against me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The guy in front of me pulled my hand to his package, and I felt him swelling under my palm as I rubbed him. He reached under my skirt, and pushed his thick finger between my lips. He was rough, but I was practically dripping, so he slipped inside easily. I gasped as the guy behind me pushed me against his friend’s fingers. I have no idea how obvious we were, I just knew that the bass was thumping, and we were moving together, and my vision was hazed with flares of pink and yellow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” Alice moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One of them said something in my ear. I don’t know what, but next thing I know, we’re walking out the back door to the parking lot. They took me between two parked vans. They got their cocks out, and one of them leaned against a van and lifted me up. I wrapped my arms and legs around him, and bit his neck as he entered me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What—ah!—did the other guy do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He got behind me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” Alice groaned in anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They sandwiched me between them. I screamed when he pushed his cock into my ass. It burned for a minute, but then they both started moving, and all I could do was hold on. Fuck, Alice, I’ve never been so full. Those guys fucked me like a team. They moved in sync. I dunno if they’ve done it before, but it was this constant wave of pleasure. I couldn’t tell where one ended and the other began. They thrust and squeezed and moaned, and all I could do was cry out and cum all over their cocks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Yes…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I came so many times. And then, when they were ready, where do you think they
came?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! In… Inside…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right, I felt them cum together. At the same moment, their cocks were throbbing, pulsing, filling me up. It was so hot. What about you, Alice? Are you ready to cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Alice squeaked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do you feel about dirty talk now? Are you ready to try? Want to tell me a story?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um, need to—ah!—I have to—uh!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice ended the call. A minute later, Julie heard her moaning loudly through the wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heh,” Julie smiled to herself. “Still got it.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 13: Zoya’s Plan</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/13-zoyas-plan/"/>
		<published>2024-07-14T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-07-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/13-zoyas-plan/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="doggy style" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="foursome" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Well, alright,” Zoya laughed as she closed the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was late afternoon, and she’d just returned to the hotel room to find Emma and the boys lounging on the bed in their underwear. Liam looked a bit sheepish, as if he’d been caught doing something naughty. Nolan met her gaze confidently. Emma put down her phone and stretched, her apparent confidence in her toplessness only slightly betrayed by the flush blooming on her cheeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I hope,” Zoya grinned, “you three haven’t been watching cat videos this whole time?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not the &lt;em&gt;whole&lt;/em&gt; time,” Emma winked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So what have you been up to?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing you wouldn’t do,” Nolan chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fantastic! Tell me everything!” She dropped her purse, kicked off her shoes and started undressing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The boys looked to Emma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she began, a bit hesitantly, “after you left, we started kissing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good place to start,” Zoya agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then, we were all touching each other. Over our clothes, at first, but, um, it got more intense.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I like the sound of that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam pulled down my cami to suck on my nipples.” Emma’s cheeks were bright red. “And I had my hand down Nolan’s shorts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Very nice.” Zoya bit her lip as she unhooked her bra. “Liam, will you show me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam hesitated for a moment, but Emma nodded, and he lowered his head to wrap his lips around her nipple. She sighed, running her fingers through his hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then—ahh—Liam lay on the bed. He’d been, um, touching himself, so he was hard, and I bent over to go down on him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What was Nolan doing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He lifted my—ah—skirt from behind.” Emma squeezed her legs together as Liam’s head moved against her chest. “He was touching me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Were you wet?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yesss…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan, why don’t you take off her panties,” Zoya suggested as she stepped out of hers, “and show me how you touched her?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He eagerly complied, and Emma lifted her hips to help. As he dropped her underwear on the floor, she spread her legs. Nolan slowly ran his hand up the inside of her thigh. Zoya climbed onto the foot of the bed to watch as he began gently caressing her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What next?” Zoya asked, excitedly squeezing her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He started to—ah!—fuck me…” Nolan had slipped a finger inside, and Emma was clearly finding it difficult to concentrate. “He fucked me from behind while—oh!—I sucked Liam’s cock.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s so hot,” Zoya purred, moving up to take Nolan’s place as he scooted down to the foot of the bed. “Did you love having your mouth full while getting fucked?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Emma panted. “I wanted—ooh—both of them at the same time…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya leaned up against Emma and kissed her deeply. The redhead squirmed and moaned as everyone touched her. Zoya broke the kiss and looked down at Nolan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you see what she tastes like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” Emma cried out as Nolan buried his face between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What happened then?” Zoya breathed into Emma’s ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I climbed on—ah!—top of Liam. Oh, shit, he—uh!—felt so good inside me… Then Nolan came around—oh!—and let me suck his cock!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so fucking sexy, Em,” she whispered. “This is turning me on so much. Keep talking. Tell me more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Oh, I—uh!—I knew they were about to… Oh! I climbed off, and—ahh—they stood over me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you beg them to cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Oh fuck, I said—ah—cum on my tits—oh!—cum on my face!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How did it feel?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hot! So hot—oooh—on my skin—uh—my lips—mmm—my mouth…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya fell into another kiss with Emma, pushing her tongue into her mouth. Liam switched to her other breast, making Emma squeal, until Zoya pulled him up to kiss him, too. Nolan did something that made Emma groan and roll her hips, as Liam and Zoya passionately kissed over her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya wasn’t surprised when she felt Nolan’s hand moving up her thigh. She pulled away from Liam’s hungry kiss and shifted her leg to give Nolan better access. Biting her lip, she encouraged Liam to kiss Emma, who was still panting with desire. Nolan’s wet fingers parted her lips and easily slipped inside, making her gasp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit, Zoya,” Nolan mumbled from between Emma’s thighs, “You’re so wet already!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve been thinking about this all day,” she replied, eyes fixed on Liam and Emma’s increasingly urgent kiss. Emma was making sexy little sounds and sucking on Liam’s tongue. He was gripping her tit and grinding his pelvis against her leg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya shivered and rolled her hips. Nolan’s long fingers seemed to reach impossibly deep inside. She looked down to find him staring up at her while he licked Emma’s clit. Meeting her eyes, he curled his fingers, tapping against her sensitive spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she growled. “Get up here, I want to taste Emma’s pussy on your lips…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They both got to their knees and met in a sloppy kiss. He kept rubbing his hand between her legs as she licked his lips. His chin, cheeks, and even nose were covered in Emma’s creamy juices, and Zoya savored the taste of her friend’s desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam, seemingly overcome with need, kicked off his boxers and rolled onto his back, pulling Emma on top of him. Nolan responded by pushing Zoya down on her back and diving between her legs. A moment later, she found out why Emma had been squirming so much. His talented tongue and fingers quickly had her clit thrumming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right, lick my pussy like that,” she purred, wrapping her hands around the back of his head and pulling him tighter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya watched eagerly as Emma moved down to kneel between Liam’s legs, taking his cock in her mouth. She bobbed her head, trying to swallow as much of his thick shaft as she could. When Zoya let out a groan at the sight, Liam met her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He reached out for her, brushing his fingers over her lips. She gasped, and he slipped his thumb inside, over her tongue. She closed her lips and sucked hard, absurdly turned on by his presumption, however accurate, that she needed something in her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They writhed together until Nolan wrapped his lips around her clit, and she cried out. Her insides clenched, eager for more than just his fingers. Liam groaned and lifted his pelvis to push deeper into Emma’s mouth, until she choked and sat up gasping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan had to jump back, releasing Zoya’s clit with a wet protest as she rolled away, practically throwing herself toward Liam’s momentarily unattended cock. Emma gasped as Zoya wrapped her lips around Liam’s head and sucked him into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, that’s hot, Zee,” she murmured, licking and kissing along the base of his shaft. “Yeah, suck his cock with me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya met her eyes as Emma encouraged her to take him deeper. When it was too much, she backed off, and Emma followed her up until they met around his tip. Liam moaned and a squirt of precum glazed their lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma made a surprised sound, and Zoya noticed Nolan standing behind her. He reached down to position himself, then grabbed her hips and pushed forward. Emma gasped, the motion pushing her head forward, lips sliding along the length of Liam’s shaft. She tried to keep kissing and licking, but was quickly distracted as Nolan started fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited, Zoya swallowed Liam until he bumped against the back of her mouth. He cried out and put a hand on her head, begging her to go further. Motivated, she tried to relax her throat, even as her jaw strained to accommodate his girth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma suddenly cried out and dug her fingernails into Liam’s thigh, making him grunt and thrust upward, pushing suddenly into Zoya’s throat. She choked and backed off, coughing and drooling. Emma’s red hair had fallen over her eyes, and she rested her head against Liam’s hip as Nolan thrust into her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watching this, Zoya had a moment of inspiration. She wanted to feel Liam’s thick cock inside her, and she wanted to watch Emma lick her pussy while getting fucked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giving Liam a quick kiss, she turned away from him and straddled his hips. Emma backed up a little and watched as Zoya lowered herself onto Liam’s cock. Carefully, she adjusted herself until she was leaning backward, bracing herself on Liam’s shoulders, legs spread wide, feet planted on either side of Emma’s arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Em,” she breathed, voice full of lust, “lick my clit?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck yes,” Emma moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fucking hell,” Nolan grunted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” Liam groaned as Emma licked up his shaft to Zoya’s clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuuuck!” Zoya cried out as Emma’s lips found her bud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam started urgently thrusting into Zoya. Emma did her best to keep licking, although Nolan’s increasingly forceful fucking made it difficult. Zoya found the position a bit awkward, but the sight of Emma’s face between her legs made her pussy clench so hard that Liam popped out, practically slapping Emma on the face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma squealed and laughed, but swallowed Liam’s cock without hesitation. Her eyes were closed, seemingly overwhelmed with lust as every thrust from Nolan pushed Liam’s cock deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya couldn’t stop, her climax was fast approaching. She reached down to rub tight circles around her clit as she watched her friend suck a cock between her legs. It was so fucking hot, she thought she might cum right on Emma’s face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” she gasped, “I’m so close!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma immediately slipped Liam’s cock back inside, rubbing and licking all over both of them. Liam grunted as he felt Zoya’s pussy squeezing around him. With Emma’s tongue on her clit and Liam buried deep inside, Zoya cried out as the pressure rose to a crescendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” Zoya screamed. “Em! I’m cumming! Liam! Shit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma squealed happily as Zoya’s climax gushed over her chin and Liam’s shaft. Nolan grunted in awe, then staggered backward, squeezing his cock and trying not to cum. Emma moaned in a mix of loss and desire, still licking and kissing. Liam’s fingers dug into Zoya’s hips, holding her tightly against him as the aftershocks rippled around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Liam popped out of her again, she climbed off with wobbly legs. As she lay on her back, holding her breasts and catching her breath, Liam got to his knees. His cock, throbbing and glistening with Zoya’s cum, jutted toward Emma, who eagerly turned around and bent over for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, Liam,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was already lining up behind her, and before she finished saying his name, he’d buried himself inside. They moaned together, then Liam started frantically fucking her, grunting as Emma met his every thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya looked at Nolan. He was still standing near the foot of the bed, eyes locked on Emma’s face, flush with ecstasy. His cock twitched in his fist, the head swollen and purple. She considered suggesting he step up and let Emma swallow him, but decided she wanted to feel him inside her instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan,” she murmured. He looked over, blinking, to find her beckoning him. Grinning, he stepped closer as she scooted her ass to the edge of the bed and wrapped her legs around him. He rubbed his cock along her dripping entrance until she hooked her ankles behind his butt to pull him closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he slipped inside. It was different from Liam, but equally delicious. Her lips were plump and swollen from her climax, and every movement sent a wave of stimulation flooding through her system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He leaned over her, taking her breasts in his hands as he started screwing her slowly and methodically. She arched her back and held on to his arms, hoping he wouldn’t cum too quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma was panting with every thrust. Her eyes were open, but unseeing, all her attention focused on the way Liam filled her, and her rapidly approaching orgasm. Liam’s eyes were screwed shut, and he was gripping her hips so tightly his knuckles were white.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma, you’re so sexy,” Zoya purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” Emma squealed. “Zee, I… Oh! I… I need…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me help,” Zoya urged. “Come here.” She scooted sideways, Nolan following her lead, until she was lying beneath Emma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck, this was hot. She was looking directly up at Liam’s swollen cock plowing into Emma’s pussy. Her friend’s clit was swollen and erect, jutting from her hood as if begging for attention. Nolan, clearly aroused by the position, started fucking Zoya harder. Little mini-orgasms radiated from her core, until her vision seemed to be hazed with pink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached up, grazing her fingers against Emma’s clit. The redhead stiffened, and cried out. Liam grunted at the sensation, and continued fucking as Zoya expertly pushed Emma to the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Oh! Ah! Fuck!” Emma collapsed on top of Zoya, voice muffled with her face pressed into Zoya’s hip. “Yes, Zee, please! Fuck me, fuck, fuck, fuck, Liam! You’re gonna make me cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Zoya breathed. “Cum for me, Em!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Ah! Ahhh!” Emma’s legs tightened around Zoya’s head, her entire body going rigid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, I’m cumming too,” Liam grunted. He slammed forward one last time, burying himself in Emma’s spasming pussy. Zoya watched, fascinated, as his balls tightened and his cock throbbed, pumping his cum deep inside. Emma moaned at the sensation, long and low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Liam backed away, Zoya squealed as his thick cum gushed out of Emma, splashing on her face. Without thinking about it, she raised her head and opened her lips to catch the rest of it. The mixed flavors of Emma and Liam’s cum filled her mouth. She moaned happily, swallowing and working her tongue between Emma’s lips to find more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, Zee!” Emma gasped and squirmed as Zoya licked and kissed and sucked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan moaned, and she felt him grab her thighs. He was close. She squeezed, encouraging him. Emma sensed it coming and raised herself to watch. Zoya imagined the view of Nolan’s pale white cock thrusting between her dark lips, and Emma salivating at the sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, fuck, I’m gonna…” Nolan grunted, and then slammed deep inside. She felt his cock twitch, and a sudden warmth inside, then he withdrew. Emma made a startled sound, and Zoya laughed giddily as she realized he’d pulled out to push his cock into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma, fuck!” Nolan gasped. Emma moaned with pleasure, and Zoya heard her gulping and swallowing as Nolan flooded her mouth with his cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overwhelmed by the thought, Zoya reached down to rub her clit. A moment later, Nolan staggered back, and Zoya gasped as hot cum fell from Emma’s mouth onto her fingers and lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, that was so much cum,” Emma gulped. Zoya moaned as she felt Emma licking her fingers. She pulled her hand away, and Emma enthusiastically licked Nolan’s cum from her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya returned the favor, licking and sucking Emma’s clit. Soon they were both moaning and gasping, pushing fingers inside, and swirling tongues. Emma stiffened and squeezed her thighs around Zoya’s head, and Zoya rolled her hips. They both surfed the plateau of arousal, squirming and writhing together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, Emma rolled away, gasping for breath and shivering with overstimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan was leaning against the bathroom doorframe with a crooked smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam was sprawled against the headboard, looking pleased and sleepy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughing giddily, Zoya sat up and raised her arms triumphantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Best! Vacation! Ever!”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 12: Emma and the Boys</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/12-emma-and-the-boys/"/>
		<published>2024-06-30T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-06-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/12-emma-and-the-boys/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="threesomes" />
    <category term="mmf" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="doggy style" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="facial" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The next morning wasn’t exactly awkward, but there was a noticeable tension in the air, like the pressure before a storm. Everyone was waiting for Zoya to make the next move. They were all fairly sure they knew what her big plan was, but no one wanted to jinx it by saying it out loud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everybody showered and dressed. They joked and laughed, but no one talked about the tension. They went out for coffee. No one mentioned that they’d all had sex. They did a bit of shopping. No one brought up what they hoped would happen next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For her part, Zoya seemed happy to leave them all in suspense. She would only say that she was going out for a special birthday lunch with her parents, and would return later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they got back to the hotel room, Emma couldn’t take it anymore. She followed Zoya into the bathroom when she went to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, Zee, spill.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm?” Zoya was distracted, arranging her outfit. “Spill what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s your plan?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told you,” she smiled. “I’m going to lunch, and I’ll be back in a few hours.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I mean, what’s your &lt;em&gt;plan&lt;/em&gt;? You’ve said you’ve been building us towards something, and last night was part of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; plan” Zoya laughed. “Nothing complicated. We’re all gonna fuck.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like, all of us at the same time?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s right!” She continued in a sing-song voice, “all together now!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve…” Emma hesitated. “I’ve never done anything like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, babe. That’s why I was so excited yesterday! You and Liam crushing on each other was perfect timing. I was already pretty sure Nolan would be down, but I thought the two of you were going to need some extra coaxing.” She shot Emma a raised eyebrow. “How was it, by the way?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was really hot,” Emma blushed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” Zoya beamed. “That’ll make it more fun tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, but what should we do while you’re gone?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever you want.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously, Zee, can’t you feel the tension out there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever. You. Want,” she replied calmly, while nodding approvingly at her reflection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You mean… like, me and the guys should do it without you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, that would certainly relieve some &lt;em&gt;tension&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, um… Huh.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;There&lt;/em&gt; it is.” Zoya stepped closer, putting her hands on either side of Emma’s face. “I know you’ve been fantasizing about this. Go get it, girl!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll be back later. Get them warmed up for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma melted into her arms as Zoya pulled her into a slow, sensual kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You got this, Em?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah. Yeah, I think so.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good, ’cause if I’m late for my own birthday lunch, Mum’ll never let me hear the end of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya exited the bathroom, with Emma trailing in her wake, still a bit dazed from the kiss. The boys looked up from their phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, lads, I’m off. Don’t do anything I wouldn’t do!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee,” Liam asked with a laugh, “what exactly does that exclude?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not much!” Zoya grinned and blew them all a kiss. “Have fun!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The door closed. Emma turned to face the guys. They regarded her with a curious expression, clearly expecting her to know what was next. She hesitated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan was sprawled across the bed, leaning against the headboard. He gave her a knowing wink that made her blush. As Zoya said, his calm, confident manner suggested he was down for anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam was sitting on the foot of the bed. He seemed a bit unsure, as if he was trying to gauge the vibe of the group now that they’d all hooked up. Still, there was an undeniable spark of hunger in his eyes when he looked at her. She bit her lip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she resolved. “Do you guys wanna have some fun?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you have in mind?” Nolan grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma held out a hand to Liam, and pulled him up. She beckoned to Nolan as well, who came to join them. Getting things started turned out to be easier than she thought. First, she kissed Liam. Then she turned to Nolan, lifting her head to kiss him while pulling Liam’s hand to her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He excitedly started caressing her breasts and ass from behind. When he started kissing her neck, she tangled her fingers in his dark hair even as she leaned into Nolan’s kiss. The tall blonde surfer brushed his thumbs over her nipples, causing them to stiffen under her cami.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached behind her, rubbing the front of Liam’s shorts as she turned, so the boys were on either side of her. They each took a breast in hand, teasing her sensitive buds until she gasped, breaking the kiss with Nolan. Liam’s cock was quickly swelling under her palm. Nolan nibbled her earlobe, letting his hand migrate down her body and over her skirt to press between her legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turning back to Liam, she leaned into him as he slipped his tongue into her mouth. Nolan was pushing up on her from behind, grinding against her ass, sandwiching her between him and Liam. She moaned as their hands continued to explore her body, touching her hips, her sides, her chest and thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, Liam tugged down her top, exposing her breasts. He eagerly sucked on her sensitive nipples, making her cry out. She shrugged her shoulders, encouraging the straps to fall off as his tongue swirled over her puckered skin. She squeezed her legs together as the smoldering heat in her core seemed to blaze into roaring flame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan continued moving behind her, kissing her neck with more intensity. She reached back, feeling for his cock. He groaned as she rubbed him, and fumbled to open his waistband so she could reach inside to grasp him directly. His breath was hot on her neck as he thrust into her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam sucked more of her breast into his mouth while clumsily stepping out of his shorts. Electricity crackled down her spine as he began rubbing his thick shaft. She squeezed Nolan’s cock harder and started stroking him at the same time, thrilled by the symmetry of the situation. For a moment, the three of them were moving perfectly in sync, surfing the rising tide of desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam released her breasts and staggered back to fall on the bed. He lay down, leaning on one elbow and continuing to stroke his cock for her. She licked her lips and quickly shimmied her cami down around her waist. Sensing what was coming, Nolan reached down to lift her skirt as she leaned forward. She braced herself with one hand on Liam’s hip, and grabbed the base of his shaft with the other. Nolan ran his hand up between her thighs as she swallowed Liam’s swollen head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan’s fingers teased and caressed between her lips, seeking her wetness. She trembled with anticipation as he moved behind her. Liam’s cock throbbed insistently against her tongue, and she sucked harder. She felt Nolan’s tip prodding, spreading her open, and sliding slowly inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His long cock seemed to reach impossibly deep. She moaned with Liam’s girth filling her mouth. Nolan grabbed her hips and started slowly fucking her. With every thrust, he pushed her forward. She swallowed, trying to take Liam deeper, until she had to back off. She gasped for breath and looked back at Nolan while rubbing Liam’s cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan met her gaze and started fucking her harder. She cried out each time he pushed inside, each time his hips slammed into her ass. Liam put his hand on the back of her head, and she looked up at him as he encouraged her to take his cock back in her mouth. Moaning around him with each thrust, she did her best, stroking up when Nolan pulled back, and swallowing deep when he pushed forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was her fantasy come to life. Nolan fucking her hard and fast while Liam lifted his hips to use her mouth. She squealed and grunted, digging her fingernails into Liam’s leg. He groaned, and with a handful of her hair, tried to go deeper. For a moment, he slipped into her throat, but it was too much, he was too big. She gagged, and pulled back, gasping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit! Mmmmm… Ah! Fuck!” She swore incoherently, wiping drool from her chin as Nolan continued fucking her. Liam’s eyes were filled with awe and hunger for her. Urgently, she climbed on the bed, letting Nolan slip out of her. She pushed Liam down and kissed him passionately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sitting back up, straddling his hips, she positioned him at her entrance. Quickly, she lowered herself, crying out as she did. His girth filled her more completely than Nolan’s, and she imagined herself blossoming around him. She closed her eyes and slowly rolled her hips, feeling his unyielding stiffness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You fill me up so good,” she groaned. Already, there were flares of color at the edge of her vision. The pressure was building quickly. She felt movement on the bed, and opened her eyes to find Nolan standing by Liam’s shoulders, cock bobbing wetly in front of her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck yes,” she blurted as he entered her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The taste of her pussy on his cock made her clench around Liam, who groaned and started lifting his hips to thrust harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit, oh yeah,” Nolan murmured. He put a hand on her head and started moving more insistently. She moaned and swallowed, surprised at how easily his long shaft slipped into her throat. Nolan gasped and gripped her hair tightly, until she choked and had to back up, panting and grunting each time she bounced on Liam’s cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam was cursing incoherently, eyes screwed shut, squeezing her ass and fucking her hard against him. Every time he bottomed out, she felt a flare of heat in her core. She looked up at Nolan, desperately stroking his cock right in front of her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, Emma,” he begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her insides were already starting to squeeze tighter around Liam. She was going to cum, and she wanted them both inside her when she did. Moaning, she wrapped her lips around his head, one hand around the base of his shaft to keep him from going too deep. He started desperately fucking into her grip and her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squirmed as the sensations built inside her. It was nearly overwhelming. The boys were both filling her, fucking her, wild for her. The flares of color merged into a pink and yellow haze as she cried out, muffled by Nolan’s cock. He thrust faster, wanting more, wanting to go deeper, wanting to cum in her throat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam was grunting and groaning, his fingers digging into her hips, slamming her up and down. His thick cock stretched her out, stimulating everything. She felt a gush of release, and a startled noise from Liam as she clenched around him over and over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan shouted and thrust forward, and she flattened her hand to take him deeper. Her eyes watered as she felt his cock throbbing and swelling in her throat. Her climax crashed through her body violently, loosening her limbs, until she felt as if she were only being held up by their cocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were close, about to flood her with cum. She wanted them to, but even more, she wanted to see it, to feel it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pushed Nolan away, coughing as he pulled out of her mouth. His cock head was a livid, swollen purple, glistening wetly in his fist as he stroked it, seemingly about to burst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With wobbly knees, she climbed off Liam, kneeling on the bed. His shaft was wet with her cream, and throbbing with need. He got to his feet, standing next to Nolan. They glanced at each other, then back at her, stroking urgently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was still gasping and flushed from her climax. Watching them getting ready to finish on her made her insides clench, already missing Liam’s girth. She squeezed her tits, rolling her nipples as she looked up at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” she gasped. “Do it for me. I want to see you both cum. Cum on my tits. Cum on face. I want to feel it, I want to taste it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan came first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cumming,” he grunted, leaning forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” She tipped her head back and opened her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan shuddered as his whole body went rigid. Thick ropes of cum fell on her face, splattering her cheeks and chin. She squealed with delight and grabbed his cock, pulling him into her mouth, milking the last of it. He cried out as her tongue swirled, and staggered back, suddenly too sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked hungrily at Liam, and reached up to touch her face, running her fingers through the cum. She couldn’t believe how turned on she felt. Her entire body was crackling with lust as she watched him tug on his cock. She licked her lips, letting some of Nolan’s cum run down her chin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, Liam, cum for me,” she growled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He stepped closer, pointing his cock at her open mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it,” she said, more forcefully. “Cum in my mouth!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Emma!” He groaned. His cum splashed onto her lips and tongue. He swayed with each powerful surge of his orgasm. She moaned happily, letting his cum drool onto her chest, where she massaged it into her tits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma knelt there for what felt like a long time, lost in her post-orgasmic haze. She felt triumphant, her fantasy realized. The boys lay side by side against the headboard, not touching, just catching their breath and watching her with awe in their eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit, Em,” Nolan laughed when she seemed to come back into herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She could only bite her lip and grin, still gently squeezing her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was amazing,” Liam agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was, wasn’t it?” She beamed at them both. “Now, I’m going to go rinse off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She walked to the bathroom door and looked back at the guys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you coming?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She laughed at how quickly they vaulted off the bed.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 11: Emma and Liam Take a Walk</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/11-emma-and-liam-take-a-walk/"/>
		<published>2024-06-15T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-06-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/11-emma-and-liam-take-a-walk/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="outdoor" />
    <category term="beach" />
    <category term="dirty talk" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;As the sun kissed the horizon, Emma pretended to shiver and scooted closer to Liam. He raised an eyebrow, but allowed her to pull his arm over her shoulders. The thinly scattered clouds glowed brilliant shades of pink and orange as they caught the sun’s last rays. They were sitting on a blanket spread out on the sand in the same spot where the girls did their sunbathing. She barely saw anyone there during the day, so she hoped for the same privacy at night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma wasn’t entirely sure how, but Zoya had convinced her to clear out of the hotel room for this stage of her grand plan. Something about the romance of sunsets. She laughed, remembering how Zoya had almost made it sound like she was doing her a favor by seducing Nolan in the boring old bed, while she and Liam got to explore “a new intimacy under the stars.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you chuckling about?” Liam asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Something Zee said earlier about sunsets being romantic.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, but she noticed his arm stiffen awkwardly around her. Zoya was right, Emma would have to make the first move.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the last sliver of the sun finally disappeared, they lay down to gaze upwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It gets dark so quickly here,” he remarked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s nice, though,” she said, laying her head on his shoulder. “We won’t have to wait long to see stars.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite that, the stars emerged slowly. Their conversation continued in fits and starts. She was nervous, trying to find a way to steer the evening out of platonic territory. He seemed uncomfortable, no doubt conflicted by her proximity after fantasizing about her just that morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She imagined Zoya sitting next to them, rolling her eyes and gesturing for Emma to go for it. Feeling a surge of confidence, she rolled onto her side, facing him, and put her hand on his chest. He glanced in her direction, then back to the sky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam,” she whispered. “I know you’ve been thinking about me.” She felt his heart beat faster. “It’s okay. I’ve been thinking about you, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you mean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, like, sexually.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? I…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shhh.” She put a finger to his lips, then started idly tracing her hand up and down his front. “I told you, it’s okay. I have been, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” She leaned closer, pressing up against his side. “Last night, when I was lying on the bed and Zoya was, um… Well, I saw the way you looked at me. I could tell you wanted to touch me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam’s heart was pounding. He licked his lips, unsure how to respond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I &lt;em&gt;wanted&lt;/em&gt; you to touch me,” she continued, with a bit more confidence. “I imagined you standing up, and rubbing yourself for me. I could tell it turned you on to watch her go down on me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he agreed, breathlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wanted you to come closer and stroke it over my face. I would have opened my lips…” She moved her hand lower. “I wanted to taste you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He inhaled sharply as she brushed against his growing erection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You were looking at me, I was looking at you, and Zoya was sucking on my clit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You told me,” he whispered. “That was hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It would have been hotter with your cock in my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, she pressed more firmly, feeling the outline of his shaft through his shorts. She leaned in to kiss him, but he squawked in alarm. She let go of his cock, but stayed pressed up against him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! I’m sorry! I’m sorry,” he gulped. “It’s just, um… What about Zoya?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think she’ll be okay with it,” Emma grinned. “This was her idea.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you mean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She told me how turned on you got in the movie theater when she was telling you about me and Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told her that I thought about you last night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And… I told her that I saw you masturbating in the shower this morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You did?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, sorry.” She bit her lip. “I forgot my phone, and when I came back, the bathroom door was cracked open.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god,” he groaned. “What did you hear?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I heard that you wanted me to suck your cock last night, which turned me on, since I’d been thinking the same thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It turned you on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It did. So much that I started touching myself, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s, um… That’s really hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was rubbing my clit when you started talking about cumming on my face.” She reached down to massage his erection again, and this time he didn’t stop her. “When you said you were going to cum inside me, I came all over my fingers. I barely had enough time to run out the door before you turned off the shower.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wow,” he moaned as she pressed more firmly against him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she purred. “That’s what Zoya said when I told her. I was worried she’d be upset, but she was excited.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really?” His eyes had a growing hunger in them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. She said she thought it was going to be harder to get us comfortable with her plan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“P-Plan?” He groaned as she reached inside his shorts to massage him directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s her birthday tomorrow. She said we should switch guys for the night. She &lt;em&gt;wants&lt;/em&gt; us to hook up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gasped, and she felt a squirt of precum against her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam,” she purred, brushing her lips against his ear. “Tell me again. Tell me what you want me to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” he panted, swelling in her grip. “Use your mouth…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” she breathed, squeezing tighter. “Say it like you did in the shower.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck! I, uh, I want… I want you to wrap your lips around me. I want you to suck my cock!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, she tugged the front of his shorts down and did as he asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit, that feels good. Your mouth is so hot!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock was thicker than Nolan’s, and it filled her mouth. She bobbed her head, working him deeper, wanting more, as he continued to talk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wanted to see you—ah!—swallow my cock while Zoya licked your clit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned as he throbbed against her tongue, and squeezed her legs together. Her lips felt swollen and slick, already excited by the thought of him inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wanted to push—ugh!—deep into your mouth while you came. I wanted to feel you moaning—aaah!—with my cock in your throat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was too much. She needed him. Quickly, she pushed his shorts down around his knees, lifted her skirt, and swung her leg over to straddle him. He gasped when he felt her wet lips against his shaft, and realized she wasn’t wearing any underwear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma!” He could only groan her name as she impaled herself on him. She had to brace her hands on his shoulders as she adjusted to his girth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she started rocking in place, savoring the way he filled her. He excitedly pulled up the bottom of her tank top, reaching under to squeeze her breasts, and trapping her stiff nipples between his fingers. The sensation, which seemed to travel down her spine, made her gasp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She dropped to kiss him, moaning as he slipped his tongue between her lips. His cocked throbbed and her insides fluttered. Her fingers tangled in his hair as he thrust upward, pushing deeper and making her see stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rocked back onto her knees, hands on his chest, taking control. He gazed up at her with lust in his eyes as she fell into a rhythm, rocking forward and back, grinding her clit against his pelvis. Already, she felt the pressure building. All the awkward tension between them had melted away, replaced with urgent need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You feel so fucking good,” he panted. “I’m getting close…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ask me again,” she urged him. “Like in the shower. Ask me where to cum…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck! I—ah!—Should I cum on your face?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped, imagining him standing over her, stroking his cock until hot cum fell onto her lips and cheeks, dripping onto her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Or should I—oh!—cum down your throat? Let you—ah!—&lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; you swallow my spunk.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She groaned, and her pussy tightened around him at the thought. She would roll onto her back, and let him kneel, pushing his cock into her mouth and deeper, until she felt him twitching, and could barely swallow it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Or, should I roll you over and shove—uh!—shove my cock deep into your dripping snatch? Fuck! You just got so tight! That’s what you want, isn’t it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She nodded frantically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look how much it turns you on! Oh fuck, Emma. Tell me. Tell me how badly you want it. Ah! How bad you want me to fill you up. Tell me—ah!—to cum in your tight fucking cunt!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she squealed. “I want it! Cum in me! Cum in my tight… fucking… cunt!” Her pussy clenched around his cock with each word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frantically, they rolled over, as he thrust urgently between her spread thighs. She felt his cock twitching and throbbing as a new heat filled her. He cried out and fell forward, face buried in her neck, grunting with each pulse. She held him tightly, savoring his weight on top of her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a long time, and with some reluctance, he rolled off her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” he gasped in surprise. “Look at the stars!”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 10: Zoya and Nolan Watch a Movie</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/10-zoya-and-nolan-watch-a-movie/"/>
		<published>2024-06-08T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-06-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/10-zoya-and-nolan-watch-a-movie/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="interracial" />
    <category term="indian" />
    <category term="desi" />
    <category term="titfuck" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Zoya looked up from her book as Emma returned from the hotel room. Without saying anything, the redhead dropped her phone and coverup into the bag and ran down the beach. She waded out chest-deep in the water, and splashed around a bit. After a few minutes, she walked back and sat on her towel, looking flushed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Found your phone, did you?” Zoya raised an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, under the bed,” Emma started. She was clearly bursting to say more, but stopped when she saw Liam approaching with his surfboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He casually kicked off his flip-flops, nodded to Zoya, and ran down to join Nolan, all while carefully avoiding looking at Emma, who was just as carefully avoiding looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya, mouth open with delighted surprise, stared at Emma, who was now blushing furiously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, did you guys…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!” Emma protested. “Well… kinda?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that why you ran into the ocean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I, uh, I might have needed to rinse off a bit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Zoya put down her book and sat up, giving Emma her full attention. “Tell me absolutely everything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So,” Emma started, “You have to understand, as I was walking back to the hotel room, I was worried I might find Liam still in bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why were you worried?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because I kinda can’t stop thinking about him? Like, sexually?” She hesitated before continuing. “Even while Nolan was fucking me, I was imagining Liam in front of me at the same time. Um, in my mouth.” Emma brought a hand to her lips, as though shocked to hear herself say it out loud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nice! Two guys at once is fucking hot,” Zoya winked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee!” Emma laughed, with obvious relief. “I was worried you’d be upset.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girl, what has given you the impression that I would be the jealous type?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fair enough.” She smiled. “So last night, when you, um, went down on me, I was looking at Liam, and he was looking at me, and there was, like, a &lt;em&gt;moment&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I heard you telling him what I was doing! How’d he react?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He licked his lips and watched me cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hawt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” Emma took a moment to collect herself. “That’s why I was flustered. If he were still in bed, it’d be the first moment we were alone since then, and I wasn’t sure how he would react. Or how I would.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, was he in bed?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, thankfully, he was in the shower. I grabbed my phone, but the bathroom door was open a little and I, um, realized he was masturbating. I told myself I should leave, but then he said my name.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ooh! Did he know you were there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, he was imagining me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He was describing how he wanted me to suck his dick. And then he started talking about how turned on he got watching me, and how he wanted to, um, to fuck my mouth while you went down on me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, Liam!” Zoya laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, I kinda started touching myself while I was listening to him. When he said he was going to cum inside me, I gushed all over my fingers. I had to run out the door before he turned off the shower!” Emma paused, tucking a strand of hair behind her ear. “Are you sure it doesn’t bother you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not at all.” Zoya grinned, wolfishly. This was all going better than she could have imagined. “I honestly thought it’d take a bit more coaxing to get you and Liam unwound.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Coaxing?” Emma laughed. “You sound like you’ve got a plan or something.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Em, tomorrow is my birthday, and our last night here. You better believe I have a plan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Emma laughed, taking a sip of water. “So what’s the next step in your ‘grand plan?’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re gonna trade guys,” Zoya beamed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma choked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hours later, Zoya was sitting on the bed next to Nolan. They were watching funny videos on his phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe you’ve never seen these guys,” Nolan laughed as he searched for another video to show her. “They’re hilarious. They’re Aussie, but I thought they were popular everywhere.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam, who was perched on the side of the bed, eating the last of his takeout dinner and half-watching the videos with them, nodded in agreement. Before he could say anything, the bathroom door opened and Emma walked out, wearing a short skirt and tank-top, and carrying her bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m going down to the beach for the sunset and a bit of stargazing.” She looked in Liam’s direction. “Anyone want to come with?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan opened his mouth to answer her, but before he could, Zoya draped her arm around his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m beat, babe. I’m gonna stay here and keep watching videos with Nolan. But Liam, you should go with her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam hesitated. He’d barely said a word to Emma all day, and it was clear to Zoya that he was feeling awkward about jerking off to her earlier. She blinked cheerfully at him, pretending not to see it. He looked back and forth between the girls, both looking at him expectantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah, sure, I’m in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Great!” Zoya beamed. “Have fun, you two!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they walked out the door, Emma grinned at Zoya, who blew her a kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she said, snuggling closer to Nolan and taking the phone from him. “I’m done with funny videos now. Let’s watch something else.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Nolan agreed. “What do you have in mind?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What kind of porn do you like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh… what?” Nolan stiffened as she loaded pornhub and pulled up his search history. “Wait, don’t…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His most recent searches were “Indian girl fucked,” “Indian girl white cock,” and “Indian girl facial.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh-ho!” Zoya sat up and held the phone out of reach as Nolan tried to grab it. She quickly scrolled further back, revealing much more predictable searches. His interest in Indian girls appeared to be quite recent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan!” She looked at him, delighted. “Did I give you a taste for brown sugar?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I…” Nolan stopped trying to grab the phone and leaned back against the headboard, struggling to think of a way to deny the obvious. “I mean, maybe you got me a bit curious?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Curious I can work with,” Zoya grinned. She scanned the search results and frowned. “But barely any of these girls are Indian. Look, she’s Latina, those two are clearly Asian, and this lady’s African. You’ll get better results if you search for ‘Desi.’” She updated the search. “There, see? Much better, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah,” Nolan agreed, looking at a screen full of brown-skinned girls with dark hair, all sucking or being fucked by white guys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ooh, that girl looks like me,” Zoya giggled, pointing to a girl getting a facial. “Let’s watch her.” She pushed Nolan’s legs apart, moved between them, leaned up against his chest, and pressed play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The video was shot from the guy’s perspective, sitting on the couch. A TV was playing in the background, and a gigantic bong was on the coffee table. The girl was kneeling between his knees, wearing only a purple bra, and sucking his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya squeezed her legs together and bit her lip. The guy was thick, and the girl was eager, but struggling to swallow his girth. She had one hand on his leg and one wrapped around the base of his shaft. She grinned at the camera every time she came up for air. The guy groaned as she pushed down, taking him deeper, and came up with a sound that was half a gasp and half a moan of pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan shifted awkwardly, and she felt him stiffening against the small of her back. She wiggled her hips to press against him encouragingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The girl in the video finally took the guy’s cock as deep as she could. He groaned loudly as he pushed into her throat. She held him for a few seconds, then pulled back, releasing him wetly, and panting for breath. He grabbed her shoulder and pulled her closer as he urgently pumped his shaft until thick ropes of cum shot out, coating her face and making her moan. The video ended with her licking her lips and grinning triumphantly at the camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan’s cock twitched against her back. Scrolling down, she found another video from the same girl and pressed play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time, the girl was wearing a silk top and her hair was tied up in a nice bun, as if she’d just come home from work and immediately pulled out his cock. Smiling eagerly at the camera, she unbuttoned her shirt to reveal a lacy yellow bra, both of which she quickly removed. She licked his already hard cock, getting it wet before nestling it between her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan inhaled at the sight, and his cock throbbed against her. She squeezed his leg and bit her lip, just as turned on as he was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the video, the girl squeezed her tits around the guy’s cock and started rocking up and down, meeting his excited thrusting. The girl watched hungrily, seemingly transfixed by the contrast of his pale cock emerging from her darker cleavage. At last, the guy groaned loudly, and she dropped to wrap her lips around him, swallowing happily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me,” Zoya breathed, “That was hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Nolan mumbled. “Um… Have you ever?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya dropped his phone and turned around on her knees to face him. He looked a bit flushed, and his erection was tenting his shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she grinned. “I have.” She declined to mention that most recently, she’d done it with Liam the night before. “Have you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he swallowed nervously. “Not with a brown girl.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God, yes, please.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Zoya peeled off her clothes as Nolan did the same. As he leaned back against the headboard, she kissed him passionately, then worked her way down his front. His cock twitched eagerly as she got closer. It wasn’t as thick as Liam’s, but it was longer. He gasped when she licked up the length of his shaft and pressed him against her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squeezed her breasts around him. Just like the girl in the video, she was fascinated by the sight of his pale cock disappearing and reappearing from her cleavage. He groaned, and a drop of precum appeared on the tip. She leaned a bit lower and licked it up, savoring the taste of his arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does this turn you on?” She looked up at him. “Seeing your white cock nestled between my brown tits?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, gripping the sheet and gasping with each thrust into the softness of her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want me try to swallow your cock like that girl in the video did? See my lips wrap around you? Watch me try to take you deep?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Zoya, please!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She immediately shifted to take him into her mouth. His cock was long, and she didn’t know if she’d be able to take it all. But that didn’t matter. Like the girl in the video, she made eye contact with him every time she came up for air. She gasped, a thick string of drool swaying between her lips and his tip. She went back for more, again and again, trying to take him deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He bumped against the back of her mouth, and she tried to relax, resisting the need to gag. She dug her fingernails into his thigh and he cried out, lifting his hips to push deeper. His cock slipped into her throat, and she moaned when her lips reached the base of his shaft. She felt him throbbing and swallowed, trying to keep him deep, until finally, she was forced to retreat. Eyes watering and panting for breath, she looked at him triumphantly. His cock twitched, and a few squirts of precum shot out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Want to see what an Indian girl’s pussy looks like?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, and she rolled onto her back, spreading her legs wide. He eagerly followed, lying down between her thighs and watching reverently as she spread her dark lips for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you’re so pink inside!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, yeah,” she laughed. “What color did you think you’d see?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t really think about it. I guess I thought you’d be dark inside, too. And you’re so creamy…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan,” she said huskily, “do you want to taste an Indian girl’s pussy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In answer, he buried his face in her. She squealed in surprise, and moaned as his tongue pushed deep inside. She ran her fingers through his long blonde hair, pulling him tighter. He eagerly lapped up all her cream. She gasped and squirmed as he sucked her lips into his mouth, then moved up to trace lazy circles around her clit. At last, he wrapped his lips around her sensitive nub and sucked on it until she cried out, clamping her thighs around his head. He didn’t stop until she pushed him away, gasping and squeezing her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had her eyes closed, but felt him settle his weight on top of her. She moaned happily and wrapped her arms and legs around him. He kissed her deeply, and she could taste herself. His cock bumped eagerly against her slick lips. She rocked her hips until his head slipped into position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, Nolan! Please, push that long white cock… ah!” She gasped as he did what she wanted. “Oh fuck, you reach so deep inside me,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan grunted into her neck and started frantically fucking her. She hooked her ankles behind his thighs, pulling up to meet him with every thrust. Her fingernails dug into his back as she held on, taking everything he could give her. She felt pressure building again, and saw light flashing every time he pushed forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, he pulled back, rocking onto his knees and gripping his cock tightly. Crying out with frustration, she reached down and started rubbing her clit, squirming as he tried not to cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Give me a second,” he gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” she protested. “I need you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just want to last a little longer.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You don’t have to, it’s okay!” She rolled over onto her hands and knees, face pressed into the blanket, as she continued rubbing her clit. She knew the sight of her wet pussy would remove his self-control. “Please! You can cum, just keep fucking me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he groaned, as he moved into position. He gripped her hips and shoved back inside with one hard thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She screamed, and felt her insides start clenching around him. As he started fucking her again, fireworks erupted behind her closed eyes. Her clit seemed to crackle with electricity, and every thrust sent nearly overwhelming stimulation through her system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya!” He cried out urgently. “I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Cum in me!” She felt him twitching as her pussy squeezed, pulsing in time with his throbbing. A gush of hot liquid washed over her fingers. Wordlessly, she groaned as wave after wave of pleasure rolled through her, leaving her unaware of anything except the way he felt inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They collapsed together, and for a long time, they lay there, spooning and catching their breath. He wrapped his arms around her, and nuzzled the back of her neck. She purred happily and squeezed his hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Best. Vacation. Ever,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No joke,” he chuckled. “Too bad tomorrow’s our last full day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My birthday,” she grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, no way. Happy early birthday! Sorry I didn’t get you anything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, you just gave me something pretty nice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ha! I guess I did.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A bit sticky, though,” she laughed. “But don’t worry, I’ve got an idea for a birthday present. Something the whole group can go in on together.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell you tomorrow.” She grinned.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 9: Emma Watches Liam</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/9-emma-watches-liam/"/>
		<published>2024-05-18T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/9-emma-watches-liam/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="vacation" />
    <category term="shower" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Everyone but Nolan had been a bit slow to wake up that morning. The blonde surfer had emerged from the bathroom rubbing his hair dry, announced that the surf was up, and they should all get out of bed. When no one moved, he’d laughed, called them all “bludgers” and thrown open the curtains to let the sunlight in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam groaned from the floor at the sudden light. Zoya, who was sleeping cuddled up against Emma, grumbled and buried her face in Emma’s shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Coffee,” Emma slurred. “Bring us coffee, if you’re so awake.” Nolan laughed again and walked out the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An hour later, coffees in hand, she and Zoya were changed into their bikinis and standing by the door with their beach bags. Liam was still sitting in bed, nursing his coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You guys go ahead,” he waved. “I’m gonna take a shower. I’ll catch up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shit, where’s my phone?” Emma muttered, rummaging through her bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Want me to try calling it?” Zoya suggested, already laid out on her towel in the sun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I always have it on silent.” She sighed and dumped the contents of the bag out on her towel and started sorting. There was a tube of sunblock, a water bottle, her wallet, a magazine from the airport, and assorted snacks, but no phone. “Ugh, I must have left it back in the room.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How do you forget your mobile?” Zoya laughed. “That’s like forgetting your arm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My bag got knocked over while we were all getting ready. My phone must have fallen out. I bet it slid under the bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you going back for it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” Emma hesitated. “I don’t suppose you want to come with me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, girl, I just got settled. Have a nice walk. Give Liam a pinch if he’s still in bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma looked hopefully down the beach for Nolan, but he was already paddling out into the waves. With a shrug, she pulled on her cover-up and started back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was being silly. There was no reason she should feel awkward about being alone with Liam. Besides, she probably wouldn’t even see him. He said he was going to take a shower. It would be fine. There’s no way he knew she’d been fantasizing about him last night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She blushed as she remembered the hunger in his eyes as he watched Zoya lick Nolan’s cum from her chest. Little did he know that if he had stood up at that moment, she would have swallowed him in a heartbeat. The thought of cumming with Zoya’s lips wrapped around her clit and Liam’s cock throbbing in her mouth made her shiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was strange to think of her childhood friend Liam in a sexual light. Not like Nolan. She had no history with him, and he was tall, charming, and friendly. From the moment she’d laid eyes on him, she’d wanted to climb him like a tree. When she went after Nolan, and Zoya went after Liam, it all felt natural.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yet, once the &lt;em&gt;idea&lt;/em&gt; of Liam got into her head, it was difficult to shake. She found herself thinking about what it would be like to be with him. Even while finally having sex with Nolan, she hadn’t been able to stop imagining Liam’s reaction if he saw her on her hands and knees. She’d imagined him kneeling in front of her, stroking his cock. Fantasized about taking him in her mouth while Nolan fucked her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, the idea that she might walk in to find Liam still in bed had her feeling a bit confused. What if she walked in, and saw his sheet tented over an erection? How would he react to her sudden appearance? Would he know, just from the look in her eyes, that she’d been thinking about him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did she want him to know?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shook her head as she approached the door to their hotel room, trying to think of something casual to say while she looked for her phone. She pulled her cover-up tighter, trying to hide the way her nipples excitedly poked through the thin fabric of her bikini top. Taking a deep breath, she opened the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To her great relief, she could hear the shower running. The bathroom door was open a crack, and steam rolled through the gap. If she found her phone quickly, he’d never know she was here, or wonder why she looked so flushed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She dropped to her hands and knees and peeked under the bed. Sure enough, there it was, over by Nolan’s side. She crawled around, reached under, and retrieved it. Triumphantly, she got back to her feet and was about to leave when she heard something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A moan from the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, shit. He was masturbating! She immediately felt foolish for imagining that he’d be waiting around to notice the confused lust in her eyes. He’d waited for them all to leave so he could get some alone time in the shower. He was probably thinking about Zoya, the beautiful girl who’d ridden him to climax last night, not his awkward redheaded friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another moan, this one almost sounding pained. Emma hesitated. Maybe he wasn’t jerking off. What if he’d slipped and hurt himself? If she left, and it turned out he was in pain, she’d feel terrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She should probably check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a quick peek, no harm in that. Just to make sure he wasn’t hurt. If he was okay, then she would just slip out, and he’d never have to know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peeking through the bathroom door, she could see him through the translucent shower curtain. He had his back to the door, and one hand braced on the wall. His legs were spread, and his other arm was moving—Okay! Emma backed away, blushing furiously. He wasn’t hurt, and she needed to leave now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh! She froze in place. A complex whirlwind of emotions threatened to overwhelm her. Guilt for intruding on something private. Pride that he was thinking about her and not Zoya. Shame that she was pleased about that. But mostly lust. Hearing him say her name while he rubbed his cock immediately flooded her with desire. She went back to the door, and quietly pushed it open a bit wider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Open your mouth,” he urged, and she did, from thrilled surprise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He must be thinking about last night too! Imagining her lying on her back, gazing up at him, while Zoya wrapped her lips around her clit. She pressed her hand between her thighs and strained to listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to feel your lips wrapped around my cock,” he said to his imaginary version of her. “Feel my thick prick in your—ahh—in your throat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She imagined how it would feel, his shaft filling her mouth, pushing deeper and deeper. She squeezed her breast with one hand, tweaking her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, yes, Emma, suck my cock,” he grunted, stroking faster. “That’s so hot seeing you—oh—swallow my cock while Zoya licks your clit. Ah! Does it turn you on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She nodded and slipped one finger under her bikini bottoms, teasing it between her lips to find her wetness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The way you looked—uh—looked at me while Zoya licked all the cum off your tits… Oh fuck, Emma. You’re so fucking hot. Your little nipples are so hard—ah—and your mouth is so hot!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip and pushed her finger deeper, coating it in her juices, starting to fuck herself. Her head was swimming with lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya couldn’t control herself when she saw you, she jumped up with my—oh!—my cum dripping from her pussy. You wanted more, didn’t you? When she pushed her tongue inside you, you wanted my cock, I could tell—ah!—You want my cock!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma added a second finger in her pussy, clinging to the doorframe. She was so juicy now, if the shower hadn’t been on, Liam would be able to hear how wet she was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Emma, I’m gonna fuck your hot mouth—ah!—fuck your tight throat—oh!—while Zoya sucks on your clit—ah!—and makes you cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearly overwhelmed, she dropped to her knees and shoved her other hand down the front of her bikini, frantically rubbing her clit while she fucked herself. Her mouth hung open as she imagined swallowing Liam’s cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want me to cum?” His voice was getting more urgent. “Should I cum on your face?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped, thinking of his hot cum on her skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Or should I—uh!—cum down your throat? Will you swallow my spunk?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She nodded, licking her lips and gasping for air, desperately imagining his cum flooding her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Or should I—ah!—spin you around and shove—uh!—shove my cock into your dripping snatch? Fuck! Emma! That’s what you want, isn’t it? Look how excited you are—ah!—for me to fuck you. Oh! Shit! Fucking tell me, tell me how bad you want it. Ah! Ah! Tell me to cum in your tight fucking cunt!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, cum,” she whispered. “Cum in my… tight… fucking… cunt!” Her pussy clenched with each word, and her juices flowed freely, dripping onto the carpet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma!” Liam grunted, arching his back and thrusting repeatedly as he fucked his fantasy of her. “Fuck! I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cumming,” she breathed in agreement, rocking in place. “I’m cumming too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam groaned over and over. Emma tried not to moan, watching his body strain. If he turned around right now, he’d be able to see her, kneeling on the floor, climaxing along with him. The thought caused a series of aftershocks to radiate out from her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he finally relaxed, dropping his head and leaning into the spray, she shakily got to her feet. Looking around for something to clean up with, all she could find was one of Nolan’s t-shirts. She stepped away from the door and wiped her dripping cum from her thighs and fingers. Quickly tucking it back into his dirty laundry bag, she grabbed her phone and ran for the door, hearing the shower turn off just as she closed it behind her.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 8: Zoya and Liam Go All The Way</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/8-zoya-and-liam-go-all-the-way/"/>
		<published>2024-05-13T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/8-zoya-and-liam-go-all-the-way/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="titfuck" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="cum on tits" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;After Emma kissed her and rolled away to have sex with Nolan, Zoya lay on her back trying to catch her breath. That sexy little redhead had really gotten her going. Her heart was pounding, and she was already wet. Not that it took much. She’d been in sexual overdrive since they arrived. So when Emma’s new take-charge attitude targeted Zoya, even just for a moment, it left her a bit weak in the knees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, quietly, she moved to Emma’s side of the bed and peeked over. She and Nolan were already making out, and she had his cock growing in her hand. Zoya bit her lip, and for a moment, considered just watching the two of them again. It would be so hot to see Emma’s face while Nolan fucked her. But seeing Liam’s face when she let him cum inside her would be even hotter. And if things continued on their current trajectory, she’d get to see plenty more of Emma’s O-face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited, she rolled back over to her side of the bed and peeked over at Liam. He’d slept through the last two nights of sexual activity, but today she’d let him know what had been happening. She’d also suggested that she might be open to having sex tonight. There was no way he’d be asleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, he was wide awake, lying on his back and looking up at her. She grinned, and with exaggeratedly slow, quiet movements, got out of bed to lie next to him. He opened his mouth to say something, but she pressed a finger to his lips. Shaking her head, she gestured toward the other side of the bed, letting him think they had to stay quiet so Emma and Nolan wouldn’t hear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled his covers off, and helped him remove his t-shirt and boxers. He was already mostly hard, and she eagerly moved to straddle him. He looked surprised when her bare pussy touched his cock and he realized she wasn’t wearing any underwear. She rolled her hips a bit, mashing against him, feeling him get harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moved to unbutton her shirt, and paused, raising an eyebrow at him, as though she were asking if he wanted her to take it off. He nodded eagerly, and she gave him a little lap dance as she teased him by undoing every button slowly, even though she could pull the whole thing over her head if she wanted. By the end, his cock was fully erect and throbbing under her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He reached for her chest and she leaned forward, putting a hand on either side of his head. He massaged her breasts gleefully. She shifted her weight to press one into his face, and he eagerly sucked on her nipple. His cock twitched, and she rolled her hips to grind against him as he switched sides. She loved the effect her body had on the men she allowed in her bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But she knew something that would really get him excited. Slowly, she pulled away, his obvious disappointment quickly turning to excitement as she knelt between his legs. He watched with wide eyes as she licked up the length of him, wrapped her lips around his head, and took him as deep as she could. Then she released him, and pressed his glistening cock between her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guys fucking loved this. As long as they were wet enough, she didn’t mind. The sight of a hard cock emerging from her cleavage was pretty sexy, she had to admit. Liam stifled a groan and lifted his hips, humping against her chest. She squeezed her breasts around him, awkwardly using the tips of her fingers to keep him in position. Every time he thrust up far enough, she kissed his tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a couple of minutes of this, he was going crazy, and her breasts were covered with lubrication, a mix of her drool and his leaking precum. Finally, she got bored with the game, let go of her breasts and took him into her mouth. He gasped as she swallowed him deeper and deeper until her eyes were watering, only backing off when his cock twitched in her throat and she almost choked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She climbed back up to straddle him again, gasping and excited. He gazed at her with pure desire, as she wiped her mouth and rubbed the wetness into her breasts. She shifted her hips until his cock was nestled between her lips, and slowly slid up and down the length of him, covering him in her wetness. He bit his knuckle, trying not to loudly moan at the sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She placed one hand on his shoulder, bracing herself, and reached down to position him against her opening. He gasped as she slowly lowered herself onto him. She felt her pussy blossom as his bulbous head spread her open. His girth filled her as she took him deeper, until at last she rested on top of him. He felt delicious inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled his head to her breast, just to give him something to focus on while she savored the feeling. She loved this moment. The first time you allowed a guy’s cock to fill you. It never stopped being good, but the first time with a guy was something special. She rocked her hips a bit, experimenting with the angle, and gasped as he twitched inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she sighed happily and moved back up to a sitting position. She stretched her arms and rolled her neck. Liam squirmed and tried to lift his hips to fuck her, but she wouldn’t let him move yet. From this angle, the head of his cock pressed forward, in a way that she knew would feel incredible when she started riding him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sensed some motion, looked to her side, and was pleasantly surprised to see Nolan across the bed staring at her. He was kneeling behind Emma, about to start fucking her, but had been startled to see her pop up. She licked her lips and nodded, giving him permission to look at her while he fucked Emma. He didn’t hesitate, immediately gripping her hips and thrusting forward. She heard Emma’s moan muffled in the pillow and grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked down at Liam, and once again held her finger to her lips as she started moving her hips. He nodded frantically, caressing her thighs as she started to fuck him. She looked back to Nolan, and squeezed her breasts for him, rolling her nipples between her fingers. He continued thrusting urgently into Emma, who was now squealing loudly, the pillow barely muffling the sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam let out a soft groan, and she looked back down at him. He was staring up at her with lust in his eyes. There was no way he couldn’t hear Emma. Did it turn him on to know she was getting fucked on the other side of the bed?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya moved faster, starting to bounce on his cock. He let out a strangled cry, and she leaned forward to cover his mouth, which only seemed to turn him on more. He started to thrust up to meet her with every bounce, urgently trying to fuck her harder. She leaned down and kissed him deeply, moaning into his mouth as his cock twitched repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your cock fills me up so good,” she purred. “Don’t finish yet, I want to cum on you first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and closed his eyes, gritting his teeth and trying to hold out. She got back up and started rubbing her clit. Nolan was still staring. She let him see how turned on she was. Pressure was building quickly now. Nolan grunted and fucked Emma, now crying out with every thrust. Zoya’s fingers moved frantically over her sensitive bud, and she rolled her hips, trying to press Liam’s cock against the spot that made her see colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan groaned, loudly. She couldn’t see Emma, but it sounded like she was sucking on her fingers, which made Zoya’s pussy clench. Fuck, she was so close. Her entire body seemed to be crackling with electricity. Her clit was swollen and needy under her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” Nolan gasped, “where?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on my tits,” Emma begged, spinning around to kneel in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam groaned when he heard this and squeezed her hips. She watched as Nolan started pumping his cock, about to cum all over Emma’s pale white breasts. Zoya wanted badly to suck on them. She wanted to lick Nolan’s cum off those little pink nipples. The thought pushed her over the edge. She closed her eyes and shook as an orgasm surged through her body. She felt a gush of hot liquid around the base of Liam’s cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let out a strangled cry and came at the same time. His cock throbbed and twitched as he pumped all his cum into her hungry pussy. She rocked in place, squeezing her breasts. Flares of color erupted behind her eyelids as her insides clenched over and over, trying to pull Liam deeper, to possess him completely. Waves of pleasure rolled through her nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened her eyes to find both Nolan and Emma watching her cum. She gasped and grinned at them, drunk with pleasure. Nolan groaned, and his cock exploded, shooting spray after spray of thick, sticky cum onto Emma’s chest. The redhead squealed and pinched her nipples. Liam’s cock twitched and slipped out, making Zoya shiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without thinking about it, she found herself climbing onto the bed, laughing and pulling Emma up with her. She pushed her friend onto her back and fell forward, eagerly licking up Nolan’s cum. Emma squealed as she sucked on her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, you two are hot,” Zoya purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Oh god,” Emma moaned, frantically rubbing her clit. “You’re gonna make me cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya loudly slurped up every bit of Nolan’s cum that she could find. He had a strong taste, but she was so aroused she didn’t mind. When she couldn’t find any more cum, she moved down Emma’s body, pushing her fingers out of the way to wrap lips around her swollen clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Liam,” Emma moaned. “She’s sucking on my clit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing that Emma and Liam were looking at each other while she went down on Emma turned her on even more. She looked up into Nolan’s eyes, who was watching and rubbing his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Ah!” Emma squirmed and bucked as Zoya flicked her tongue against her clit. “I’m cumming, I’m cumming, I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The redhead’s pussy started contracting repeatedly, and Zoya slipped two fingers inside to give her something to squeeze. She stared at Nolan, the taste of his cum and Emma’s mingling on her tongue. The thought that both boys were watching her make Emma cum made her insides clench, pushing Liam’s cum out of her pussy. She gasped, releasing Emma’s clit, as the sticky fluid dripped down her thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma laughed deliriously, squeezing her legs together as the aftershocks rolled through her system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya sat up on her knees, and licked Emma’s cream from her fingers. She looked back at Liam, and then at Nolan. Both looked stunned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You boys gonna be alright?” Zoya asked, carefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They glanced at each other, and quickly looked back at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, for sure,” Nolan murmured with a crooked smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh, all good,” Liam stammered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fantastic!” Zoya grinned at them both. “Because this vacation isn’t over yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She climbed to her feet, pulling Emma, still giggling, up with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, Em, let’s grab a shower and give the boys some space.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, night-night, boys!” Emma laughed and blew them a kiss as Zoya pulled her into the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 7: Emma and Nolan Go All The Way</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/7-emma-and-nolan-go-all-the-way/"/>
		<published>2024-05-11T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/7-emma-and-nolan-go-all-the-way/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="cum on tits" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“I’ve decided you’re right, Zoya.” Emma was walking arm-in-arm with her friend on the beach. The rain had finally cleared up, and the four of them were walking back to
the hotel from the beachfront taco stand where they’d had dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Naturally,” Zoya grinned. “What am I right about this time?” She shielded her eyes against the sunset and squinted ahead to where the boys had run off, like puppies with too much energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“About vacation flings, and doing what feels right, and not overthinking things.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Excellent! So, what are you trying not to overthink?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m going all the way with Nolan tonight,” Emma grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, great minds think alike! I decided to let Liam fuck me tonight, too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Emma giggled. “Was that before or after the movie?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, was there a movie playing?” Zoya laughed. “I didn’t notice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew it! When you headed off to the back of the theater, I knew you two were going to fool around.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about you two?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, we made out a little, and he put his hand up my shirt, but there were people sitting near us, and I was too nervous to do anything more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should have sat in the back, like us. As soon as the lights turned out, I started whispering in his ear and rubbing his cock. I told him how turned on I’ve been since watching you and Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You told him?” Emma blushed. “I feel like I should be mad, but…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, you want to know how he reacted?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” Emma laughed. “Is that weird? I’m not used to thinking about Liam that way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not weird! And judging by how hard he got, he’s got no problem thinking of you that way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think that might’ve had more to do with you than me, but go on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All I know is the way he begged me to suck his cock left me dripping. As soon as I swallowed, I hitched up my skirt and told him to finger me while I rubbed my clit. I came almost as fast as he did.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Zoya!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s what he said!” she laughed. “I told him I’d think about it, but really, I’d already made up my mind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait,” Emma frowned. “Tonight, when I climb down to have sex with Nolan…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll also be getting down to ride Liam.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, we’ll both be having sex on the floor on opposite sides of the bed? That seems silly. If we’re not trying to keep it secret anymore, why don’t we just use the bed?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t think the boys are &lt;em&gt;quite&lt;/em&gt; ready to do it together,” Zoya grinned. “But I bet we’ll get them there before this trip is over. For tonight, keep pretending like you don’t want me or Liam to hear.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re thinking about it, aren’t you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re imagining all of us having sex on the bed at the same time. Maybe you and I are touching a little? Maybe I’m sucking on your nipples while the boys fuck us both?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sounds like you’re the one who’s thinking about it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I definitely am. Best. Vacation. Ever!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they got ready for bed, it was unclear to Emma how much the boys were aware of the sexual tension in the room. She caught a few flirty looks from Nolan, and she spotted Liam watching Zoya hopefully, but otherwise they stuck to their normal routines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For her part, the anticipation was exciting. She and Zoya had a whispered conversation in the bathroom about what to wear. In the end, she wore Zoya’s satin nightie again, with no underwear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why bother with panties?” Zoya quipped, buttoning up her nightshirt. “I’m not. You’re just gonna get them wet and take them off. Save yourself the trouble.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting into bed meant walking past Nolan, who was already lying down. She got a thrill out of giving him a wink and letting him have a peek up her nightie as she climbed under the covers. He licked his lips hungrily, which made her blush, but also caused a flutter of desire in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya turned out the light and got into bed beside her, eyes glinting with excitement. Emma felt like she was vibrating with nervous energy. Zoya gently tucked a strand of red hair behind Emma’s ear and reached under the covers to squeeze her hand. She appreciated the encouragement, but this time she didn’t need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following an impulse, Emma leaned forward and kissed Zoya. Her friend seemed surprised, but quickly melted into the kiss. Emma quietly moved closer, tangling their legs together. She teased her tongue between Zoya’s lips, and the kiss became more passionate. Zoya squirmed and grabbed Emma’s ass, pulling their bodies together. At last, Emma playfully bit Zoya’s lower lip and rolled away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peeking over the edge of the bed, she was pleased to see Nolan gazing up at her. He’d already kicked his sheet off, and was idly rubbing himself through his boxers. Emma waggled her eyebrows at him and gestured with her chin for him to take them off. He did so, revealing that he wasn’t quite hard yet. Emma was eager to feel him get turned on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She slipped out of bed and dropped to lie along his side. She wrapped her hand around his cock and let herself be pulled into a kiss. Unable to resist comparing, she noticed that his lips weren’t as soft as Zoya’s. His stubble rubbed against her in a way that wasn’t unpleasant. He seemed more urgent, almost demanding, in the way he kissed her, sucking on her bottom lip. She realized with some surprise that while she was excited to have sex with him, he wasn’t as good a kisser as Zoya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She broke away from the kiss so she could look down at his cock rapidly stiffening in her hand. It pulsed with his heartbeat as she massaged it to life. Nolan sucked on her neck, panting a bit as she started stroking harder, rubbing her palm up and down the full length of his shaft. When she saw the first drop of precum appear, she didn’t hesitate to move down and lick it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she took him into her mouth, he gasped and lifted his hips, wanting more. She pushed him down, wanting to be in control. Slowly, methodically, she started bobbing her head, taking him a little deeper each time, until he was bumping against the back of her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While she was doing that, her free hand was busy between her thighs. She spread her lips, and dipped her fingers. It felt good to spread her creamy wetness over her lips. She teased her clit as his cock throbbed in her mouth, and imagined how good it would feel to guide him inside. She gave him one last suck and released him, leaving him hard and wet and desperate for more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma rolled onto her back, spreading her legs and pulling his arm so he’d roll on top of her. She reached down and guided his erection to slide against her. She gasped as he settled his weight between her thighs. He rocked in place, grinding his pelvis against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suck on my nipples,” she breathed. He scooted a bit lower and eagerly slipped the skinny straps off her shoulders, pulling the front of the nightie down to expose her chest. She felt her insides clench as he pulled her breast into his mouth. Sparks danced down her spine as his tongue flicked against her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His weight felt so good between her legs as he continued to grind against her. She squirmed, dripping with arousal as his cock prodded her bottom. He switched back and forth between her nipples, squeezing one and licking the other. She ran her hands over his shoulders and through his hair, full of excitement for what was about to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan,” she gasped, “I want you inside me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” He looked up, still squeezing her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she urged, pulling him up, and reaching down to position his head between her lips. “Please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan didn’t hesitate, slipping inside easily. He grunted, and she inhaled as he suddenly filled her. He lowered himself onto his elbows, buried his face in her shoulder and kissed her neck. She wrapped her legs around him, holding him in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your pussy is so hot,” he breathed in her ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immediately, he started moving. She held on, digging her fingernails into his back as he thrust with increasing passion. He sucked harder on her neck. She knew he was going to leave a mark, but didn’t care. He was deep, and with each thrust, he seemed to go deeper. She squeezed, clenching her pussy around him, and Nolan groaned into her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tangled her fingers in his hair and pulled him roughly into a kiss. Suddenly, his urgent kissing felt right, and his rough stubble didn’t bother her so much. Eagerly, she sucked on his tongue when he pushed it between her lips. Flares of colored light were dancing at the edge of her vision with each thrust, but abruptly he pulled away, rocking back on his knees and slipping out of her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He held up his hand, indicating that he needed a minute. She watched, fascinated, as he gripped his cock tightly, as though trying to restrain it. He grimaced, like he was holding something back, and his cock twitched several times in his hand. Despite how tightly he was squeezing, a squirt of precum dripped down his fingers. A moment later, he relaxed his grip and grinned at her. She got up on her knees and leaned in to whisper in his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Was that for me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I was about to cum. You feel so good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want it,” she breathed, feeling a surge of excitement. “I want you to cum for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I will, I just didn’t want to be done so fast.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get behind me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Emma dropped to her hands and knees. Nolan moved forward, and she gasped as he rubbed his cock against her until he found her opening and pushed back inside. This was her favorite. When a guy was behind her, something about the angles worked better. It felt like they could reach deeper, and every movement stimulated her more. She could usually come like this, especially if she rubbed her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan grabbed her and started thrusting. It felt delicious. She buried her face in his pillow to avoid making any noise. For a moment, he froze, as if startled by something, but then he started fucking her harder. She tried not to squeal as he squeezed her hips tighter, driving toward his climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a minute, she couldn’t hold her noises in anymore, and just hoped the pillow was muffling her cries of pleasure. Zoya would probably hear her and approve, or even egg her on, wanting her to get louder. Could Liam hear her? She imagined looking up over the bed and seeing Liam watching her, mouth open in shock. She did squeal, then, as her cunt clenched tightly around Nolan’s cock. He grunted and kept fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pictured Liam sitting before her, furiously masturbating to the sight of her getting fucked. Panting with each thrust, she got up on her hands again. She imagined Liam coming closer, rubbing his cock in front of her until neither of them could resist. Suddenly desperate for something to suck on, she shoved two fingers in her mouth, pushing deep and wishing it was Liam’s cock. She imagined him using her mouth as eagerly as Nolan was using her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan groaned, much louder than she expected, and for a moment, she wondered if he knew about her fantasy, and it was getting him off, too. She moaned around her fingers as his cock swelled inside her. She knew he was close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” he gasped, “where?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited, she spun around, popping him out of her. She knelt in front of him and looked up as he started stroking his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cum on my tits,” she urged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan looked down at her, eyes full of lust. Then he glanced to the side. She followed his gaze and saw Zoya, clearly riding Liam, who was hidden by the bed. Zoya had her tits in her hands and bounced in place, eyes closed, mouth open in ecstasy. Emma couldn’t tell if she’d just cum or was about to. She heard Liam make a strangled sound, and Zoya let out a long, low moan as she froze, absorbed in the sensation of Liam cumming inside her. She opened her eyes, saw Emma and Nolan watching, and grinned happily at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan grunted and Emma felt the first hot splash of cum on her chest. He was staring at her again and frantically stroking his cock. She squealed as his body rocked in place, shooting cum all over her breasts. The wanton look in his eyes made her insides clench repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, Nolan collapsed onto his back, still holding his cock and panting as the last of his orgasm rolled through his body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma leaned against the bed, head swimming with arousal. She squeezed her nipples, sending lightning crackling through her system. Before she could decide to ask Nolan to help her cum, she felt Zoya climb onto the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her friend laughed and pulled her up to lay on her back. She gasped as Zoya immediately began licking all the cum from her chest. Emma reached between her legs and found her clit, swollen with need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, you two are hot,” Zoya mumbled around her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Oh, God, you’re gonna make me cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma looked down, and saw Nolan sitting up, watching the two of them with awe in his eyes. She spread her legs so he had a better view of her pussy and started rubbing tight circles around her clit. Zoya continued, loudly slurping up all of Nolan’s cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked to the other side of the bed and wasn’t surprised to find Liam watching as well. The hunger she saw in his eyes made her shiver with excitement. She couldn’t believe Liam was looking at her like that, watching his two friends writhe on the bed. She rubbed her clit faster and moaned as she remembered her fantasy. If Liam stood up right now with an erection, she would eagerly swallow him. She wondered if he could see how turned on she was by the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya, having apparently licked up all the cum, started moving down Emma’s body, kissing her stomach, licking her hips, nuzzling her hand out of the way. Emma moaned at Liam as Zoya wrapped her lips around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Liam,” she gasped. “She’s sucking my clit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam licked his lips and watched as Zoya pushed Emma over the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Ah! Fuck, I’m cumming, I’m cumming, I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma closed her eyes and saw fireworks.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 6: Zoya and Liam Watch a Movie</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/6-zoya-and-liam-watch-a-movie/"/>
		<published>2024-05-03T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/6-zoya-and-liam-watch-a-movie/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="public" />
    <category term="movie theater" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Zoya stretched languidly and listened to the sound of pouring rain. The bed was warm, and she was in no hurry to get up. She could hear Nolan in the shower, and pictured him soaping up to wash away his and Emma’s cum. It had been hard not to make any noise as she masturbated to them going down on each other. Even after cumming twice, her dreams had been a swirl of intensely erotic scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glancing over the edge of the bed, she saw Liam sleeping on his back, one leg sticking out from under his sheet. He clearly had morning wood. She bit her lip and considered waking him up with a surprise blowjob, but then the shower turned off. Nolan would walk out in a minute, and Liam didn’t strike her as the kind of guy who appreciated an audience. Too bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled over toward Emma, who was facing away from her. The redhead stirred as Zoya spooned her, cupping her breast. She grinned when she felt Emma’s nipple stiffen through the satin fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good morning, Em,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mornin’, Zee,” Emma mumbled, gently brushing Zoya’s hand away and sitting up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“G’day!” Nolan exclaimed cheerfully as he emerged from the bathroom wearing shorts and a t-shirt, still rubbing his hair dry with a towel. “Shame about the rain. What should we do today?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe a movie?” Zoya suggested, scooting up to lean against the headboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam yawned and sat up, resting his elbows on the bed and blinking the sleep from his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A movie sounds good to me,” Emma agreed. She got up and stepped past Nolan, letting her fingertips brush against his. On her way into the bathroom, she noticed her discarded panties lying on the floor near Nolan’s blanket and quickly bent over to pick them up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam made a startled sound. Zoya glanced in his direction to see his eyes practically bugging out of his head. He’d clearly just caught a look at Emma’s bare backside. Maybe even a glimpse of her pussy, from how red he was turning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya cleared her throat, and he shot her a guilty look, realizing he’d been caught peeping. When her only response was to give him a knowing wink, he seemed flustered and busied himself digging for clean clothes in his bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theater wasn’t too crowded, Zoya was pleased to note. The boys had picked some obnoxious big-budget thing with cars and spies. That was fine because she had no intention of watching it. She had her own entertainment planned, and it involved finding seats away from everyone else, including Emma and Nolan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let’s sit toward the middle,” Nolan announced confidently, already walking with his popcorn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re going to sit up there,” Zoya replied, gesturing to the back of the room. Emma grinned and went after Nolan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All the way up here?” Liam asked, following her to the last seat in the last row, in the furthest corner of the room. The view of the screen was terrible. No one was sitting anywhere near them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that alright?” Zoya asked, smiling and adjusting her skirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah,” he replied, glancing at the screen and then at her. “Totally.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh look,” she giggled as the lights dimmed. “The armrests fold up.” She scooted closer, pulling his arm over her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the trailers played, Zoya started idly running a finger up and down his thigh. He caressed her upper arm as she leaned against him. When the lights finally turned all the way off as the movie started, she brushed her lips against his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I saw you looking at Emma this morning,” she murmured. He started to object, but she put a finger to his lips. “Shh. Did you catch a glimpse of her pussy when she bent over?” He stiffened, unsure how to answer. “She’s sexy, isn’t she? It’s okay, I think so, too.” Slowly, he nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I had fun with you in the ocean yesterday,” she purred, moving her hand down his chest. “I saw you checking me out. When I took my top off. That night at dinner.” Lower, over his abdomen. “The whole time you were teaching me to surf. You couldn’t keep your eyes off my body.” Even lower, over his shorts. “And when I found you hard, all I wanted to do was touch you.” He jumped as she caressed the outline of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But here’s a secret, Liam. By that time, I was already turned on. Do you want to know why?” He nodded and squeezed her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because the night before, Emma woke me up when she climbed out of bed. I watched her rub Nolan’s cock while he sucked on her nipples. Then she straddled his leg and humped his thigh until he came in her hand. She licked it all up.” Liam groaned, and she felt his erection swelling under her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So that’s why I was ready to go yesterday. And that’s why I don’t blame you for checking Emma out.” She rubbed his cock more firmly, and nibbled on his earlobe. He gasped and squirmed. “Do you want to know why she wasn’t wearing any underwear this morning?” He nodded, frantically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Last night, Emma climbed out of bed again. I watched her go down on Nolan.” Liam made a strangled sound and humped against her palm. “She kneeled next to him and wrapped her lips around him. She looked so fucking sexy doing it. And from Nolan’s reaction, I think she’s good, too. He was lifting his hips, just like you’re doing, pushing deeper into her mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, Liam, I was so fucking horny.” She unbuttoned his shorts, reaching inside to wrap her hand around his firm shaft. “I couldn’t help it. I started touching myself as I watched them. It was so hard to stay quiet. Especially when Nolan took off her panties and pulled her leg over his head so he could go down on her at the same time.” Liam grunted, and she felt a squirt of precum against her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, does that turn you on?” Zoya licked his neck. “It made me cum. I had to bite Emma’s pillow to keep quiet. He had his fingers inside her and his tongue on her clit. She came all over his face when he shot his load down her throat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Zoya!” he whispered. “Please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, what?” she whispered urgently in his ear. “Tell me. Tell me what you want me to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Use your mouth…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, say it, Nolan.” She rubbed faster. “Say it!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suck my cock!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excitedly, she helped him scoot his shorts lower. He gasped as she wrapped her lips around his head and pulled him into the heat of her mouth. His hand was on the back of her head, and he was lifting his hips, already desperate for more. She moaned happily and swallowed him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock was throbbing against her tongue. She relaxed her throat, and tried to let him go deeper. It was clear he wouldn’t be able to last long. She squeezed her thighs together and pulled back, bobbing her head up and down, swirling her tongue against the tip. He grunted, his cock twitched, and she tasted his precum, like a promise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Zoya! Fuck,” he groaned quietly. “I want to cum in your mouth!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wave of lust flooded her. She redoubled her efforts, squeezing the base of his shaft, slurping greedily, desperate to make him explode. It excited her to know that no one but Liam could hear the wet sounds she was making. Suddenly, his legs stiffened and he moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock twitched repeatedly as he flooded her mouth with hot cum. She swallowed again and again, deliriously happy. He rocked back and forth until finally, he collapsed against his seat, panting as she let him slip from between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, she pulled up her skirt, braced her legs on the seat in front of her, and started eagerly rubbing her clit. Liam watched, amazed. She hadn’t worn any panties to the movie, and her wetness coated her lips and thighs. She’d been turned on all day, and with his taste still on her tongue, she knew she would cum quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Put your fingers in me,” she groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wasted no time, leaning closer and slipping two between her swollen lips. She gasped and rubbed faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, yes, fuck me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He pushed his fingers deeper, pulling them out and sliding them slowly back in. It felt good, but she needed more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Harder,” she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moved faster, thrusting in and out, fucking her. She closed her eyes. This was it. Fast and frantic and insistent. The pressure built in waves, more and more intense, until finally, they crashed, and she came, hard. Her insides clenched around his fingers until she pushed him away, rocking in place as the aftershocks washed over her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When her vision finally cleared, Liam was staring at her, awestruck. She beamed at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Zoya…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” she sighed happily. “Maybe tonight. Right now, I’m too sensitive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You heard me,” she grinned. “Put your cock away, watch the movie, and I’ll think about fucking you tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, and buttoned up his shorts as Zoya snuggled up against him.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 5: Emma and Nolan Go Downtown</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/5-emma-and-nolan-go-downtown/"/>
		<published>2024-04-28T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/5-emma-and-nolan-go-downtown/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="sixty-nine" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I’m having fun with Nolan,” Emma admitted as she tried to choose between two dresses. “But I don’t know if I should take it further.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should absolutely take it further,” Zoya grinned as she scooped herself into her bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The families were heading into the city for dinner at a fancy sushi place downtown. The boys had already left, wearing slacks and dress shirts, leaving the girls alone to get ready.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But what does it &lt;em&gt;mean&lt;/em&gt;?” Emma frowned, worried that the little black dress might be too much for dinner with her parents. “We live on opposite sides of the planet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s the best part of a vacation fling! It doesn’t have to mean anything. In a few days, you both go home, and you don’t have to see him again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if Liam brings him again next year?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t threaten me with a good time,” Zoya laughed. “You’re overthinking it. Wear the green one.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Overthinking Nolan or the dress?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Both!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, you think I should fool around with Nolan again tonight?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girl, if you don’t, I might! I have been &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; turned on all day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Even after Liam?” Emma knowingly raised an eyebrow as she slipped into the green dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you saw us? I thought you were too distracted to notice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I saw you fall off the surfboard and come up kissing him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm, we did more than that.” Zoya bit her lip as she turned away to let Emma zip her up. “I gave him a handy, and he returned the favor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right there in the ocean?” Emma giggled. “That’s hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was, but then you two came back, and he’s barely said a word since. I think he doesn’t know how to behave around me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, what now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, we go to dinner—you look great in that dress, by the way—and make sure these boys understand how lucky they are to have caught our attention. Then tonight, you do what feels right with Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about you and Liam?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see.” Zoya gave her a wink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hours later, Emma lay in bed, hesitating. Even with all of Zoya’s encouragement, she wasn’t sure about doing anything more with Nolan. He’d been flirtatious and playful on the beach, but never mentioned what happened last night. Zoya said he was being respectful, letting her set the pace. Emma wished he was a little more clear about what he was looking for. The ambiguity made it harder for her to figure out what she wanted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner had been dripping with sexual tension. Zoya toyed with Liam like a cat with a bird. He seemed interested, but reluctant to respond around Nolan, no matter how much Zoya pushed her arms together to exaggerate her cleavage. Emma caught Nolan checking her out repeatedly, but he never pushed it. He seemed confident that if she wanted more, she’d let him know. Despite her uncertainty, the idea of doing more had her squeezing her thighs together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they got ready for bed, Zoya loaned her a satin nightie, “just in case,” which was much sexier than what she usually slept in. She paired it with a simple pair of black panties, and felt self-conscious about how short it was until she got under the covers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan went to bed wearing boxers without a shirt, just like last night. Liam, to Zoya’s obvious annoyance, seemed oblivious. After throwing on an old t-shirt, he’d crawled under his blankets and fell asleep right away. She could hear him softly snoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the now-familiar quiet rustling came from Nolan’s side of the bed, Zoya prodded her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go!” She mouthed the words, eyes sparkling with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma bit her lip and raised her eyebrows, as if asking, “Do you think I should?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya gave her a look and moved as if to throw her covers off, reminding Emma of her earlier threat to jump on Nolan if she didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, okay,” she silently replied, grinning as Zoya gave her a thumbs-up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled away, peeking over the edge of the bed. Nolan had already kicked his sheet off. He had one hand down his boxers, stroking his erection. They made eye contact, and it was immediately electric. He smiled and lifted his chin in a greeting, clearly pleased to see her awake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She slipped out from under her covers and dropped by his side. He wrapped his arm around her and pulled her smoothly into a kiss. She rolled against him, throwing one leg over his, and touching his chest. The growing intensity of the kiss matched the rapid blooming of arousal in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She broke away from his lips when she felt him start stroking himself again. She wanted to see, but his boxers were still in the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so sexy,” he breathed in her ear, sending a shiver down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So are you,” she whispered, hooking her thumb under his waistband. He followed her lead, lifting his butt and helping her slide his boxers down his legs until he could kick them off. He gripped the base of his cock and angled it upward, giving her a better look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squirmed as he squeezed her ass, lifting his thigh a bit to put pressure between her legs. Excitedly, she reached down, wrapping her hand around the shaft just above his. He exhaled, stifling a moan as she squeezed him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They moved together, him pushing into her hand, and her grinding against him. She loved the way he responded to her touch. When she felt him pulling up the hem of her nightie, she felt a thrill. A moment later, he reached into her panties to grab her ass directly. His fingers pressed into her flesh and she buried her face in his shoulder, trying not to make any noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wondered if he knew that Zoya was watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking down, she saw a drop of precum glistening on the tip of his cock. Without hesitating, she shifted to kneel beside him. He watched with hunger in his eyes as she lowered her head and licked it up. Slowly, teasingly, she took him into her mouth. He bit his lip and squeezed her ass harder. She swirled her tongue and squirmed, feeling a sudden wetness soak into her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She closed her eyes and tried to take him deeper. He breathed heavily, his cock throbbing in her hand and swelling in her mouth. She stroked his shaft as she bobbed her head, letting him slip just a bit further each time. He rewarded her with another squirt of precum on her tongue, giving her a taste of what was to come. She wanted to make him climax, to feel his cock twitching, to know she did that, made him explode with desire for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted and shifted his position, thrusting his hand further down her underwear. She swallowed a squeal as he found her wet lips, working a finger between them. It threw her off her rhythm. She had to back off, gasping as he pushed easily inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked up at him, mouth wide in surprise. Somehow, she hadn’t expected him to touch her like this. He grinned and started dipping his finger in and out. Her body responded instantly, welcoming him in, inviting him deeper. She found herself rolling her hips, pushing back against his hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eager to regain control, she wrapped her lips around his head again, swirling her tongue. He twitched in her hand, and she squeezed him harder. He didn’t stop, fingers moving against her swollen lips. She sucked hard, and he responded by slipping another inside. Her walls clenched around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached below his balls, tickling the sensitive skin there with a fingertip, something she’d read about somewhere. He let out a surprised exhalation, and bucked his hips, pushing deeper. She struggled not to choke, trying to relax and take him into her throat. His fingers were rigid, thrust deep inside her needy pussy. She felt him swelling, throbbing, and tried not to moan. She wanted it, wanted him to cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But he pulled back. Before she could respond, he withdrew his fingers, making her gasp, and then roughly tugged her panties down. She wondered if he was going to roll her over and fuck her. She wondered if she wanted him to. He encouraged her to lift one knee and then the other, sliding them off. Then he pulled her leg, moving her to straddle his face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She did moan, then, around his cock, as he eagerly started licking. His tongue danced along her folds, lapping up her juices. She responded in kind, lashing her tongue around the ridge of his head. It was difficult to focus. She jumped when he put his fingers back in, first one and then another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a lot. Nearly overwhelming. His body was hot under hers. His tongue danced against her. She swallowed, tasting more precum, his heady flavor coating her tongue. His fingers moved inside her fluttering walls. He was lifting his hips to push urgently into her mouth. She tried to keep up. She wanted to feel his body go stiff, but there were distracting flares of color behind her closed eyes and matching flares of heat in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he sucked her clit between his lips, it happened. She felt her insides clenching and grasping at him, over and over. He made a small surprised sound as her juices squirted around his fingers. He thrust again and again, deeper into her throat. She could only groan and pull back a bit as his cock started throbbing and twitching. His cum flooded her mouth. She swallowed as much as she could, but it was too much, and the excess drooled from her lips around the base of his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They moved as one, rocking against each other as their climaxes peaked and crashed together. When she finally released his cock, and rested her head against his hip, he slipped his fingers from her and dropped his head. They were both panting with exertion. For a long time, they just lay like that, catching their breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she climbed off, kneeling next to him, wiping his cum from her chin. He looked at her with awe in his eyes, and she returned it. Neither of them spoke as she got to her feet. She held a finger to her lips as she stepped over him to climb back into bed. He nodded and pulled his sheet up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya’s eyes were glinting eagerly, and before she could react, her friend pulled her into a quiet but intense kiss. Emma melted happily as Zoya’s tongue slipped between her lips, seeking a taste of Nolan’s cum. Finally satisfied, Zoya breathed into her ear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, you two were amazing. I came twice!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma bit her lip as the girls settled onto their pillows and grinned at each other. Maybe Zoya was right about not overthinking things.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 4: Zoya and Liam Play in the Ocean</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/4-zoya-and-liam-play-in-the-ocean/"/>
		<published>2024-04-25T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/4-zoya-and-liam-play-in-the-ocean/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="handjob" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="ocean" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Zoya looked up from her book as Liam flopped onto the towel next to her. Despite Emma’s dismissiveness, he really had filled out nicely. Not as tall or broad as Nolan, granted, but Zoya wouldn’t kick him out of her bed. Her eyes roamed down past his chest. There was just a hint of hair trailing below the waistband of his board shorts. She wondered if he trimmed. He looked up, catching her biting her lip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up?” He asked, raising an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing,” she smiled. “I thought you guys were surfing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan said it’s too calm for surfing.” He shrugged. “Then he ran off with Emma.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya glanced in the direction he indicated and saw the redhead and the tall blonde frolicking in the waves. Liam sighed, drawing her attention back to him. She imagined tangling her fingers in his tousled hair and pulling his mouth to hers. Feeling his bare chest press against her… Fuck. She shook her head, trying to clear the haze of aroused thoughts. Watching Emma and Nolan fool around last night had left her worked up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How awful of him to run off and leave you with just me for company,” she teased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s not what I meant,” he grinned. “It’s just that he always does this. We make plans, and then he ends up flirting with some chick.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm,” she considered, stretching languidly, and pretending not to notice him watching. “Maybe when he does that, he’s trying to give you space to hit on someone?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I dunno, I’m terrible at flirting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you?” Zoya rolled her shoulders. “It’s not that difficult. Just a matter of being receptive to signals.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I guess.” He frowned. “Girls don’t send me a lot of signals.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I doubt that,” she said, turning away from him. “Will you rub my shoulders? I’m a bit stiff.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, uh, sure.” He sat behind her and started massaging her back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s nice. I must have slept funny last night. How about you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not so bad. We surfed a lot yesterday, so I passed out right away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can go a bit lower,” she purred, leaning into his touch. “I’m glad you slept alright. I was worried about you, down there on the floor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, uh, we got lots of, um, extra blankets…” He trailed off as his hands drifted down her sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” she murmured as he daringly reached forward just enough to brush the edge of her bikini.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah.” He caressed the sides of her breasts for a moment, trying to act like it was part of the massage, before losing his courage and going back to her shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright.” Zoya decisively got to her feet and offered him her hand. “Come on, Liam. Show me how to surf.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But,” he protested as she helped him get to his feet, “it’s too calm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s fine,” she laughed, “just teach me how to stand up on the board.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shrugged, grabbed his board, and led her into the surf until they were chest-deep. The water felt lovely in the midday heat. As Liam had said, the waves were very gentle. Useless for surfing, but perfect for standing close, swaying with the flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He showed her how to straddle the board and float in place, holding her hand while she found her balance. Then how to lay full-length and paddle around. She smiled every time she caught him looking at her body. He seemed a bit distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he tried to show her how to jump to her feet, as if she was about to catch a wave, but she kept falling off. Every time she came up out of the water laughing, Liam tried not to stare as she got back on the board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third time she fell, she not-so-accidentally came up against him. She was delighted to discover he was hard. He blushed and stepped back, but she allowed a wave to push her closer, pressing her body against his.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Zoya!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She pretended to be surprised. “Is this because of me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh… yeah,” he admitted, with his erection poking into her hip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why, Liam, do you fancy me?” She grinned, teasing him a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, I tried not to be a creep!” He grimaced. “It’s just that since I saw you topless yesterday, I can’t stop thinking about you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good.” She wrapped her arms around his shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” Liam relaxed. “You’re not mad?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not mad,” she murmured, pulling him into a kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They swayed together with the movement of the water. Liam turned out to be quite a good kisser. When he cupped her ass to pull her more firmly against him, she felt a quickly growing heat in her core. His cock throbbed between them, and she moaned. She wanted to see it, to touch him, to feel it in her hands. She broke the kiss and took a half-step back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Show me,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded and quickly tugged his shorts down around his knees. The water was crystal clear, and see could see his cock jutting proudly toward her. She’d guessed right, he kept his dark hair trimmed. His shaft was a bit more brown than the rest of his skin, gradually growing darker closer to his head, which was already swollen with need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I touch you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God, yes,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She eagerly wrapped her hand around him and squeezed, laughing when he twitched in response. Slowly, she slid her hand up and down the full length. He exhaled slowly and let the waves rock him in time with her touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya, you’re turning me on so much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can tell.” She rubbed her thumb over the sensitive ridge of his head, making him jump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I see your tits again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked up and down the beach to confirm no one was watching. Emma and Nolan were distracted, and there were only a handful of other people in sight, all some distance away. She grinned and slipped her bikini cups to either side. Liam gawked at her breasts breaking the surface of the water. She let him look for a moment, and then brought his hands up to cup them. He happily massaged her chest as she resumed caressing his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is this what you were thinking about after you saw me yesterday?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. I fell asleep thinking about your nipples. I had the most awkward erection.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should have asked me to help,” she teased as she squeezed the base of his shaft with one hand and cupped his balls with the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me. If I’d known that was an option, I would have.” He groaned, squeezing her nipples as he thrust into her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt her insides clench as she imagined doing what Emma did. Climbing down beside him. Grinding against his thigh. Rubbing his cock until he exploded. She squeezed her legs together, deeply aroused by the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here,” she gasped, pulling his hand down, inside her bikini bottom. She pressed his middle finger above her clit, and showed him how to touch her. “Like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He concentrated on doing what she asked, and she resumed stroking his cock. They looked into each other’s eyes, brimming with lust, both gasping in surprise at the stimulation the other was providing. She felt the pressure building quickly, and rolled her hips. He fumbled lower, reaching for her slit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, not inside, stay at the top, that’s—ah!—that’s what I want,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya, you’re so fucking hot,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah? Are you gonna cum for me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you keep doing that, yeah…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya felt her insides flutter at the thought. She watched, excited, as he started thrusting eagerly into her hands. This was so hot. Here in the sun, standing in the crystal clear ocean, jerking Liam off where anyone could see. She wanted him to cum, to see what it would look like in the water. She matched his pace, bucking her hips and rubbing herself against the firm pressure of his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam, yes, don’t stop, keep touching me like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tried to keep her eyes wide open as the heat between her thighs grew more intense. Her climax was approaching, but she wanted to see him do it first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya,” he gasped. “I’m gonna—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, do it,” she growled, squeezing her legs together. “Come on, I’m so close, do it now!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted as she rubbed her palm over his sensitive tip, then went rigid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yes, Liam, cum for me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock started twitching and throbbing, and she watched, fascinated, as white fluid squirted between her fingers. It floated there as he shot gob after gob of it. She urgently stroked his shaft, squeezing every drop out. He shuddered and pulled his cock from her grasp, as his cum drifted away, diffusing into the ocean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sight of his climax caused her own to crest. She gripped his arm and frantically fucked herself against his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Liam! Fuck!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her insides clenched rhythmically, over and over, the pulse of her orgasm leaving her rocking in place. Her vision blurred, and she collapsed forward, gasping against his chest. He wrapped his free arm around her shoulder and held her as the waves of pleasure rolled through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she pulled his hand out of her bikini and kissed him deeply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” he gasped. “Zoya, you’re incredible.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What did I tell you?” She purred. “You’ve just got to be receptive to a girl’s signals.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
</feed>
