<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Ruby Pink Romance</title>
	<subtitle>Classy smut for classy people</subtitle>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/"/>
	<updated>2024-05-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Ruby Pink</name>
		<email>hello@rubypinkromance.com</email>
	</author>
  <icon>https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rubypink.jpg</icon>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 8: Zoya and Liam Go All The Way</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/8-zoya-and-liam-go-all-the-way/"/>
		<published>2024-05-13T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/8-zoya-and-liam-go-all-the-way/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="titfuck" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="cum on tits" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;After Emma kissed her and rolled away to have sex with Nolan, Zoya lay on her back trying to catch her breath. That sexy little redhead had really gotten her going. Her heart was pounding, and she was already wet. Not that it took much. She’d been in sexual overdrive since they arrived. So when Emma’s new take-charge attitude targeted Zoya, even just for a moment, it left her a bit weak in the knees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, quietly, she moved to Emma’s side of the bed and peeked over. She and Nolan were already making out, and she had his cock growing in her hand. Zoya bit her lip, and for a moment, considered just watching the two of them again. It would be so hot to see Emma’s face while Nolan fucked her. But seeing Liam’s face when she let him cum inside her would be even hotter. And if things continued on their current trajectory, she’d get to see plenty more of Emma’s O-face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited, she rolled back over to her side of the bed and peeked over at Liam. He’d slept through the last two nights of sexual activity, but today she’d let him know what had been happening. She’d also suggested that she might be open to having sex tonight. There was no way he’d be asleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, he was wide awake, lying on his back and looking up at her. She grinned, and with exaggeratedly slow, quiet movements, got out of bed to lie next to him. He opened his mouth to say something, but she pressed a finger to his lips. Shaking her head, she gestured toward the other side of the bed, letting him think they had to stay quiet so Emma and Nolan wouldn’t hear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled his covers off, and helped him remove his t-shirt and boxers. He was already mostly hard, and she eagerly moved to straddle him. He looked surprised when her bare pussy touched his cock and he realized she wasn’t wearing any underwear. She rolled her hips a bit, mashing against him, feeling him get harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moved to unbutton her shirt, and paused, raising an eyebrow at him, as though she were asking if he wanted her to take it off. He nodded eagerly, and she gave him a little lap dance as she teased him by undoing every button slowly, even though she could pull the whole thing over her head if she wanted. By the end, his cock was fully erect and throbbing under her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He reached for her chest and she leaned forward, putting a hand on either side of his head. He massaged her breasts gleefully. She shifted her weight to press one into his face, and he eagerly sucked on her nipple. His cock twitched, and she rolled her hips to grind against him as he switched sides. She loved the effect her body had on the men she allowed in her bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But she knew something that would really get him excited. Slowly, she pulled away, his obvious disappointment quickly turning to excitement as she knelt between his legs. He watched with wide eyes as she licked up the length of him, wrapped her lips around his head, and took him as deep as she could. Then she released him, and pressed his glistening cock between her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guys fucking loved this. As long as they were wet enough, she didn’t mind. The sight of a hard cock emerging from her cleavage was pretty sexy, she had to admit. Liam stifled a groan and lifted his hips, humping against her chest. She squeezed her breasts around him, awkwardly using the tips of her fingers to keep him in position. Every time he thrust up far enough, she kissed his tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a couple of minutes of this, he was going crazy, and her breasts were covered with lubrication, a mix of her drool and his leaking precum. Finally, she got bored with the game, let go of her breasts and took him into her mouth. He gasped as she swallowed him deeper and deeper until her eyes were watering, only backing off when his cock twitched in her throat and she almost choked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She climbed back up to straddle him again, gasping and excited. He gazed at her with pure desire, as she wiped her mouth and rubbed the wetness into her breasts. She shifted her hips until his cock was nestled between her lips, and slowly slid up and down the length of him, covering him in her wetness. He bit his knuckle, trying not to loudly moan at the sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She placed one hand on his shoulder, bracing herself, and reached down to position him against her opening. He gasped as she slowly lowered herself onto him. She felt her pussy blossom as his bulbous head spread her open. His girth filled her as she took him deeper, until at last she rested on top of him. He felt delicious inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled his head to her breast, just to give him something to focus on while she savored the feeling. She loved this moment. The first time you allowed a guy’s cock to fill you. It never stopped being good, but the first time with a guy was something special. She rocked her hips a bit, experimenting with the angle, and gasped as he twitched inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she sighed happily and moved back up to a sitting position. She stretched her arms and rolled her neck. Liam squirmed and tried to lift his hips to fuck her, but she wouldn’t let him move yet. From this angle, the head of his cock pressed forward, in a way that she knew would feel incredible when she started riding him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sensed some motion, looked to her side, and was pleasantly surprised to see Nolan across the bed staring at her. He was kneeling behind Emma, about to start fucking her, but had been startled to see her pop up. She licked her lips and nodded, giving him permission to look at her while he fucked Emma. He didn’t hesitate, immediately gripping her hips and thrusting forward. She heard Emma’s moan muffled in the pillow and grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked down at Liam, and once again held her finger to her lips as she started moving her hips. He nodded frantically, caressing her thighs as she started to fuck him. She looked back to Nolan, and squeezed her breasts for him, rolling her nipples between her fingers. He continued thrusting urgently into Emma, who was now squealing loudly, the pillow barely muffling the sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam let out a soft groan, and she looked back down at him. He was staring up at her with lust in his eyes. There was no way he couldn’t hear Emma. Did it turn him on to know she was getting fucked on the other side of the bed?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya moved faster, starting to bounce on his cock. He let out a strangled cry, and she leaned forward to cover his mouth, which only seemed to turn him on more. He started to thrust up to meet her with every bounce, urgently trying to fuck her harder. She leaned down and kissed him deeply, moaning into his mouth as his cock twitched repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your cock fills me up so good,” she purred. “Don’t finish yet, I want to cum on you first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and closed his eyes, gritting his teeth and trying to hold out. She got back up and started rubbing her clit. Nolan was still staring. She let him see how turned on she was. Pressure was building quickly now. Nolan grunted and fucked Emma, now crying out with every thrust. Zoya’s fingers moved frantically over her sensitive bud, and she rolled her hips, trying to press Liam’s cock against the spot that made her see colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan groaned, loudly. She couldn’t see Emma, but it sounded like she was sucking on her fingers, which made Zoya’s pussy clench. Fuck, she was so close. Her entire body seemed to be crackling with electricity. Her clit was swollen and needy under her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” Nolan gasped, “where?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on my tits,” Emma begged, spinning around to kneel in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam groaned when he heard this and squeezed her hips. She watched as Nolan started pumping his cock, about to cum all over Emma’s pale white breasts. Zoya wanted badly to suck on them. She wanted to lick Nolan’s cum off those little pink nipples. The thought pushed her over the edge. She closed her eyes and shook as an orgasm surged through her body. She felt a gush of hot liquid around the base of Liam’s cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let out a strangled cry and came at the same time. His cock throbbed and twitched as he pumped all his cum into her hungry pussy. She rocked in place, squeezing her breasts. Flares of color erupted behind her eyelids as her insides clenched over and over, trying to pull Liam deeper, to possess him completely. Waves of pleasure rolled through her nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened her eyes to find both Nolan and Emma watching her cum. She gasped and grinned at them, drunk with pleasure. Nolan groaned, and his cock exploded, shooting spray after spray of thick, sticky cum onto Emma’s chest. The redhead squealed and pinched her nipples. Liam’s cock twitched and slipped out, making Zoya shiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without thinking about it, she found herself climbing onto the bed, laughing and pulling Emma up with her. She pushed her friend onto her back and fell forward, eagerly licking up Nolan’s cum. Emma squealed as she sucked on her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, you two are hot,” Zoya purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Oh god,” Emma moaned, frantically rubbing her clit. “You’re gonna make me cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya loudly slurped up every bit of Nolan’s cum that she could find. He had a strong taste, but she was so aroused she didn’t mind. When she couldn’t find any more cum, she moved down Emma’s body, pushing her fingers out of the way to wrap lips around her swollen clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Liam,” Emma moaned. “She’s sucking on my clit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing that Emma and Liam were looking at each other while she went down on Emma turned her on even more. She looked up into Nolan’s eyes, who was watching and rubbing his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Ah!” Emma squirmed and bucked as Zoya flicked her tongue against her clit. “I’m cumming, I’m cumming, I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The redhead’s pussy started contracting repeatedly, and Zoya slipped two fingers inside to give her something to squeeze. She stared at Nolan, the taste of his cum and Emma’s mingling on her tongue. The thought that both boys were watching her make Emma cum made her insides clench, pushing Liam’s cum out of her pussy. She gasped, releasing Emma’s clit, as the sticky fluid dripped down her thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma laughed deliriously, squeezing her legs together as the aftershocks rolled through her system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya sat up on her knees, and licked Emma’s cream from her fingers. She looked back at Liam, and then at Nolan. Both looked stunned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You boys gonna be alright?” Zoya asked, carefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They glanced at each other, and quickly looked back at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, for sure,” Nolan murmured with a crooked smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh, all good,” Liam stammered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fantastic!” Zoya grinned at them both. “Because this vacation isn’t over yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She climbed to her feet, pulling Emma, still giggling, up with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, Em, let’s grab a shower and give the boys some space.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, night-night, boys!” Emma laughed and blew them a kiss as Zoya pulled her into the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 7: Emma and Nolan Go All The Way</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/7-emma-and-nolan-go-all-the-way/"/>
		<published>2024-05-11T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/7-emma-and-nolan-go-all-the-way/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="cum on tits" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“I’ve decided you’re right, Zoya.” Emma was walking arm-in-arm with her friend on the beach. The rain had finally cleared up, and the four of them were walking back to
the hotel from the beachfront taco stand where they’d had dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Naturally,” Zoya grinned. “What am I right about this time?” She shielded her eyes against the sunset and squinted ahead to where the boys had run off, like puppies with too much energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“About vacation flings, and doing what feels right, and not overthinking things.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Excellent! So, what are you trying not to overthink?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m going all the way with Nolan tonight,” Emma grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, great minds think alike! I decided to let Liam fuck me tonight, too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Emma giggled. “Was that before or after the movie?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, was there a movie playing?” Zoya laughed. “I didn’t notice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew it! When you headed off to the back of the theater, I knew you two were going to fool around.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about you two?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, we made out a little, and he put his hand up my shirt, but there were people sitting near us, and I was too nervous to do anything more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should have sat in the back, like us. As soon as the lights turned out, I started whispering in his ear and rubbing his cock. I told him how turned on I’ve been since watching you and Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You told him?” Emma blushed. “I feel like I should be mad, but…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, you want to know how he reacted?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” Emma laughed. “Is that weird? I’m not used to thinking about Liam that way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not weird! And judging by how hard he got, he’s got no problem thinking of you that way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think that might’ve had more to do with you than me, but go on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All I know is the way he begged me to suck his cock left me dripping. As soon as I swallowed, I hitched up my skirt and told him to finger me while I rubbed my clit. I came almost as fast as he did.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Zoya!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s what he said!” she laughed. “I told him I’d think about it, but really, I’d already made up my mind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait,” Emma frowned. “Tonight, when I climb down to have sex with Nolan…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll also be getting down to ride Liam.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, we’ll both be having sex on the floor on opposite sides of the bed? That seems silly. If we’re not trying to keep it secret anymore, why don’t we just use the bed?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t think the boys are &lt;em&gt;quite&lt;/em&gt; ready to do it together,” Zoya grinned. “But I bet we’ll get them there before this trip is over. For tonight, keep pretending like you don’t want me or Liam to hear.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re thinking about it, aren’t you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re imagining all of us having sex on the bed at the same time. Maybe you and I are touching a little? Maybe I’m sucking on your nipples while the boys fuck us both?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sounds like you’re the one who’s thinking about it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I definitely am. Best. Vacation. Ever!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they got ready for bed, it was unclear to Emma how much the boys were aware of the sexual tension in the room. She caught a few flirty looks from Nolan, and she spotted Liam watching Zoya hopefully, but otherwise they stuck to their normal routines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For her part, the anticipation was exciting. She and Zoya had a whispered conversation in the bathroom about what to wear. In the end, she wore Zoya’s satin nightie again, with no underwear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why bother with panties?” Zoya quipped, buttoning up her nightshirt. “I’m not. You’re just gonna get them wet and take them off. Save yourself the trouble.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting into bed meant walking past Nolan, who was already lying down. She got a thrill out of giving him a wink and letting him have a peek up her nightie as she climbed under the covers. He licked his lips hungrily, which made her blush, but also caused a flutter of desire in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya turned out the light and got into bed beside her, eyes glinting with excitement. Emma felt like she was vibrating with nervous energy. Zoya gently tucked a strand of red hair behind Emma’s ear and reached under the covers to squeeze her hand. She appreciated the encouragement, but this time she didn’t need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following an impulse, Emma leaned forward and kissed Zoya. Her friend seemed surprised, but quickly melted into the kiss. Emma quietly moved closer, tangling their legs together. She teased her tongue between Zoya’s lips, and the kiss became more passionate. Zoya squirmed and grabbed Emma’s ass, pulling their bodies together. At last, Emma playfully bit Zoya’s lower lip and rolled away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peeking over the edge of the bed, she was pleased to see Nolan gazing up at her. He’d already kicked his sheet off, and was idly rubbing himself through his boxers. Emma waggled her eyebrows at him and gestured with her chin for him to take them off. He did so, revealing that he wasn’t quite hard yet. Emma was eager to feel him get turned on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She slipped out of bed and dropped to lie along his side. She wrapped her hand around his cock and let herself be pulled into a kiss. Unable to resist comparing, she noticed that his lips weren’t as soft as Zoya’s. His stubble rubbed against her in a way that wasn’t unpleasant. He seemed more urgent, almost demanding, in the way he kissed her, sucking on her bottom lip. She realized with some surprise that while she was excited to have sex with him, he wasn’t as good a kisser as Zoya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She broke away from the kiss so she could look down at his cock rapidly stiffening in her hand. It pulsed with his heartbeat as she massaged it to life. Nolan sucked on her neck, panting a bit as she started stroking harder, rubbing her palm up and down the full length of his shaft. When she saw the first drop of precum appear, she didn’t hesitate to move down and lick it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she took him into her mouth, he gasped and lifted his hips, wanting more. She pushed him down, wanting to be in control. Slowly, methodically, she started bobbing her head, taking him a little deeper each time, until he was bumping against the back of her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While she was doing that, her free hand was busy between her thighs. She spread her lips, and dipped her fingers. It felt good to spread her creamy wetness over her lips. She teased her clit as his cock throbbed in her mouth, and imagined how good it would feel to guide him inside. She gave him one last suck and released him, leaving him hard and wet and desperate for more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma rolled onto her back, spreading her legs and pulling his arm so he’d roll on top of her. She reached down and guided his erection to slide against her. She gasped as he settled his weight between her thighs. He rocked in place, grinding his pelvis against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suck on my nipples,” she breathed. He scooted a bit lower and eagerly slipped the skinny straps off her shoulders, pulling the front of the nightie down to expose her chest. She felt her insides clench as he pulled her breast into his mouth. Sparks danced down her spine as his tongue flicked against her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His weight felt so good between her legs as he continued to grind against her. She squirmed, dripping with arousal as his cock prodded her bottom. He switched back and forth between her nipples, squeezing one and licking the other. She ran her hands over his shoulders and through his hair, full of excitement for what was about to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan,” she gasped, “I want you inside me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” He looked up, still squeezing her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she urged, pulling him up, and reaching down to position his head between her lips. “Please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan didn’t hesitate, slipping inside easily. He grunted, and she inhaled as he suddenly filled her. He lowered himself onto his elbows, buried his face in her shoulder and kissed her neck. She wrapped her legs around him, holding him in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your pussy is so hot,” he breathed in her ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immediately, he started moving. She held on, digging her fingernails into his back as he thrust with increasing passion. He sucked harder on her neck. She knew he was going to leave a mark, but didn’t care. He was deep, and with each thrust, he seemed to go deeper. She squeezed, clenching her pussy around him, and Nolan groaned into her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tangled her fingers in his hair and pulled him roughly into a kiss. Suddenly, his urgent kissing felt right, and his rough stubble didn’t bother her so much. Eagerly, she sucked on his tongue when he pushed it between her lips. Flares of colored light were dancing at the edge of her vision with each thrust, but abruptly he pulled away, rocking back on his knees and slipping out of her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He held up his hand, indicating that he needed a minute. She watched, fascinated, as he gripped his cock tightly, as though trying to restrain it. He grimaced, like he was holding something back, and his cock twitched several times in his hand. Despite how tightly he was squeezing, a squirt of precum dripped down his fingers. A moment later, he relaxed his grip and grinned at her. She got up on her knees and leaned in to whisper in his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Was that for me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I was about to cum. You feel so good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want it,” she breathed, feeling a surge of excitement. “I want you to cum for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I will, I just didn’t want to be done so fast.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get behind me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Emma dropped to her hands and knees. Nolan moved forward, and she gasped as he rubbed his cock against her until he found her opening and pushed back inside. This was her favorite. When a guy was behind her, something about the angles worked better. It felt like they could reach deeper, and every movement stimulated her more. She could usually come like this, especially if she rubbed her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan grabbed her and started thrusting. It felt delicious. She buried her face in his pillow to avoid making any noise. For a moment, he froze, as if startled by something, but then he started fucking her harder. She tried not to squeal as he squeezed her hips tighter, driving toward his climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a minute, she couldn’t hold her noises in anymore, and just hoped the pillow was muffling her cries of pleasure. Zoya would probably hear her and approve, or even egg her on, wanting her to get louder. Could Liam hear her? She imagined looking up over the bed and seeing Liam watching her, mouth open in shock. She did squeal, then, as her cunt clenched tightly around Nolan’s cock. He grunted and kept fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pictured Liam sitting before her, furiously masturbating to the sight of her getting fucked. Panting with each thrust, she got up on her hands again. She imagined Liam coming closer, rubbing his cock in front of her until neither of them could resist. Suddenly desperate for something to suck on, she shoved two fingers in her mouth, pushing deep and wishing it was Liam’s cock. She imagined him using her mouth as eagerly as Nolan was using her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan groaned, much louder than she expected, and for a moment, she wondered if he knew about her fantasy, and it was getting him off, too. She moaned around her fingers as his cock swelled inside her. She knew he was close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” he gasped, “where?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited, she spun around, popping him out of her. She knelt in front of him and looked up as he started stroking his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cum on my tits,” she urged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan looked down at her, eyes full of lust. Then he glanced to the side. She followed his gaze and saw Zoya, clearly riding Liam, who was hidden by the bed. Zoya had her tits in her hands and bounced in place, eyes closed, mouth open in ecstasy. Emma couldn’t tell if she’d just cum or was about to. She heard Liam make a strangled sound, and Zoya let out a long, low moan as she froze, absorbed in the sensation of Liam cumming inside her. She opened her eyes, saw Emma and Nolan watching, and grinned happily at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan grunted and Emma felt the first hot splash of cum on her chest. He was staring at her again and frantically stroking his cock. She squealed as his body rocked in place, shooting cum all over her breasts. The wanton look in his eyes made her insides clench repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, Nolan collapsed onto his back, still holding his cock and panting as the last of his orgasm rolled through his body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma leaned against the bed, head swimming with arousal. She squeezed her nipples, sending lightning crackling through her system. Before she could decide to ask Nolan to help her cum, she felt Zoya climb onto the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her friend laughed and pulled her up to lay on her back. She gasped as Zoya immediately began licking all the cum from her chest. Emma reached between her legs and found her clit, swollen with need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, you two are hot,” Zoya mumbled around her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Oh, God, you’re gonna make me cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma looked down, and saw Nolan sitting up, watching the two of them with awe in his eyes. She spread her legs so he had a better view of her pussy and started rubbing tight circles around her clit. Zoya continued, loudly slurping up all of Nolan’s cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked to the other side of the bed and wasn’t surprised to find Liam watching as well. The hunger she saw in his eyes made her shiver with excitement. She couldn’t believe Liam was looking at her like that, watching his two friends writhe on the bed. She rubbed her clit faster and moaned as she remembered her fantasy. If Liam stood up right now with an erection, she would eagerly swallow him. She wondered if he could see how turned on she was by the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya, having apparently licked up all the cum, started moving down Emma’s body, kissing her stomach, licking her hips, nuzzling her hand out of the way. Emma moaned at Liam as Zoya wrapped her lips around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Liam,” she gasped. “She’s sucking my clit!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam licked his lips and watched as Zoya pushed Emma over the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zee! Ah! Fuck, I’m cumming, I’m cumming, I’m cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma closed her eyes and saw fireworks.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 6: Zoya and Liam Watch a Movie</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/6-zoya-and-liam-watch-a-movie/"/>
		<published>2024-05-03T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-05-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/6-zoya-and-liam-watch-a-movie/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="public" />
    <category term="movie theater" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Zoya stretched languidly and listened to the sound of pouring rain. The bed was warm, and she was in no hurry to get up. She could hear Nolan in the shower, and pictured him soaping up to wash away his and Emma’s cum. It had been hard not to make any noise as she masturbated to them going down on each other. Even after cumming twice, her dreams had been a swirl of intensely erotic scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glancing over the edge of the bed, she saw Liam sleeping on his back, one leg sticking out from under his sheet. He clearly had morning wood. She bit her lip and considered waking him up with a surprise blowjob, but then the shower turned off. Nolan would walk out in a minute, and Liam didn’t strike her as the kind of guy who appreciated an audience. Too bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled over toward Emma, who was facing away from her. The redhead stirred as Zoya spooned her, cupping her breast. She grinned when she felt Emma’s nipple stiffen through the satin fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good morning, Em,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mornin’, Zee,” Emma mumbled, gently brushing Zoya’s hand away and sitting up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“G’day!” Nolan exclaimed cheerfully as he emerged from the bathroom wearing shorts and a t-shirt, still rubbing his hair dry with a towel. “Shame about the rain. What should we do today?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe a movie?” Zoya suggested, scooting up to lean against the headboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam yawned and sat up, resting his elbows on the bed and blinking the sleep from his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A movie sounds good to me,” Emma agreed. She got up and stepped past Nolan, letting her fingertips brush against his. On her way into the bathroom, she noticed her discarded panties lying on the floor near Nolan’s blanket and quickly bent over to pick them up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam made a startled sound. Zoya glanced in his direction to see his eyes practically bugging out of his head. He’d clearly just caught a look at Emma’s bare backside. Maybe even a glimpse of her pussy, from how red he was turning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya cleared her throat, and he shot her a guilty look, realizing he’d been caught peeping. When her only response was to give him a knowing wink, he seemed flustered and busied himself digging for clean clothes in his bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theater wasn’t too crowded, Zoya was pleased to note. The boys had picked some obnoxious big-budget thing with cars and spies. That was fine because she had no intention of watching it. She had her own entertainment planned, and it involved finding seats away from everyone else, including Emma and Nolan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let’s sit toward the middle,” Nolan announced confidently, already walking with his popcorn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re going to sit up there,” Zoya replied, gesturing to the back of the room. Emma grinned and went after Nolan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All the way up here?” Liam asked, following her to the last seat in the last row, in the furthest corner of the room. The view of the screen was terrible. No one was sitting anywhere near them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that alright?” Zoya asked, smiling and adjusting her skirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah,” he replied, glancing at the screen and then at her. “Totally.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh look,” she giggled as the lights dimmed. “The armrests fold up.” She scooted closer, pulling his arm over her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the trailers played, Zoya started idly running a finger up and down his thigh. He caressed her upper arm as she leaned against him. When the lights finally turned all the way off as the movie started, she brushed her lips against his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I saw you looking at Emma this morning,” she murmured. He started to object, but she put a finger to his lips. “Shh. Did you catch a glimpse of her pussy when she bent over?” He stiffened, unsure how to answer. “She’s sexy, isn’t she? It’s okay, I think so, too.” Slowly, he nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I had fun with you in the ocean yesterday,” she purred, moving her hand down his chest. “I saw you checking me out. When I took my top off. That night at dinner.” Lower, over his abdomen. “The whole time you were teaching me to surf. You couldn’t keep your eyes off my body.” Even lower, over his shorts. “And when I found you hard, all I wanted to do was touch you.” He jumped as she caressed the outline of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But here’s a secret, Liam. By that time, I was already turned on. Do you want to know why?” He nodded and squeezed her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because the night before, Emma woke me up when she climbed out of bed. I watched her rub Nolan’s cock while he sucked on her nipples. Then she straddled his leg and humped his thigh until he came in her hand. She licked it all up.” Liam groaned, and she felt his erection swelling under her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So that’s why I was ready to go yesterday. And that’s why I don’t blame you for checking Emma out.” She rubbed his cock more firmly, and nibbled on his earlobe. He gasped and squirmed. “Do you want to know why she wasn’t wearing any underwear this morning?” He nodded, frantically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Last night, Emma climbed out of bed again. I watched her go down on Nolan.” Liam made a strangled sound and humped against her palm. “She kneeled next to him and wrapped her lips around him. She looked so fucking sexy doing it. And from Nolan’s reaction, I think she’s good, too. He was lifting his hips, just like you’re doing, pushing deeper into her mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, Liam, I was so fucking horny.” She unbuttoned his shorts, reaching inside to wrap her hand around his firm shaft. “I couldn’t help it. I started touching myself as I watched them. It was so hard to stay quiet. Especially when Nolan took off her panties and pulled her leg over his head so he could go down on her at the same time.” Liam grunted, and she felt a squirt of precum against her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, does that turn you on?” Zoya licked his neck. “It made me cum. I had to bite Emma’s pillow to keep quiet. He had his fingers inside her and his tongue on her clit. She came all over his face when he shot his load down her throat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Zoya!” he whispered. “Please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, what?” she whispered urgently in his ear. “Tell me. Tell me what you want me to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Use your mouth…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, say it, Nolan.” She rubbed faster. “Say it!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suck my cock!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excitedly, she helped him scoot his shorts lower. He gasped as she wrapped her lips around his head and pulled him into the heat of her mouth. His hand was on the back of her head, and he was lifting his hips, already desperate for more. She moaned happily and swallowed him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock was throbbing against her tongue. She relaxed her throat, and tried to let him go deeper. It was clear he wouldn’t be able to last long. She squeezed her thighs together and pulled back, bobbing her head up and down, swirling her tongue against the tip. He grunted, his cock twitched, and she tasted his precum, like a promise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Zoya! Fuck,” he groaned quietly. “I want to cum in your mouth!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wave of lust flooded her. She redoubled her efforts, squeezing the base of his shaft, slurping greedily, desperate to make him explode. It excited her to know that no one but Liam could hear the wet sounds she was making. Suddenly, his legs stiffened and he moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock twitched repeatedly as he flooded her mouth with hot cum. She swallowed again and again, deliriously happy. He rocked back and forth until finally, he collapsed against his seat, panting as she let him slip from between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, she pulled up her skirt, braced her legs on the seat in front of her, and started eagerly rubbing her clit. Liam watched, amazed. She hadn’t worn any panties to the movie, and her wetness coated her lips and thighs. She’d been turned on all day, and with his taste still on her tongue, she knew she would cum quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Put your fingers in me,” she groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wasted no time, leaning closer and slipping two between her swollen lips. She gasped and rubbed faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, yes, fuck me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He pushed his fingers deeper, pulling them out and sliding them slowly back in. It felt good, but she needed more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Harder,” she moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moved faster, thrusting in and out, fucking her. She closed her eyes. This was it. Fast and frantic and insistent. The pressure built in waves, more and more intense, until finally, they crashed, and she came, hard. Her insides clenched around his fingers until she pushed him away, rocking in place as the aftershocks washed over her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When her vision finally cleared, Liam was staring at her, awestruck. She beamed at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Zoya…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” she sighed happily. “Maybe tonight. Right now, I’m too sensitive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You heard me,” she grinned. “Put your cock away, watch the movie, and I’ll think about fucking you tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, and buttoned up his shorts as Zoya snuggled up against him.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 5: Emma and Nolan Go Downtown</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/5-emma-and-nolan-go-downtown/"/>
		<published>2024-04-28T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/5-emma-and-nolan-go-downtown/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="sixty-nine" />
    <category term="swallow" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I’m having fun with Nolan,” Emma admitted as she tried to choose between two dresses. “But I don’t know if I should take it further.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should absolutely take it further,” Zoya grinned as she scooped herself into her bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The families were heading into the city for dinner at a fancy sushi place downtown. The boys had already left, wearing slacks and dress shirts, leaving the girls alone to get ready.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But what does it &lt;em&gt;mean&lt;/em&gt;?” Emma frowned, worried that the little black dress might be too much for dinner with her parents. “We live on opposite sides of the planet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s the best part of a vacation fling! It doesn’t have to mean anything. In a few days, you both go home, and you don’t have to see him again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if Liam brings him again next year?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t threaten me with a good time,” Zoya laughed. “You’re overthinking it. Wear the green one.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Overthinking Nolan or the dress?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Both!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, you think I should fool around with Nolan again tonight?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girl, if you don’t, I might! I have been &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; turned on all day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Even after Liam?” Emma knowingly raised an eyebrow as she slipped into the green dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you saw us? I thought you were too distracted to notice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I saw you fall off the surfboard and come up kissing him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm, we did more than that.” Zoya bit her lip as she turned away to let Emma zip her up. “I gave him a handy, and he returned the favor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right there in the ocean?” Emma giggled. “That’s hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was, but then you two came back, and he’s barely said a word since. I think he doesn’t know how to behave around me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, what now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, we go to dinner—you look great in that dress, by the way—and make sure these boys understand how lucky they are to have caught our attention. Then tonight, you do what feels right with Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about you and Liam?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see.” Zoya gave her a wink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hours later, Emma lay in bed, hesitating. Even with all of Zoya’s encouragement, she wasn’t sure about doing anything more with Nolan. He’d been flirtatious and playful on the beach, but never mentioned what happened last night. Zoya said he was being respectful, letting her set the pace. Emma wished he was a little more clear about what he was looking for. The ambiguity made it harder for her to figure out what she wanted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner had been dripping with sexual tension. Zoya toyed with Liam like a cat with a bird. He seemed interested, but reluctant to respond around Nolan, no matter how much Zoya pushed her arms together to exaggerate her cleavage. Emma caught Nolan checking her out repeatedly, but he never pushed it. He seemed confident that if she wanted more, she’d let him know. Despite her uncertainty, the idea of doing more had her squeezing her thighs together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they got ready for bed, Zoya loaned her a satin nightie, “just in case,” which was much sexier than what she usually slept in. She paired it with a simple pair of black panties, and felt self-conscious about how short it was until she got under the covers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan went to bed wearing boxers without a shirt, just like last night. Liam, to Zoya’s obvious annoyance, seemed oblivious. After throwing on an old t-shirt, he’d crawled under his blankets and fell asleep right away. She could hear him softly snoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the now-familiar quiet rustling came from Nolan’s side of the bed, Zoya prodded her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go!” She mouthed the words, eyes sparkling with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma bit her lip and raised her eyebrows, as if asking, “Do you think I should?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya gave her a look and moved as if to throw her covers off, reminding Emma of her earlier threat to jump on Nolan if she didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, okay,” she silently replied, grinning as Zoya gave her a thumbs-up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled away, peeking over the edge of the bed. Nolan had already kicked his sheet off. He had one hand down his boxers, stroking his erection. They made eye contact, and it was immediately electric. He smiled and lifted his chin in a greeting, clearly pleased to see her awake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She slipped out from under her covers and dropped by his side. He wrapped his arm around her and pulled her smoothly into a kiss. She rolled against him, throwing one leg over his, and touching his chest. The growing intensity of the kiss matched the rapid blooming of arousal in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She broke away from his lips when she felt him start stroking himself again. She wanted to see, but his boxers were still in the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so sexy,” he breathed in her ear, sending a shiver down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So are you,” she whispered, hooking her thumb under his waistband. He followed her lead, lifting his butt and helping her slide his boxers down his legs until he could kick them off. He gripped the base of his cock and angled it upward, giving her a better look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squirmed as he squeezed her ass, lifting his thigh a bit to put pressure between her legs. Excitedly, she reached down, wrapping her hand around the shaft just above his. He exhaled, stifling a moan as she squeezed him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They moved together, him pushing into her hand, and her grinding against him. She loved the way he responded to her touch. When she felt him pulling up the hem of her nightie, she felt a thrill. A moment later, he reached into her panties to grab her ass directly. His fingers pressed into her flesh and she buried her face in his shoulder, trying not to make any noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wondered if he knew that Zoya was watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking down, she saw a drop of precum glistening on the tip of his cock. Without hesitating, she shifted to kneel beside him. He watched with hunger in his eyes as she lowered her head and licked it up. Slowly, teasingly, she took him into her mouth. He bit his lip and squeezed her ass harder. She swirled her tongue and squirmed, feeling a sudden wetness soak into her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She closed her eyes and tried to take him deeper. He breathed heavily, his cock throbbing in her hand and swelling in her mouth. She stroked his shaft as she bobbed her head, letting him slip just a bit further each time. He rewarded her with another squirt of precum on her tongue, giving her a taste of what was to come. She wanted to make him climax, to feel his cock twitching, to know she did that, made him explode with desire for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted and shifted his position, thrusting his hand further down her underwear. She swallowed a squeal as he found her wet lips, working a finger between them. It threw her off her rhythm. She had to back off, gasping as he pushed easily inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked up at him, mouth wide in surprise. Somehow, she hadn’t expected him to touch her like this. He grinned and started dipping his finger in and out. Her body responded instantly, welcoming him in, inviting him deeper. She found herself rolling her hips, pushing back against his hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eager to regain control, she wrapped her lips around his head again, swirling her tongue. He twitched in her hand, and she squeezed him harder. He didn’t stop, fingers moving against her swollen lips. She sucked hard, and he responded by slipping another inside. Her walls clenched around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached below his balls, tickling the sensitive skin there with a fingertip, something she’d read about somewhere. He let out a surprised exhalation, and bucked his hips, pushing deeper. She struggled not to choke, trying to relax and take him into her throat. His fingers were rigid, thrust deep inside her needy pussy. She felt him swelling, throbbing, and tried not to moan. She wanted it, wanted him to cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But he pulled back. Before she could respond, he withdrew his fingers, making her gasp, and then roughly tugged her panties down. She wondered if he was going to roll her over and fuck her. She wondered if she wanted him to. He encouraged her to lift one knee and then the other, sliding them off. Then he pulled her leg, moving her to straddle his face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She did moan, then, around his cock, as he eagerly started licking. His tongue danced along her folds, lapping up her juices. She responded in kind, lashing her tongue around the ridge of his head. It was difficult to focus. She jumped when he put his fingers back in, first one and then another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a lot. Nearly overwhelming. His body was hot under hers. His tongue danced against her. She swallowed, tasting more precum, his heady flavor coating her tongue. His fingers moved inside her fluttering walls. He was lifting his hips to push urgently into her mouth. She tried to keep up. She wanted to feel his body go stiff, but there were distracting flares of color behind her closed eyes and matching flares of heat in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he sucked her clit between his lips, it happened. She felt her insides clenching and grasping at him, over and over. He made a small surprised sound as her juices squirted around his fingers. He thrust again and again, deeper into her throat. She could only groan and pull back a bit as his cock started throbbing and twitching. His cum flooded her mouth. She swallowed as much as she could, but it was too much, and the excess drooled from her lips around the base of his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They moved as one, rocking against each other as their climaxes peaked and crashed together. When she finally released his cock, and rested her head against his hip, he slipped his fingers from her and dropped his head. They were both panting with exertion. For a long time, they just lay like that, catching their breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she climbed off, kneeling next to him, wiping his cum from her chin. He looked at her with awe in his eyes, and she returned it. Neither of them spoke as she got to her feet. She held a finger to her lips as she stepped over him to climb back into bed. He nodded and pulled his sheet up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya’s eyes were glinting eagerly, and before she could react, her friend pulled her into a quiet but intense kiss. Emma melted happily as Zoya’s tongue slipped between her lips, seeking a taste of Nolan’s cum. Finally satisfied, Zoya breathed into her ear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, you two were amazing. I came twice!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma bit her lip as the girls settled onto their pillows and grinned at each other. Maybe Zoya was right about not overthinking things.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 4: Zoya and Liam Play in the Ocean</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/4-zoya-and-liam-play-in-the-ocean/"/>
		<published>2024-04-25T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/4-zoya-and-liam-play-in-the-ocean/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="seduction" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="handjob" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="ocean" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Zoya looked up from her book as Liam flopped onto the towel next to her. Despite Emma’s dismissiveness, he really had filled out nicely. Not as tall or broad as Nolan, granted, but Zoya wouldn’t kick him out of her bed. Her eyes roamed down past his chest. There was just a hint of hair trailing below the waistband of his board shorts. She wondered if he trimmed. He looked up, catching her biting her lip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up?” He asked, raising an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing,” she smiled. “I thought you guys were surfing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan said it’s too calm for surfing.” He shrugged. “Then he ran off with Emma.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya glanced in the direction he indicated and saw the redhead and the tall blonde frolicking in the waves. Liam sighed, drawing her attention back to him. She imagined tangling her fingers in his tousled hair and pulling his mouth to hers. Feeling his bare chest press against her… Fuck. She shook her head, trying to clear the haze of aroused thoughts. Watching Emma and Nolan fool around last night had left her worked up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How awful of him to run off and leave you with just me for company,” she teased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s not what I meant,” he grinned. “It’s just that he always does this. We make plans, and then he ends up flirting with some chick.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm,” she considered, stretching languidly, and pretending not to notice him watching. “Maybe when he does that, he’s trying to give you space to hit on someone?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I dunno, I’m terrible at flirting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you?” Zoya rolled her shoulders. “It’s not that difficult. Just a matter of being receptive to signals.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I guess.” He frowned. “Girls don’t send me a lot of signals.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I doubt that,” she said, turning away from him. “Will you rub my shoulders? I’m a bit stiff.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, uh, sure.” He sat behind her and started massaging her back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s nice. I must have slept funny last night. How about you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not so bad. We surfed a lot yesterday, so I passed out right away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can go a bit lower,” she purred, leaning into his touch. “I’m glad you slept alright. I was worried about you, down there on the floor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, uh, we got lots of, um, extra blankets…” He trailed off as his hands drifted down her sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good,” she murmured as he daringly reached forward just enough to brush the edge of her bikini.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah.” He caressed the sides of her breasts for a moment, trying to act like it was part of the massage, before losing his courage and going back to her shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright.” Zoya decisively got to her feet and offered him her hand. “Come on, Liam. Show me how to surf.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But,” he protested as she helped him get to his feet, “it’s too calm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s fine,” she laughed, “just teach me how to stand up on the board.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shrugged, grabbed his board, and led her into the surf until they were chest-deep. The water felt lovely in the midday heat. As Liam had said, the waves were very gentle. Useless for surfing, but perfect for standing close, swaying with the flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He showed her how to straddle the board and float in place, holding her hand while she found her balance. Then how to lay full-length and paddle around. She smiled every time she caught him looking at her body. He seemed a bit distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he tried to show her how to jump to her feet, as if she was about to catch a wave, but she kept falling off. Every time she came up out of the water laughing, Liam tried not to stare as she got back on the board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third time she fell, she not-so-accidentally came up against him. She was delighted to discover he was hard. He blushed and stepped back, but she allowed a wave to push her closer, pressing her body against his.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Zoya!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She pretended to be surprised. “Is this because of me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I, uh… yeah,” he admitted, with his erection poking into her hip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why, Liam, do you fancy me?” She grinned, teasing him a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, I tried not to be a creep!” He grimaced. “It’s just that since I saw you topless yesterday, I can’t stop thinking about you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good.” She wrapped her arms around his shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.” Liam relaxed. “You’re not mad?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not mad,” she murmured, pulling him into a kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They swayed together with the movement of the water. Liam turned out to be quite a good kisser. When he cupped her ass to pull her more firmly against him, she felt a quickly growing heat in her core. His cock throbbed between them, and she moaned. She wanted to see it, to touch him, to feel it in her hands. She broke the kiss and took a half-step back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Show me,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded and quickly tugged his shorts down around his knees. The water was crystal clear, and see could see his cock jutting proudly toward her. She’d guessed right, he kept his dark hair trimmed. His shaft was a bit more brown than the rest of his skin, gradually growing darker closer to his head, which was already swollen with need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I touch you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God, yes,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She eagerly wrapped her hand around him and squeezed, laughing when he twitched in response. Slowly, she slid her hand up and down the full length. He exhaled slowly and let the waves rock him in time with her touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya, you’re turning me on so much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can tell.” She rubbed her thumb over the sensitive ridge of his head, making him jump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I see your tits again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked up and down the beach to confirm no one was watching. Emma and Nolan were distracted, and there were only a handful of other people in sight, all some distance away. She grinned and slipped her bikini cups to either side. Liam gawked at her breasts breaking the surface of the water. She let him look for a moment, and then brought his hands up to cup them. He happily massaged her chest as she resumed caressing his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is this what you were thinking about after you saw me yesterday?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. I fell asleep thinking about your nipples. I had the most awkward erection.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should have asked me to help,” she teased as she squeezed the base of his shaft with one hand and cupped his balls with the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me. If I’d known that was an option, I would have.” He groaned, squeezing her nipples as he thrust into her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt her insides clench as she imagined doing what Emma did. Climbing down beside him. Grinding against his thigh. Rubbing his cock until he exploded. She squeezed her legs together, deeply aroused by the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here,” she gasped, pulling his hand down, inside her bikini bottom. She pressed his middle finger above her clit, and showed him how to touch her. “Like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He concentrated on doing what she asked, and she resumed stroking his cock. They looked into each other’s eyes, brimming with lust, both gasping in surprise at the stimulation the other was providing. She felt the pressure building quickly, and rolled her hips. He fumbled lower, reaching for her slit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, not inside, stay at the top, that’s—ah!—that’s what I want,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya, you’re so fucking hot,” he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah? Are you gonna cum for me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you keep doing that, yeah…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya felt her insides flutter at the thought. She watched, excited, as he started thrusting eagerly into her hands. This was so hot. Here in the sun, standing in the crystal clear ocean, jerking Liam off where anyone could see. She wanted him to cum, to see what it would look like in the water. She matched his pace, bucking her hips and rubbing herself against the firm pressure of his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam, yes, don’t stop, keep touching me like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tried to keep her eyes wide open as the heat between her thighs grew more intense. Her climax was approaching, but she wanted to see him do it first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya,” he gasped. “I’m gonna—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, do it,” she growled, squeezing her legs together. “Come on, I’m so close, do it now!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted as she rubbed her palm over his sensitive tip, then went rigid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yes, Liam, cum for me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock started twitching and throbbing, and she watched, fascinated, as white fluid squirted between her fingers. It floated there as he shot gob after gob of it. She urgently stroked his shaft, squeezing every drop out. He shuddered and pulled his cock from her grasp, as his cum drifted away, diffusing into the ocean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sight of his climax caused her own to crest. She gripped his arm and frantically fucked herself against his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Liam! Fuck!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her insides clenched rhythmically, over and over, the pulse of her orgasm leaving her rocking in place. Her vision blurred, and she collapsed forward, gasping against his chest. He wrapped his free arm around her shoulder and held her as the waves of pleasure rolled through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she pulled his hand out of her bikini and kissed him deeply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” he gasped. “Zoya, you’re incredible.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What did I tell you?” She purred. “You’ve just got to be receptive to a girl’s signals.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 3: Emma Gives Nolan a Hand</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/3-emma-gives-nolan-a-hand/"/>
		<published>2024-04-18T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/3-emma-gives-nolan-a-hand/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="teen" />
    <category term="vacation" />
    <category term="flirting" />
    <category term="handjob" />
    <category term="nipples" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Emma pretended to sleep, but every fiber of her being was alert for any sound or movement from Nolan. She wanted to heave a sigh, or toss and turn, but worried she’d spook him. The longer she waited, the more doubts filled her head. What if he knew she’d watched him last night? What if he didn’t feel like doing it again tonight? Despite Zoya’s assurances, what if she just wasn’t his type?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had to admit the trick with the towels had totally worked. When they walked out of the bathroom, the boys had put so much work into &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; looking at them, it was almost more obvious than if they had openly gawked. Zoya had given her an I-told-you-so look after they closed the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, when the families went out for dinner, Zoya ensured that Emma was sitting next to Nolan. He turned out to be easy to talk to, pulling her in with funny stories about his childhood. He laughed at her misconceptions about Australia, but she was forced to admit that his 90s-era vision of Seattle was still largely accurate. She learned he was single, and planning to take a gap year to travel through Europe. He expressed interest in her plan to buy a van to drive the length of Highway 101 down to California.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the time they got back to the hotel room, and the boys stepped out to let them change for bed, Zoya was practically crowing with delight at her matchmaking efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m telling you, Em, he’s hooked! He was flirting all through dinner. There’s no way he doesn’t go to bed thinking about you. You’ll get your moment tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But lying in the dark, hours later, Emma wasn’t so sure. Nolan had been polite, but didn’t behave like he was infatuated, or even aware of her interest. No furtive looks. No ever-so-casual touches. The more she imagined working up the nerve to climb down and join him if he started masturbating again, the more she worried he would reject her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She risked another peek, opening one eye just enough to confirm that Nolan still appeared to be sound asleep. Frustrated and dejected, Emma was about to give up and roll away when he yawned and stretched. He blinked slowly and rubbed his eyes, and she closed hers just in time as he glanced up in her direction. Was he checking if she was asleep?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She waited, trying to keep her breathing even and not give any sign she was still awake. After a very long minute, with her eyes squeezed shut, she heard the slow rustling sound again. Heart pounding, she opened her eyes, and saw he was rubbing himself. She watched, entranced, as the shape of his cock grew under the sheet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let out a slow, quiet sigh and bit his lip. Then, just like last night, he strained his legs, pulling the sheet down enough to expose his chest. She felt a secret thrill watching as his movements grew more urgent, pushing and pulling on his erection, the muscles in his shoulders tensing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As before, she felt a heat blooming in her core, and a longing to touch him, to feel his body against hers. He stretched again, moving the sheet even lower, threatening to expose himself. Was he pulling the sheet off faster than last night?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was it. The moment Zoya had mentioned. She tried to work up the nerve to climb down next to him. How would he react? Would he be excited? Aroused? Shocked? Horrified? What if he covered up? What if he pushed her away? She knew Zoya would be exasperated with all these questions. Her friend would give her a shove, causing her to fall out of bed and—whoops!—on top of him. She’d give her a wink and tell her to be bold. Why was this so hard?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nolan stretched again, and kicked the sheet off fully. He pulled his boxers down, setting them aside, and leaving himself fully exposed. She stared, wide-eyed, as he stroked the length of his shaft, rubbing his thumb over the tip each time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, he seemed to be murmuring under his breath. She strained, trying desperately to hear what he was saying, what words got him excited. With a shock, she realized he was saying her name, over and over. He &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; thinking about her!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” he breathed, lifting his hips a bit, as if trying to thrust. She wondered what he was imagining. Was he just thinking about her tits from earlier? Was he picturing her body pressed against his? Her hand on his cock? Her tits in his face?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma,” he repeated, still barely a whisper, though it felt daringly loud, almost as if he wanted her to hear. His abdomen was clenched tight, and she wanted to slide her hand down the length of it, to wrap around the base of his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan,” she exhaled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His eyes flew open, and he went still as he met her gaze, eyes filled with lust. She held a single finger to her lips, and he slowly nodded. Carefully, she slipped out from under the blanket and lowered herself to lie at his side. They stared into each other’s eyes for a long moment, then she leaned in for a kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It started sweet, but soon their lips parted with hunger, and the kiss became more intense. She pressed closer and caressed his chest. She could feel his right arm moving against her as he started rubbing himself again. As his tongue danced with hers, she reached lower, tracing the trail of hair from his belly button. He jumped a little when she wrapped her fingers around the base of his shaft, even as he kept stroking near the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She broke the kiss and propped herself up on her elbow to gaze at his cock. Her fingers closed around him, squeezing. He groaned softly, and she felt him twitch in her grip. She looked back at his face and found him staring at her nipples, excitedly poking through the thin fabric of her cami.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stared hungrily as she awkwardly hiked her shirt up above her tits. She shifted her position to bring them closer, and gasped as he wrapped his lips around her nipple. His shaft swelled in her hand, and she tried not to make any noise as he flicked his tongue against her sensitive flesh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let go of his cock and reached up to squeeze her breasts, pulling her almost on top of him, and eagerly switching between them. She stifled a squeak and rubbed up and down the length of his throbbing erection. A drop of precum appeared under her fingers, and she eagerly rubbed it into his skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted, and lightly bit her, teeth grazing against her puckered skin. Little bolts of electricity arced between her nipples and her clit. She felt a clenching, and a bit of wetness soak into her sleep shorts. Urgently, she stroked him, savoring the way he fit in her hand. He responded in kind, lifting his hips to thrust into her grip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He kept squeezing and licking and sucking and biting until she was squirming with desire, rolling her hips against him. His body seemed to writhe, building steadily towards his climax. She wanted it. Wanted to feel his hot cum. To know she had taken him over the edge. But she was a bit distracted. There was a growing pressure in her core, and there were sparks dancing at the edge of her vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nolan,” she whispered, “please!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He responded by pulling more of her breast into the heat of his mouth and swirling his tongue demandingly against her nipple. She gasped and felt the dam burst, sending waves of pleasure through her body. It was all she could do to hold on to him and try desperately not to make a sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it became too much, she pulled breathlessly away from him and moved to straddle his thigh. He lifted his leg to press against her, and it felt delicious, but she settled herself firmly, wrapping both hands around his cock. He watched, excited, as she began stroking firmly up and down. She was on a mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More and more precum leaked from his tip, slick and hot to the touch. She started twisting her hands, stimulating the sensitive ridge of his head with her fingers. He grabbed her hip and squeezed, dropping his head back onto the pillow. She could feel him swelling and knew he was close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His body went rigid, his thigh straining between her legs. She watched, excited, as he groaned silently and his cock started twitching. His first shot of cum splashed between her fingers on the upstroke, and when she pushed down to squeeze the base of his shaft, rope after rope of thick, hot cum sprayed onto his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, she ran her fingers through the sticky mess, smearing it into his hair. His body slowly relaxed, and she was surprised to find herself licking her fingers clean. His flavor was salty and masculine, and reminded her a bit of the ocean. She realized he was watching, eyes still filled with desire, and leaned down to give him a kiss on the cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then she held a single finger to her lips again, winked, and climbed back into bed, where she was only a little surprised to see Zoya’s eyes gleaming. As Nolan quietly slipped into the bathroom to clean up, the girls grinned triumphantly at each other.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 2: Zoya and Emma Go Sunbathing</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/2-zoya-and-emma-go-sunbathing/"/>
		<published>2024-04-15T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/2-zoya-and-emma-go-sunbathing/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="redhead" />
    <category term="topless" />
    <category term="shower" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="vacation" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Zee, will you put sunblock on me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Again?” Zoya glanced at Emma, lying on her front in the sun. “I did your back before we left the hotel room.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s my Irish heritage. I have to keep reapplying, or I burn.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya grabbed the bottle of sunblock from Emma’s bag, and straddled her legs. The redhead squealed when she squirted a glob between her shoulder blades, then relaxed as she started to massage it in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’d been at the beach for a few hours, reading and relaxing while the boys surfed. Well, Zoya had been reading. Emma was mostly watching Nolan. Even now, she was still squinting against the glare of the sun on the waves, trying to catch a glimpse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s pretty empty out here, even for a weekday. I guess your dad was right about that convention or whatever.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh,” Emma agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Plus, this spot the boys found for surfing is a bit off the beaten path. Kinda isolated.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re not really listening, are you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right, right.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re too busy thinking about kissing &lt;em&gt;Nolan&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Emma glanced back, then realized what she said, and blushed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girl, you’ve got it bad for him,” Zoya chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is it obvious?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To me, yes. To Nolan, probably not. I get the impression he’s used to girls looking at him the way you do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, good,” Emma murmured, sounding like this was, in fact, terrible news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why are you so flustered?” Zoya laughed. “You’re beautiful. I’m sure you’ve pulled a lad you had a crush on before.” She finished rubbing the cream into Emma’s shoulders and gave her bottom a playful swat before settling back onto her towel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… um.” Emma rolled onto her side and looked at Zoya with quiet intensity. “Can I tell you a secret?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course,” she grinned, matching Emma’s posture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Last night I saw Nolan jerking off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, did he leave the bathroom door cracked open or something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, he was in bed. I heard a weird sound and when I rolled over, he was touching himself!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why wouldn’t he go to the bathroom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe he was worried it would wake someone up? Like, it would be less noticeable to stay there? So he waited until he thought everyone was asleep and started stroking!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, that explains why you’ve been so distracted.” Zoya grinned. “What’d you do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t do anything, I just stayed quiet and watched.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm.” Zoya frowned, a bit disappointed. “Did he cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, he came all over his chest. And, um… I think after he finished, he might have seen I was watching.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ooh! How’d he react?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He didn’t! I shut my eyes real quick. Maybe he didn’t notice? When he went to the bathroom to clean up, I turned away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just then the boys came running up, hastily dropping their surfboards and putting on flip-flops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re going to get some cokes,” Liam said breathlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“D’you two want anything?” Nolan asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure, bring us a couple of waters,” Zoya replied, since Emma was busy trying not to look at Nolan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They managed to wait until the boys were out of earshot before they started laughing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So what now?” Zoya asked. “Are you gonna take a run at him?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’d like to, but I dunno how I’ll get him alone. He and Liam have been glued together.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t mind being glued to Liam.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whaaat? Little Liam, who used to follow us around? You’re joking.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re only saying that because he’s always standing next to your tall surfer. I’m telling you, Liam’s proper fit now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god!” Emma grinned and shook her head. “What would you do if you saw Liam jerking off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I wouldn’t just watch, I can tell you that,” Zoya teased. “I’d get right in there and give him a hand.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma laughed and rolled onto her back, trying to adjust her bikini to keep herself covered but still get some sun on her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, just take it off,” Zoya said, rolling her eyes. “You Americans and your body issues.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? No, I couldn’t,” Emma scoffed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No one’s here to see.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The boys are coming back!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good! Give Nolan an eyeful, that’ll get his attention.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But Liam would see too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So what? They’re just tits.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take yours off if you’re so comfortable.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I will.” She untied her top, threw it in the bag, and raised a challenging eyebrow at Emma. Her friend frowned, comparing their chests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have incredible tits, and I’m flat as a board. Nolan won’t even notice me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Em, don’t put yourself down like that. You’re lovely, and Nolan will notice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You really think so?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Trust me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma hesitated, then removed her top. Her shoulders were covered in freckles, and the pale skin of her small breasts faded to a light rose color on her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you are. Now put on these sunglasses so you don’t have to make eye contact. I’ll tell you when they’re coming.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya felt pleased with herself as she lay down. The sun felt good on her bare skin, and Emma just needed a little push to get past her insecurities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long, she heard the boys approaching, and gave Emma a nudge. She could tell the moment they realized the girls were topless because their conversation suddenly stopped. Zoya snuck a quick peek. They were standing a short distance away, whispering to each other. Emma was already blushing, but made no move to cover herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here are your waters, ladies,” Nolan announced as they finally worked up the courage to approach. Zoya sat up and took the bottles from him. Nolan grinned easily, playing it cool, and making at point of meeting her eyes. Liam was clearly struggling not to gawk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you, boys,” Zoya purred, cracking one open and taking a drink. Peeking under her half-closed lids, she was pleased to see that Liam was sneaking a look at her chest, but Nolan was glancing at Emma’s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They dawdled as long as they could while taking their flip-flops off and retrieving their surfboards, but eventually, they ran off to surf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re welcome,” Zoya quipped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me!” Emma laughed as she sat up and cupped her breasts. “My nipples are so hard right now. Did he look?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girl, of course he looked. I told you he would.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do I do now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You wait for your moment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the next few hours, the clouds rolled in. Zoya frowned as she felt a raindrop. A moment later, they were squealing, throwing on their cover-ups, and grabbing their bags in a sudden tropical downpour. The rain was strangely warm compared to London, and she laughed as they sprinted back to the hotel room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, I’m drenched, and covered in wet sand,” Emma giggled as they dropped their things on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let’s rinse off,” Zoya said, pulling Emma after her into the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She peeled off her bottoms, and turned on the shower. As she adjusted the temperature, she turned around to find Emma hadn’t moved. Her eyes were locked on Zoya’s shaved mound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Em,” she said gently, “you’re staring.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Emma blushed and looked away quickly, covering her mouth in surprise. “I’m sorry, I just, um… you, you bent over to turn the water on, and… I didn’t mean to—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Relax.” Zoya moved closer and took her hand. “When you go to an all-girls school, you have to become an expert at interpreting looks. Is that girl glaring at me because she’s jealous? Or staring because she likes my outfit? Does she want to borrow my notes? Or does she want me to push her up against a locker and kiss her?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um… what kind of look was I giving you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Zoya hooked her finger in the redhead’s waistband and pulled her closer. “Why don’t you get in the shower with me and find out?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Emma stripped and followed her under the hot spray. As the water washed over them, Zoya pulled her into a long, soft kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was that kind of look,” Zoya murmured, kissing her again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, good,” Emma exhaled, running her hands down Zoya’s back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“First time kissing a girl?” Zoya guessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, but the first time I, um…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Felt anything?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Emma shivered as Zoya touched her breasts. “I never…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t overthink it,” Zoya reassured her. “In my experience, everyone’s a little bi. You spent all day getting squishy thinking about Nolan, and now here we are. It doesn’t have to mean anything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” Emma purred as Zoya kissed her neck. “What about you? Have you kissed many girls?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like I said, all-girls school. I’ve been with enough to know it’s fun, but I still mostly prefer guys.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have lovely tits, Zee.” Emma gently explored Zoya’s chest. “I love how dark your nipples are.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you, I like yours. They’re such a pale pink, I almost can’t see where they stop.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They’re—oh!—sensitive,” Emma gasped as Zoya dragged her thumbs over her nipples. “Sometimes I can cum just from playing with them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m jealous! Guys are always pawing at my chest, and it doesn’t do much for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Will you—ah!—suck on them?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya lowered her head and pulled one of the sensitive buds into her mouth. Emma gasped and squirmed. She alternated back and forth, tracing circles and feeling her nipples pucker under her tongue. Slowly, she slid her hand down Emma’s front.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oooh! Zoya, please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She teased her fingers through Emma’s soft curls. The redhead eagerly spread her legs, inviting her in. Zoya found her already slick and slipped a finger between her lips, drawing an excited gasp from her friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma ran her hands through Zoya’s hair, pulling her closer. Zoya squeezed her breast, and sucked hard on her nipple as she dipped first one and then two fingers inside. Emma was dripping. She must have been on edge since watching Nolan last night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Zoya!” Emma squealed, bucking her hips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya ground the heel of her hand against Emma’s clit and started thrusting her fingers insistently. But the awkward crouching stance was starting to hurt her back, so she dropped to her knees. Emma looked down at her, eyes full of shock and desire, as Zoya buried her face in her wet red curls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” she gasped. “Oh fuck.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya kept two fingers inside as she licked around Emma’s swollen clit. The hot water cascaded down her back as she pursed her lips and sucked. Emma grunted and rolled her hips, grinding against Zoya’s tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, you’re gonna make me cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya continued expertly stimulating her friend, feeling the tension build. She felt Emma’s walls fluttering as her orgasm approached. She curled her fingers, tapping the magic spot. Emma’s legs stiffened, and she cried out as a gush of hot fluid washed over Zoya’s hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a moment, Emma pulled her up into a shaky kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to make you feel good, too,” she breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya kissed her deeply and turned around, spreading her legs and placing her hands on the wall. The spray massaged her lower back as Emma moved to stand behind her. She reached around to squeeze Zoya’s breasts, and kiss the back of her neck, but laughed and straightened up again, sputtering after catching the spray in her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Touch me from behind,” Zoya encouraged. “Reach around and rub my clit. I like feeling someone behind me while I get off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma didn’t hesitate, grinding her pelvis against Zoya’s ass and grabbing her hips like she was fucking her. She thrust several times, then Zoya felt her friend’s hand tentatively reach lower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love that you shave it all off,” Emma remarked, caressing Zoya’s folds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm, I like that you keep yours,” Zoya replied. “I feel like everyone just expects you to shave. It’s hot when someone doesn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m just lazy,” Emma giggled, teasing a finger between Zoya’s lips. “Oh, you’re already wet,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I have been since you looked at me like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot,” Emma murmured as she coated her finger in Zoya’s wetness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My clit,” Zoya begged, and then gasped as Emma traced up to brush against her most sensitive spot. “Yes, yes, like that,” she purred as Emma started tracing tight little circles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve never touched another girl like this,” Emma said breathlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re doing—ah!—great, just—uh!—touch me like you’d touch yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma adjusted her hand, spreading her fingers on either side of Zoya’s clit, rubbing urgently up and down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is so fucking hot,” Emma breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya grunted in agreement. Bracing herself on the wall, she pushed back against Emma’s pelvis, making them both gasp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh that feels good,” Emma moaned, grinding against her. “I’m still so sensitive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya bit her lip and focused on the growing heat in her core as Emma fucked against her, rubbing her clit the whole time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, that’s it, just like that,” Zoya groaned. “I’m getting close, keep doing that, don’t stop, don’t stop, don’t stop.” Her body was buzzing with anticipation, and she was grunting with each thrust, the stimulation building in waves of intensity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was so close. Her vision blurred. Her fingernails scrabbled at the tile wall. The hot water washed over them both. Emma’s breathing was becoming ragged, but she didn’t stop or change pace, relentlessly pursuing Zoya’s climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” Zoya grunted, breathlessly, as her core tensed. “I’m going to—”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a sudden loud banging on the bathroom door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, don’t use all the hot water,” Liam called. “Me and Nolan are back, and we need to rinse off too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma squeaked, but Zoya grabbed her hand and held it in place, humping against her fingers as her insides started to clench. Emma let out a little surprised sound as Zoya pushed their hands lower and curled their middle fingers inside. They rocked in place as Zoya came hard around their fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a minute, she straightened up, and turned to pull her into a kiss. Emma moaned and kissed her deeply, and when she finally withdrew her finger, Zoya sighed happily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit!” Emma suddenly panicked as Zoya turned off the water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We came in here without any clothes! We’ve only got our bikini bottoms!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Relax, Em. This is an opportunity. We’re going to walk out of here wearing just a towel. And then we’ll make the boys come in here while we get dressed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s the opportunity? They saw us topless earlier. Why would a towel excite them now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s &lt;em&gt;because&lt;/em&gt; they saw us topless earlier. Being covered up in a towel is going to remind Nolan you’re naked under there. And he’ll go to bed tonight thinking about you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You think so?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know so. I told you, you’re beautiful. Nolan thinks so too, trust me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya grinned at Emma and handed her a towel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you ready?”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Oh, Mr. Johnson!</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/oh-mr-johnson/"/>
		<published>2024-04-13T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/oh-mr-johnson/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="flash erotica" />
    <category term="babysitter" />
    <category term="cheating fantasy" />
    <category term="role play" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="creampie" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/oh-mr-johnson-BFP1CeXx7A-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Mr. Johnson was a perfect gentleman who would never dream of laying a hand on me, no matter how badly I wanted him to do so. One evening, I couldn’t take it anymore and sneaked into his home office. He was sitting on the couch, looking at something on his tablet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mr. Johnson?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He glanced up when I spoke, and I saw understanding dawn in his eyes. He took in my pigtails, my short skirt, the fact that my shirt was unbuttoned a bit too far, and the obvious lust in my gaze. I moved to kneel in front of him, and he set the tablet aside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know I’m just your babysitter, but I have a favor to ask you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked curious, but didn’t say anything. Perhaps he didn’t trust himself to speak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry about the kids. They’re watching a movie with your wife. She thinks I’m asking you for a ride home.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He swallowed nervously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve seen the way you look at me. No, don’t deny it, Mr. Johnson. And it’s okay. I… I like the way you look at me. It makes me feel warm inside.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I spoke, I slowly unbuttoned my top, letting him see my white lace bralette.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And I know your wife doesn’t have sex with you anymore. I heard her talking to her sister on the phone. She’s planning to leave you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stared at me, worried about what I would do or say next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She doesn’t deserve you. She’s a frigid bitch.” I said this with excitement, and let my shirt fall to the floor. “You deserve someone who understands your… needs.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He licked his lips as his eyes hungrily devoured the sight of my eager nipples trying to poke through the fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me show you,” I purred as I unbuckled his belt. “Let me help you.” I unzipped his fly and pulled out his cock. It was already getting hard. I gasped at the sight, and eagerly ran my tongue up the length of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He leaned back, resting his head on the back of the couch as I took him in my mouth. His cock swelled to fill it, and I moaned with desire as I swallowed him. He wasn’t sure what to do with his hands, so as I started bobbing my head, I took one and showed him that he could grab my pigtails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned and followed my lead, tugging on my hair like handles, pushing me up and down on his cock. I swallowed and squirmed and tried hard not to gag. He became more eager, pushing his hips up to meet me. I choked, and he released me, a bit reluctantly, I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rocked back, wiping the drool from my chin, and got to my feet. He watched, cock twitching, as I removed my bra. Happy that he was open to what I was suggesting, I lifted my skirt to show him that I wasn’t wearing panties. He could see my wetness dripping down my thighs as I moved to climb onto his lap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, Mr. Johnson, will you let me fuck you? I’m just your babysitter, but I want to be more than that. I want you inside me, please.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned in agreement as I positioned his head against my opening. Eagerly, he wrapped his lips around my nipple, and I had to bite my finger to keep from crying out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Careful, Mr. Johnson, if you make me scream, your wife will hear!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, I lowered myself onto him. The feeling of him stretching me out was delicious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, Mr. Johnson, your cock feels so big in my tight little teen pussy!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He growled into my breast, and grabbed my ass, slamming me down on his cock. I squealed into my hand, hoping the sound wouldn’t carry. He buried himself in me to the hilt, claiming me as his own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Mr. Johnson, yes!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He started lifting me and pushing me back down. My tits bounced in his face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you like my titties, Mr. Johnson? Are they better than your wife’s saggy old boobs?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned into my cleavage, and I felt his cock twitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about my pussy? Is my pussy tighter than your wife’s? Does it feel better than hers? Tell me you like fucking my little teenage cunt better than hers!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, urgently, willing to tell me anything as long as I kept fucking him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take it, Mr. Johnson! Take my pussy! Forget all about your frigid bitch wife and fuck me. You can fuck me as much as you want. I’ll be your little cocksleeve, your little cumslut. You can bend me over and take me anytime you need.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let out a strangled cry then, and dug his fingers into my ass, slamming me down hard on his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I feel you swelling inside me, I know you’re about to cum. It’s okay! Cum inside me. You can always cum inside me. Fill me up with your hot load. Pump me full of your cum. Send me home with your spunk dripping out of me. Ah! Oh! Fuck me, Mr. Johnson, I’m cumming! I’m cumming on your big thick cock!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His entire body went rigid. I held his head to my breast as he grunted over and over, each time his cock twitched inside me. Telling me with each spurt that I was his, and that he was mine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he softened and slipped out of me. I sat next to him, resting my head on his shoulder. I must have been glowing, I was so satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hoły shit, darling, that was intense,” he gasped, still catching his breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, it was. I love playing Mr. Johnson with you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And the kids?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They really are watching a movie. Speaking of, I’d better get back down there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love you, wife.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love you, husband.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Only One Bed 1: Emma Watches Nolan</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/1-emma-watches-nolan/"/>
		<published>2024-04-10T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/only-one-bed/1-emma-watches-nolan/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="vacation" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/only-one-bed-sMcoHDLOY8-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Emma lowered her headphones as her dad parked the rental car. Sunlight gleamed on the ocean behind the hotel. She opened the door and took a deep breath of humid, tropical air as she gathered her things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wow,” her dad enthused, “smell that air!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s good to be back,” her mom agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why’d we wait so long?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, you know, first we couldn’t come because of travel restrictions, then the next year was my cousin’s wedding, and then last year you’d just started your new job. Suddenly, it’s been three years since we’ve seen everyone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everyone” in this case referred to her parents’ old college friends. Back then, they’d done everything together. They all got married in the same year, and were all in each other’s wedding ceremonies. Then they’d all had kids within months of each other. And although they’d all moved away, they kept a tradition of taking a shared week-long anniversary trip to the tropics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, after three years, they were back. Emma was both excited and nervous to see her childhood friends Zoya and Liam again. Three years felt like a lifetime to Emma. When she thought about how much she’d grown, who knew how the others had changed?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was most eager to see Zoya. Her parents were Indian, and they lived in London. Compared to Seattle, Emma thought London seemed glamorous. The last time she’d seen her, Zoya had been a quiet, bookish girl with baggy clothes and large glasses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam’s mom had married an Australian, and they moved to Perth. She remembered Liam as a slightly chubby boy who tagged along with them everywhere. They’d been good friends when he was little, but as they grew up, Liam had become awkward around her and Zoya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the hotel lobby, the adults greeted each other as if no time had passed. However, it took Emma a moment to recognize her friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya had grown into a striking woman. The glasses were gone, and so were the baggy clothes. She tossed her head and waves of black hair cascaded down her brown shoulders. She wore a simple yellow tank top and flowy white skirt, but made it look elegant. Compared to Emma’s skinny frame, Zoya seemed to be all curves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, Zoya?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Emma!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The girls hugged each other warmly, skipping over three years apart with big smiles and confidence that their bond would renew itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The changes to Liam were no less drastic. Gone was the chubby, awkward little boy. He was dressed in skinny jeans and a grey t-shirt with a faded band logo. He brushed aside his careless mop of brown hair and grinned at her and Zoya. Then he gestured over his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is my cousin Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh my. Nolan was tall, with broad shoulders and shoulder-length sun-bleached hair. His chin was covered in stubble, and his eyes twinkled with an easy confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“G’day,” Nolan nodded at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh,” Emma stumbled, “Nice to meet you, Nolan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“C’mon, mate,” Nolan said, clapping Liam on the back. “Let’s go check out the waves, I heard there’s good surfing here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they loped off, Emma shot a look at Zoya, who raised her eyebrows, and they both dissolved into a fit of giggles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s so cute,” Zoya smiled. “He brought a friend so he wouldn’t have to follow the girls around.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t mind. I’m looking forward to watching Nolan. Surf, I mean. Watching him surf.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh,” Zoya smirked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, kids,” her dad said, bustling up and handing them keycards. “Here you go. Where are the boys?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I dunno, they said something about looking at the ocean.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, well, you two can give them their keys and show them where the room is.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; room? I thought Zoya and I had a room and Liam would be in another?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was the plan. But there’s some sort of convention or something happening, and the hotel overbooked. Your Mom’s reading them the riot act since we all made reservations months ago. The best we could swing was four rooms with a single queen bed in each.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One bed? Dad, you can’t be serious. There’s no way we can all share one bed. Did you see Liam brought his cousin?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, it’s that, or share a room with your parents, and since this &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; an anniversary trip…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ew, Dad!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s what I thought,” he laughed. “It’ll be fine, you kids are practically siblings. The boys can sleep on the floor, and you two can share the bed. I’ll have the hotel send up some extra pillows and blankets. Don’t worry, we’re in paradise! The room’s just for sleeping. You’ll spend all your time on the beach anyway.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoya and Emma shared a skeptical look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The room was tiny. The four of them stood around the bed. There was nowhere else &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt; stand. Next to the door was a window with a view of the beach. On the opposite wall was a small closet and the bathroom. There was just enough space on either side of the bed for matching nightstands with lamps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is some bullshit,” Liam groused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Relax, mate,” Nolan grinned. “We’ll be spending all our time on the beach.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s what my dad said,” Emma ventured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Smart man!” Nolan winked at her, and Emma felt her cheeks flush.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So we have to sleep on the floor?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s good for your back,” Nolan laughed. “Stop being such a downer. Make yourself a nest with these, and we’ll go for a walk while the girls get settled.” He thrust a pile of blankets and pillows into Liam’s arms. “Here, I’ll even take the side by the bathroom door so you don’t have to.” With that, he started spreading a few blankets on the floor, whistling as he did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma claimed the side of the bed closer to Nolan, which Zoya generously pretended not to notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma had always been a light sleeper, so she wasn’t surprised when something woke her up in the middle of the night. She tried to figure out what it was without looking. She could hear Zoya’s quiet breathing. The hum of the air conditioner. The distant sound of the ocean. And something else she couldn’t place. A quiet rustling, perhaps? Blearily, she opened her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The room was dimly lit by moonlight, painting everything in muted blues. Zoya was asleep facing her, lips slightly parted. She thought the sound seemed to be coming from behind her. Maybe one of the boys was moving around? She rolled over to look, but whatever it was stopped. Mentally shrugging, she tried to go back to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long, it started again. She blinked the sleep from her eyes to see more clearly. The closet was closed, and the bathroom door was open. No one in there. She could see Nolan asleep on the floor. He’d gone to bed without a shirt, and she was vaguely disappointed his sheet was pulled up to his neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh! There was movement under his sheet. The last vestiges of her drowsiness fell away. Now that she looked, she realized Nolan was only pretending to be asleep. He was lying on his back, and his eyes were closed, but he was obviously touching himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma bit her lip and watched, trying to visualize what he was doing under the sheet. It was tented over his erection. His right arm was moving. She wished she could see more. Every few seconds, he tensed his legs and exhaled softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wondered what it would be like to straddle one of his thighs while he was doing it. Very slowly, trying not to make any noise, she pressed her hand between her legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His breathing was becoming more strained as he stroked more urgently. What was he thinking about? Some bleached-blonde surfer girl from back home, sucking his cock? She wondered what he tasted like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thought made her squeeze her legs together. She imagined the look of hunger in his eyes as she wrapped her lips around him. As if sensing her thought, he strained his body, causing the sheet to pull a bit lower. She could see the muscles tensing in his exposed shoulders, and felt an echo of that tension in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He exhaled again, just a little louder this time, and his hand moved faster. Emma watched, fascinated, as he bent his knees, causing the sheet to slip lower. She imagined licking his nipples, and caressing his now-exposed abdomen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please, she thought, willing him to kick the sheet off entirely. Don’t you feel constrained? Wouldn’t the cool air feel nice on your skin? Come on, show me, show me, show me. She imagined she was projecting the idea straight into his brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stifled a groan and lifted his hips. The sheet slipped even lower! It was barely covering his pelvis now. She stared hungrily at the trail of dark hair leading down from his belly button. What would it be like to trace it with her fingers? To reach lower, and wrap her hand around the base of his cock. She imagined kissing him as he frantically thrust into her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He seemed to be mumbling under his breath. She strained to hear, but couldn’t make it out. His hand was flying now, up and down the full length of his shaft. She tried to hear her name in what he was breathing, and her insides clenched at the thought. With every frantic stroke, it seemed like the edge of the sheet was slipping. Just a little lower, she pleaded silently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, he went completely rigid, lifting his ass off the ground. She watched with delight as the sheet finally pulled back enough to reveal everything. Emma stifled a surprised gasp. One hand was holding his boxers pulled down, and the other was wrapped around his cock. His mouth opened in a silent moan. A thick rope of cum erupted from the tip. It seemed to glow in the moonlight as it arced up to his abdomen. He let out a ragged breath as shot after shot of his cum fell on his stomach. At last, he relaxed, breathing heavily and dropping his hands to his sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emma longed to touch him, to run her fingers through the hot, sticky mess. She imagined how it would feel to press her body against his. What he would smell like. How his eyes would look deep into hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wait, he &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; looking at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shit! She closed her eyes quickly, and tried to breathe slowly. Could he even see her in the dim light? Was he even really looking? Maybe he was just lying there in a post-orgasmic haze, staring vaguely in her general direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She hoped he hadn’t noticed her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mostly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes later, she heard him stand up and walk into the bathroom. Only once the door was closed did she finally relax and roll away. Facing Zoya again, who had slept through everything, she bit her lip. This was going to be a fun week.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night At Robotics Camp: an erotic college romp</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/one-wild-night/"/>
		<published>2024-04-10T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/one-wild-night/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="college sex" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="coach" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Coach Samantha has brought her senior robotics team to a competition at MIT. Her students have a golden opportunity tomorrow, if only she can get them to go to sleep! But this squad of frisky youths are determined to sneak around behind her back, and Coach Jake’s advances are becoming more appealing by the minute…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This collection of hot stories all take place on the same night, from different perspectives, each building on the last. Come along as Sam gets closer to Jake, Lucia sneaks a boy in, Kara has a surprise encounter, Marcy slips into her girlfriend’s room, and Rylie finds someone to relieve her frustration.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CW3C7BCF"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>I Won’t Tell, If You Give Me Your Panties</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/give-me-your-panties/"/>
		<published>2024-04-07T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/give-me-your-panties/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="microfiction" />
    <category term="panties" />
    <category term="kissing" />
    <category term="teasing" />
    <category term="wedding" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/give-me-your-panties-YwvKmBfwjc-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Weddings make me horny. So when he caught me sneaking a joint, I gave him an opening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t tell on me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I won’t,” he said, eyes twinkling boldly, “if you give me a kiss… and your panties.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cheeky,” I murmured, and eagerly pulled his lips to mine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I should’ve asked for more,” he realized a few minutes later, when I handed him my damp underwear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, you should have,” I teased, knowing he would follow as I walked away.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Meet Me in the Supply Closet</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/meet-me-in-the-supply-closet/"/>
		<published>2024-04-03T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-04-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/meet-me-in-the-supply-closet/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="quickie" />
    <category term="coworker" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="work" />
    <category term="closet" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/meet-me-in-the-supply-closet-b48gywVw1--512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Standing naked in the dark, I shivered with anticipation. Any second now, I knew he was going to turn that knob and slip into the janitor’s supply closet to join me. I couldn’t wait to feel his lips on mine. His hands on my body. His cock in my pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both our teams were working late, stuck trying to meet a ridiculous deadline imposed by management. I’d watched him across the dining area, eating the company-provided pizza dinner with his teammates. He made eye contact once, but quickly looked away, afraid of revealing our illicit office romance. I crunched my salad and sent him a text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Meet me in the supply closet in 15 minutes. Leave the light off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I saw his expression when he read my message. Watched him resist the urge to look at me as he sent a thumbs-up in response. I told my team I needed to get some air, and excused myself. Ten minutes later, I was folding my clothes and placing them on a shelf next to some cleaning supplies. At last, I turned out the light and waited, heart pounding, for him to arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The door opened, just enough to let him step in, silhouetted in the light from the mostly empty office as he closed the door behind him. I stood to one side, in the shadows, and when he reached for the light switch, I stopped him. He stiffened in surprise, but when I pulled his hand to my bare breast, he eagerly moved closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fumbled to unbutton his shirt, reaching inside to fondle his chest. Unable to see in the dark, my other senses seemed sharper. He smelled pleasantly musky, as if he’d been working out. His chest hair felt coarser against my breasts, his stubble rougher as I leaned in to kiss him. He growled as I unfastened his belt and pants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock swelled in my hand as I squeezed him to his full girth. I gasped as he throbbed my palm. He had never felt larger. His hands moved urgently over my body, roughly fondling my tits, squeezing my ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I kissed him again as I started stroking his shaft. He grunted, and I felt his fingers tangle in my hair. His tongue attacked mine, and I felt his need. He wanted me so badly. His cock twitched with his heartbeat, thrusting urgently into my grip. I felt a sticky smear of precum against my palm, and rubbed it into his hot skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He pushed me down, then. I opened my mouth to protest, but he filled it with his cock before I could say anything. He tightened his grip on my hair and encouraged me to take him deeper. His girth strained my mouth, and I struggled to relax my jaw. He tasted strongly masculine, and despite myself, I was incredibly turned on. Some part of me wanted him to use me like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wrapped both hands around his shaft, stroking and caressing as he began to work my head up and down. I couldn’t believe I was letting him do this. With each movement, he worked his cock a bit deeper. I choked, and he backed off for only a moment before going back to fucking my mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I let out an embarrassing moan and tried to swallow him deeper, reaching to cup his balls. He grunted and pushed harder, pressing my nose into his pelvis. I gagged, and he slipped deeper, letting out a long, low groan. I dug my fingernails into his thighs as his cock throbbed in my throat. After what felt like a very long time, he withdrew, leaving me coughing and wiping drool from my chin. Part of me wanted to be upset, but it was impossible to deny the wetness dripping down my thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, he pulled me to my feet, spinning me around and pressing our bodies together. I felt his hot skin against my back and squirmed with his cock wedged between my cheeks. He mauled my tits, pulling on my nipples until I had to stifle a squeal. He sucked on my neck, sometimes biting me, until I was panting, reaching back to squeeze his ass and encourage him to grind against me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t tell how many fingers he shoved inside me because I was so sensitive that they felt thicker than usual. I let out an embarrassingly needy moan, and rocked my hips to press against his palm. He ground the heel of his hand against my clit and began thrusting in and out of me. If I hadn’t been so dripping wet, it would have been too much, but he didn’t hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With one hand gripping my tit, his lips locked against my neck, his cock grinding against my ass, and his thick fingers fucking me relentlessly, all I could do was hold on. I dug my fingernails into his skin and tried not to scream as he made me cum. In the dark, I saw fireworks of red and gold. Hot liquid gushed over his fingers, splattering on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I could catch my breath, he kicked my feet apart, spreading my legs. Eagerly, I braced myself against the nearest shelf as I felt him rub his swollen head against me. With no hesitation, he thrust inside, my sopping wet pussy offering no resistance. His girth spread me open, stretching me almost painfully. I don’t remember ever feeling so full before. He bottomed out inside me and I groaned, impaled on his throbbing cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immediately, he started fucking me. It was wild. Intense. Animalistic. His hands gripped my hips and screwed me against him with every thrust. All I could do was hold on to the shelf. My legs felt weak, and I knew I would collapse if I let go. I heard a barking sound and realized it was me, grunting and squealing every time he slammed into me. In my peripheral vision, I saw flares and sparks and stars. I came again, hard, clenching around his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He must have known I was going to scream because he clamped his hand over my mouth. I hollered, spasming and shaking uncontrollably in his grip. When I stopped, he shoved his fingers deep in my mouth. I moaned around them, as aftershocks rolled through my body, radiating out from my pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt him stiffen behind me, the pace of his thrusting becoming more urgent. He grunted, letting me know without words he was about to finish. I nodded, desperate to feel him throbbing inside me. He pulled his fingers from my mouth, and slapped my ass, hard. I squealed and clenched around him, and he moaned loudly. His grip on my hips tightened, and I felt him start twitching, filling me up. I gasped and squirmed as he held me screwed tightly against him, rocking in place. When he finally released me, he staggered back against the other shelf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His hot cum ran out of me, dripping down my thigh, and I collapsed to my knees. I was panting with exertion and my heart was pounding loudly in my ears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I heard him pulling his pants up and buckling his belt. He put a hand on my shoulder as I tried to get to my feet, encouraging me to sit and catch my breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I could say anything, he opened the door and slipped out. That seemed rude, but I was feeling too euphoric to care. After a while, I turned the light on, and laughed at the cum splattered all over the floor. I felt giddy as I found some paper towels to clean myself and our mess. Then I got dressed and went back to work, where my team was confused by my unexpected good mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That night, after we finally wrapped up and everyone went home, I texted him from bed:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, that was incredible.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right? For real, that was the best blowjob I’ve ever had in my life.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you! You’ve never been so forceful with me before. I really liked it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m not sure that I would say forceful, but I’m glad you liked it. I can’t believe you let me cum in your mouth. You always told me you hate that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? You didn’t cum in my mouth, you came inside me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I fucked you bent over the packing table, and when I was about to cum, you swallowed it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you talking about? You fucked me standing up against the shelf full of cleaning supplies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cleaning supplies? Wait, what supply closet were you in?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The janitor’s supply closet by the bathrooms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“WTF. I was in the office supply closet by the printers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, what? Who did you fuck?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who did YOU fuck?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At that point, we finally realized that we weren’t the only ones having a secret office fling, or the only couple who had misunderstood which supply closet to meet in.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 6: Rylie</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/6-rylie/"/>
		<published>2024-03-30T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/6-rylie/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="anal" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="anal creampie" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Rylie sighed, and kicked her covers off again. It was impossible to sleep in this dorm room. Without her blackout curtains, it seemed intolerably bright. The temperature was somehow both too hot and too cold. She missed her weighted blanket. And with no white noise machine, all she could hear was the sound of the lesbians fucking in the next room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy, her roommate, had slipped out almost an hour ago to meet her girlfriend, Bonnie, and they’d been going to town on the other side of the thin wall ever since. Rylie had a moment of hope when she heard Coach Sam come to their door and tell them to go to sleep, but they’d just gone right back to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie wished she’d packed earplugs. Or a vibrator. She squeezed her thighs together, confusingly aroused by Bonnie’s cries of pleasure. Idly, she caressed her breasts, imagining the two girls kissing her. She tried to picture Marcy licking down her stomach and nuzzling past her pubes to gently spread her open…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meh. The fantasy wasn’t doing it for her. Listening to them fuck was enough to get her horny, but not enough to get her off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled onto her side and pulled up one of her favorite porn videos on her phone. The girl’s shoulder-length brunette hair made her look a bit like Rylie. She dragged the play indicator to the best part. A big guy was behind her, gripping her hips and jackhammering her. The girl’s cheek was mashed into the mattress, and she was grunting with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie slipped a hand into her underwear and teased a finger between her lips. She didn’t really care for the guy in the video. He was too veiny, and his leathery skin was covered in fading tattoos. He slapped her ass, mumbled dumb porn phrases, and fucked like a machine. But Rylie didn’t care because the best part of the video was about to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The girl cried out as her eyes rolled back in her head and she started spasming. As a genuine orgasm washed over her, for just a moment, she forgot to perform. The porn star facade dropped away, and she was simply a woman overcome by stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip and dipped her finger deeper inside. The girl in the video blinked and quickly snapped back into character, loudly squealing and begging the guy to fuck her harder. Rylie rewound to watch her cum again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She played it three times through. At the end of the third time, she let it keep playing. Through the wall, Marcy was moaning loudly, and Rylie felt a growing heat in her core. The guy in the video pulled out, repositioned himself, and the girl enthusiastically begged him to fuck her ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie imagined herself in the girl’s position. Feeling rough hands spread her cheeks, and the pressure of a cock against her back door. The girl squealed and gripped the sheet tightly as he thrust forward. She urged him to go slower, then groaned, looking directly into the camera as he filled her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie knew what that felt like. Being stretched out as her body resisted the intrusion. She hadn’t had real anal with a guy yet, but she had a dildo at home that she regularly practiced with. Once she was able to get past the initial tightness, the resulting stimulation was intense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, the camera angle changed to a closeup of the guy’s ass. Ugh. She didn’t understand why anyone would choose that angle. Annoyed, she closed the video. Marcy and Bonnie loudly continued to fuck each other senseless on the other side of the wall. Rylie groaned in frustration. She was turned on, but not quite in the right headspace. Getting off was going to take too much work. She wished there was a guy here to help focus her arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she couldn’t take it anymore and walked out the door to the bathroom. The lights buzzed annoyingly as she washed her hands. She stuck out her tongue at her reflection, which was dressed in an oversized button-up pajama shirt and white panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she stepped back into the hall, she hesitated, reluctant to return to her room. Bonnie and Marcy were much less audible out here. Apparently, the door did a better job of blocking sound. She was considering what to do when she caught some movement in her peripheral vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She peered down the hall. After the brightly lit bathroom, her eyes hadn’t adjusted yet, and she couldn’t make out what had attracted her attention. Slowly, she padded toward the common room. Peeking out, she could see the coaches had fallen asleep on the couch watching a late night show, but there was no sign of any movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then she caught it again. Down the hallway on the other side of the common room. Someone was barely visible standing by one of the doors, as if hesitating to open it. For a moment, she felt self-consciously aware that she wasn’t wearing any pajama bottoms. But given the choice between seeing who else was still awake, or going back to her room to listen to Bonnie and Marcy fuck, it was an easy decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moved through the common room like a ghost and entered the dark hallway. As she got closer, she recognized Ian. He was wearing boxers and a t-shirt, and had his back to her. His hand was on the handle of the door, which was cracked open. She could hear quiet moaning coming from the room. Fuck, was everyone in this place having sex but her?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sneaked up behind him and peeked around to look through the narrow opening. Inside, she could see Wally and Amy fucking. Amy was on her back, with her legs wrapped around Wally as he thrust frantically. The sight was so distracting that it took her a moment to realize Ian had his hand down his boxers, stroking his hard cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bit her lip. This was so fucking hot. Before she knew she was doing it, she stepped closer, brushing against Ian’s arm. He jumped in alarm, but she quickly held a finger to his lips. Once she was sure he was going to be quiet, she slipped in front of him so she could see more clearly through the cracked door. Ian hesitated a moment, then looked over her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tried to avoid pressing against her, obviously worried she would notice his erection. Too late for that, Rylie thought. Amy was moaning with each thrust, and Rylie felt her arousal climbing. She turned her head to whisper in Ian’s ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought you two were gonna hook up. Why’s she fucking Wally?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ian opened his mouth to reply, then simply shrugged as he watched Amy writhe under his best friend. Rylie grinned and leaned back against him, pressing her ass into his erection. He gasped and started to pull away, but she grabbed his hand and brought it to her chest to keep him there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does it turn you on to watch them?” She breathed the question, squeezing her breast with his hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He swallowed and shrugged again, but the way his cock twitched between her cheeks said more than words. She wiggled her butt, rubbing against him as she pulled his other hand to her chest. She squeezed her thighs together, excited to find an outlet for her desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It turns &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt; on,” she purred. Ian squeezed her breasts more firmly. Her nipples stiffened under his palms, sending little crackling sparks down her spine. He pressed forward, grinding his cock into her, causing her underwear to pull taut, and she gasped softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy was clawing at Wally’s back, demanding he fuck her harder, deeper, faster. Rylie watched in delight as she saw the tell-tale signs of Amy’s approaching orgasm. The blonde’s legs were wrapped around his waist, and she was eagerly meeting his thrusts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ian was humping Rylie’s ass frantically, gripping her tits, his breath hot against her ear. She felt her insides clench, and her wetness soak into her panties as the gusset pulled tight with each thrust. Urgently, she reached down to rub her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, Wally rolled off Amy, to her obvious frustration. Rylie and Ian froze, praying they didn’t notice the door was cracked open. Wally was mumbling something, but Amy told him to shut up and climbed on top of him. Her back was to the door, and Wally only had eyes for her tits. Relieved, Rylie started unbuttoning her shirt. It was awkward with one hand, but Ian helped, pulling it open so he could touch her directly. His hands were hot against her skin. She reached up to grab his hair, pulling his face down her kiss her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie watched as Amy rolled her hips, riding Wally in pursuit of her denied climax. She rocked forward, trying to stimulate her clit. Wally raised his head to suck on her nipples, and Amy groaned, pulling him to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ian’s cock throbbed. He grunted, and sucked harder on her neck, making her squirm. In the room, Wally stiffened under Amy and cried out, but she covered his face with her hand, shoving her fingers in his mouth, telling him to let her cum first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie wanted more. She turned around and dropped to her knees, tugging Ian’s boxers down. He leaned against the wall as she wrapped her lips around his head. The salty taste of his precum was mixed with another flavor it took her a moment to recognize. Surprised, she released his cock and looked up at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ian!” She whispered in a mock outrage. “Whose pussy am I tasting?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh,” Ian looked guilty until he realized she wasn’t upset. His response was barely audible. “Kara’s?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, that was a surprise. Lucky for him, she didn’t mind the taste. Rylie grinned and pointedly licked up his shaft like a popsicle. She would never have guessed Kara had the guts to seduce Ian, especially after Amy had spent all day flirting with him. Did Amy know? Did she jump Wally to get back at Ian? Is that why he was standing in the hall stroking his cock, still covered in Kara’s cum, as he watched Amy fuck his best friend? Rylie realized she’d involved herself in a complicated situation. Not that she was going to stop now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her hands moved wetly around the base of his shaft as she swallowed him deeper. He watched her with lust-filled eyes, trying not to make any noise. With one hand, she reached back, lightly teasing behind his balls. He tensed up, squirming, as she eased a finger between his cheeks. He looked like he might protest, but she sucked harder, and was rewarded with a squirt of precum on her tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the room, she heard Amy squealing as she started to cum. They didn’t have long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie bobbed her head excitedly, savoring the combined flavors of sex in her mouth, and worked her finger deeper in Ian’s ass. He squirmed and grabbed her hair, shoving his cock into her throat. She gagged, and used her free hand to push back on his stomach, trying to keep him from going too deep. He thrust urgently, fucking her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was going to finish soon, she could tell. Part of her wanted to make him climax right here. To keep going until his cock swelled and filled her mouth with cum. But, no, she wanted more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled away, gasping. Ian stifled a surprised noise as she removed her finger. His cock twitched urgently, and another drop of precum drooled out. She got to her feet and pulled him into a rough kiss that was less romantic and more a declaration of intent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ian,” she said huskily, “Do you want to fuck me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grinning, she grabbed him by the cock and led him down the hall. Her shirt was hanging open, and the cool air felt good on her bare skin. Her panties were soaked. Ian’s cock throbbed in her hand. Breathlessly, they ran into her room and quickly discarded their clothes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She climbed onto the bed on her hands and knees, and he followed, kneeling behind her. Eagerly, she positioned him between her lips, coating his head in her wetness. Before she could say anything, he thrust forward, burying his cock in her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” she cried out, arching her back. For a long moment, he held his cock deep inside her, twitching. She gasped, savoring the way he filled her, and tense with anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then he started fucking her, hard and fast. After being frustratingly aroused for so long, her body blossomed around his cock. On every backstroke, her pussy clenched, unwilling to let him go, and eagerly welcoming him back with each thrust. Her nipples dragged on the blanket as she rocked in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached between her thighs to touch her clit. It protruded from its hood, swollen and demanding stimulation. She ground her palm against it, and reached further back to caress his cock as it entered her. His thick shaft was hot to the touch and slick with her wetness. As she pressed against her clit, colors danced behind her eyes, and everything rose to a sudden crescendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She grabbed a fistful of sheet and screamed into her pillow. Her first orgasm crashed over her like a tidal wave. Ian groaned as she pushed back against him, wanting more. He squeezed her hips and held his cock deep inside as her walls rippled along his length. Her entire body went rigid, until she shuddered and collapsed on the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy fuck,” Ian groaned as his cock slipped out of her with a wet squelch, her juices dripping off his tip. He rocked back on his haunches, one hand wrapped firmly around his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rylie could only moan in response. For several minutes, all she could do was squeeze her thighs together as the aftershocks rolled over her. Finally, she got up and flung her arms around his shoulders, kissing him passionately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, that was hot,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wow,” he agreed. “You came really hard, huh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I did. I needed that. Marcy and Bonnie were fucking on the other side of the wall earlier, and it got me all kinds of turned on. And then I saw you jerking off in the hallway to Amy and Wally…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” he trailed off, clearly unwilling to discuss that situation, which suited Rylie fine. She resumed kissing him to get his attention back on her. When she felt his cock twitching and bumping into her hip, she grinned and put it between her thighs. He took the hint and grabbed her ass, thrusting forward so he rubbed against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ian,” she mumbled between kisses. “Did Kara let you cum in her?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” he gasped, his shaft gliding across her slick lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to cum in me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck,” he groaned, slowing down long enough to look her in the eyes. “Can I?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, but not in my pussy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” He looked confused. “Then… where?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want it in my ass,” she blurted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” He blinked. “I mean, yeah!” She felt his cock throb against her. “Fuck yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, then I want you behind me again. Start in my pussy, but play with my ass, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, they got back into position. Rylie moaned happily when he slipped back inside her, and for a few minutes, they fucked like that. It felt good, but knowing what was coming next had her heart pounding with excitement. Finally, she felt a tentative probing against her back door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, just like that, nice and slow,” she moaned, as he eased the tip of his thumb into her tight opening. She rocked back against him, encouraging him to keep gently fucking her as he pushed deeper. She let out a long, low groan as he kept going, until his thumb was fully buried in her ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that good?” He asked, a bit hesitantly. She swallowed a moment of irrational annoyance, wanting him to just know how to read her signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, just—ah—just keep fucking me like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He quickly fell into a rhythm, pushing his thumb deeper when he pulled his cock out, and then reversing. She felt a quickly growing heat in her core as he squeezed her hip and fucked her slowly and firmly. Her fingers moved back to her clit, adding more stimulation, and soon she felt her legs stiffen, as she clenched around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ian, fuck—oh!—that’s good, keep doing that—ah!—if you keep going like that, I think I can cum again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie,” he groaned, “you feel so goddamn good around my cock.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck, she loved this. The evening had started out frustrating, but now that she was up on this plateau of arousal, it didn’t take much to trigger a climax. Now, she felt deliciously filled, every thrust bringing her closer. She laid her head on the pillow and closed her eyes, focused on her approaching orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It came on slower than the first, less like a tsunami and more like the tide rolling in, getting higher with every wave. When it finally crested, she moaned happily into the pillow, as pleasure washed over and through her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I’m cumming,” she breathed. “I’m cumming, I’m cumming, I’m cumming…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She could tell Ian was getting close, too. His grip on her hip was a little more urgent, his thrusts a bit more insistent. It was time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” she breathed, raising back up on her elbows, “Now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Ian pulled out of her and pressed the head of his cock against her ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go slow,” she warned him, then groaned as he pushed forward. There was a moment of resistance, then his head slipped inside. They both moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Slow, slow, slow,” she repeated. “Uh! Yes. Like that, nice and—Ah!—nice and slow. Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you okay?” He paused, halfway in, the thickest part of his shaft stretching her out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she groaned, “It just—fuck—takes a minute to get used to.” She took some deep breaths. “Okay, go ahead.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then suddenly he was all the way in. She gripped the sheet tightly, trying to relax around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” He exclaimed, “Your ass is so tight!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She could only moan in answer. He was bigger than her dildo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I…?” he asked, trailing off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she gasped. “Yeah, do it,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt his hand grip her hip firmly, and he slowly pulled partway out. She squirmed at the confusing mix of sensations, and then moaned when he pushed back in. Slowly, he started pulling her back to meet him as he pushed forward. Her body seemed to be crackling with stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Oh, fuck!” She squealed, reaching to rub her clit again. “Your cock feels so big in my ass!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He quickened his pace, thrusting more eagerly into her. She started seeing flashes of color each time he bottomed out. Every flick of her clit sent a buzzing arc of delight rolling up her spine. She shoved two fingers into her soaking wet pussy, needing something to squeeze. Her ass was stretched out and achingly full. Every movement he made sent waves of pleasure rippling through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, please, fuck my ass,” she begged. The pillow was in the way, so she threw it to the floor. Her cheek was pressed into the mattress, mouth open, panting with exertion, fingers flying on her clit. He was squeezing her hips roughly, no longer trying to go slow or be careful. He thrust forcefully, grunting and cursing, using her for his need. That thought drove her over the edge. Several intense orgasms rolled through her, one after another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Fuck my ass!” She cried loudly, echoing the lines from her favorite video. “Take me! Fuck me harder!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rylie,” he grunted, “I’m gonna cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it, Ian! Oh god, do it! Cum in my ass! Fill me up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh! Ah! Ah! Ah!” He thrust forward one last time and held her firmly against him as his cock pumped cum deep inside her. She laughed and screamed and clawed at the mattress, completely overwhelmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he released her, and his cock slipped out, making her squeak. He sat back on the bed, breathing heavily, and she clamped her hand tightly over her vulva. Her insides clenched in one final spasm of pleasure, making her giggle as some of his hot cum squeezed out over her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, Rylie, that was amazing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She grinned as she dug a packet of wet wipes out of her bag. She passed one to him and set about cleaning herself up, humming happily to herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon, they cuddled under her blanket. She had her head on his shoulder and her thigh thrown over his. Finally, she felt drowsy and ready to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Rylie?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is it cool if I stay here? I’m not sure if Amy’s still in my room.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Probably a good idea,” she murmured. “But you’ll have to sneak out in the morning, so the coaches don’t see you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, okay.” He hesitated for a long moment. “Um, would you want to, like, go out sometime? Get some coffee or something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That depends,” she smiled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“On what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whether you’ll fuck me like that again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! I mean, uh, yeah, of course, like, anytime.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then, sure. And forget the coffee,” she purred. “Now go to sleep.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 5: Marcy</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/5-marcy/"/>
		<published>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/5-marcy/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="pussy eating" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Why are you sitting way over there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy grinned at the text. It was from her girlfriend, Bonnie, who was currently sitting across from her at the airport. They were waiting at the crowded departure gate with the rest of their team to board a plane to MIT for the robotics competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry,” she texted back. “I got distracted because SOMEONE hasn’t stopped texting me since we got off the bus, and when I looked up, all the other seats were taken.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So?” Bonnie grinned. “Get over here and tell Amy to fuck off and sit somewhere else. Or just come sit on my lap.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t think Coach Sam would like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who cares what she likes, I want you on top of me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy looked around to make sure no one was looking at her phone. Bonnie’s texts had been escalating from playful to explicit, and she was a little worried someone would see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she responded, “maybe they’ll let us share a room.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, that would be amazing.” Bonnie winked at her. “I’d keep you up all night. You could send me home covered in hickeys.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re making it hard to think about anything else.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t help it, you’re so fucking hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unconsciously, Marcy ran a hand through her dark hair. She’d recently gotten an overtly queer asymmetric cut and had been worried about what Bonnie, always the more traditionally femme of the two, would think. Turns out, she had nothing to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey,” Bonnie sent, “guess what I’m wearing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing Marcy would immediately look up, Bonnie casually stretched, her crop top lifting just enough to tease a glimpse of pink lace. She was wearing the sexy longline bra they’d bought together on a memorable shopping trip that had ended with a lap dance in the dressing room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love the way that looks on you,” Marcy texted, “It turns me on so much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good, because your leather jacket gets me wet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Be patient, Bon-bon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want to be patient. I want you to pull my hair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shifted in her seat as Bonnie shot her a wicked look, licking her lips as she adjusted her ponytail, tugging her blonde hair back just a bit harder than necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop!” Marcy mouthed the word, glancing nervously at Coach Sam, a few seats away, worried they’d get caught. Bonnie just grinned and picked up her phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I need your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Bonnie.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, fuck Bonnie! Now you’re getting it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re gonna get it,” she texted, weakly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get what? Your head between my thighs?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy squeezed her legs together, uncomfortably aware of how aroused she was becoming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie, please,” she texted. “I can’t make it through the flight if you get me all worked up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shot her a pleading look. Bonnie gave her an understanding smile. Then she stood up and started walking away, tucking her phone into the back pocket of her jean shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie,” Coach Sam called, “Where are you going?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just to the bathroom,” she replied without stopping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, well, listen for our flight announcement, we should be boarding soon!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy took a deep breath and tried to clear her head. Now that Bonnie was done texting, it was time to slow things down and make it through the flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her phone buzzed again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a photo of Bonnie from the bathroom stall. She was lifting her shirt and sticking out her tongue. Her dark nipples were clearly visible through the thin lace of her bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come see how wet I am.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck. Two more texts came one after another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Push me against the wall.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suck on my nipples.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She checked the time. Their flight would start boarding in ten minutes. They’d have to be quick. She responded with a running emoji and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Last stall, hurry.” Bonnie texted back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Marcy,” Coach Sam warned as she walked away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I know, I’ll be quick!” She broke into a jog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miraculously, the bathroom was nearly deserted. Almost all the stalls were unoccupied, and there was only one woman in a nice suit washing her hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy walked straight to the last stall. The door was closed but not locked, and she opened it to find Bonnie grinning at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They fell into each other’s arms, Marcy fumbling to lock the door, then pushing her girlfriend against the wall, urgently kissing her. They were both flooded with lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck, I’m glad you came,” Bonnie gasped, stifling a squeal as Marcy reached under her crop top to squeeze her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How could I not?” Marcy whispered, “You’re so goddamn sexy, and you’ve been teasing me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wasn’t teasing, I’m yours,” she purred, reaching under Marcy’s leather jacket to caress her sides and chest. “And I need your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remembering how little time they had, Marcy unbuttoned Bonnie’s shorts and reached into her panties. She was already squirming as Marcy worked a finger between her lips. As promised, she was already wet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” Bonnie whispered. But Marcy paused, making eye contact as she reached her other hand up to grip Bonnie’s ponytail. She nodded, and Marcy pulled, gently at first, but increasingly firmly, tipping her head back, before finally slipping her finger inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonnie immediately started gasping as Marcy fingered her and sucked on her neck. She arched her back, desperate for more. Marcy felt her lust surging as she released Bonnie’s hair and added a second finger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panting with each thrust of her fingers, Bonnie tugged up Marcy’s shirt and began kissing down her chest, scooping a breast from her strappy black bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We don’t have long,” Marcy exhaled, fingers buried in her girlfriend’s soaking pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rub my clit,” Bonnie panted, closing her lips around the brunette’s nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shifted her hand, pressing her palm against the sensitive bud. Bonnie rolled her hips, grinding against the pressure, moaning into Marcy’s breast, and moving urgently towards her release. Marcy moved her hand faster until Bonnie suddenly went stiff, releasing her nipple with a wet sound and gasped into her cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling her need surging, Marcy pulled her hand out and pushed Bonnie back against the wall, frantically kissing her. Urgently, she pulled up Bonnie’s top, wet fingers squeezing her breasts through the thin fabric, leaving her moaning and grabbing Marcy’s ass to pull her closer, grinding against her thigh—when they suddenly heard the final boarding announcement for their flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughing, they pulled their clothes back into place and ran out of the stall holding hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a very long flight, not made any easier by her damp underwear and the lingering scent of Bonnie on her fingers. Their seats were far apart, and she spent most of the time watching videos on her phone, trying to distract herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they finally arrived at the dorms that MIT provided, Marcy was disappointed but not surprised that the coaches put her and Bonnie in separate rooms. She was sharing a room with Rylie, and Bonnie was next door with Amy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her first stop was the restroom, to change into a dry pair of underwear, sports bra, soft t-shirt, and lounge pants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By eleven, Rylie was already in bed wearing a sleep mask, but Marcy was still too wound up to sleep. It was hours earlier than she normally went to bed. She found herself sitting on top of the covers, screwing around on her phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It buzzed with a text from Bonnie: “Still awake?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I can’t sleep this early.” She grinned and added, “Plus, you got me all worked up earlier.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, not sorry. You look so fucking hot in that leather jacket.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When do you think we can be alone again? Sucks they wouldn’t let us share a room. No love for the gays, I guess.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Soon, I hope. I can’t stop thinking about the way you took me at the airport.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t stop thinking about you during the flight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm tell me more.” Marcy could imagine Bonnie purring as she said it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shot a look toward her roommate, trying to judge if she was asleep yet. Rylie was rolled away, facing the wall, and breathing slowly… but then she scratched her arm and adjusted her pillow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was thinking about your lips around my nipple.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so fucking sexy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thinking about how you moved against me when I put my fingers in you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thinking about what I would do next.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to take off your top and push you down on the bed and suck on your tits.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yesss. What then?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kiss my way down your front and pull your panties down just enough to lick you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot. I love seeing you look up at me from between my legs. I want to run my fingers through your hair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’d pull your underwear off and finger you while I lick your clit. I won’t stop until you have to scream into a pillow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, I want that so bad. When you’re done, I wa”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy blinked at the screen. The text ended abruptly, and just when it was getting good. Probably, Bonnie was typing one-handed. She grinned, and looked at Rylie, trying to judge whether she could get away with doing the same when her phone buzzed again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“OMG get over here quick. Amy just left.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy sat bolt upright. Holy shit. Amy had been flirting aggressively with Ian all day long. If she’d snuck out, it was probably to go hook up with him somewhere. Which meant Bonnie was alone in the next room!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carefully, she padded barefoot toward the door. Rylie didn’t react. She was about to open it when she heard footsteps coming down the hall. Concerned it was Amy returning, she hesitated until she heard the bathroom door open and shut. After a moment, she slipped out, closing the door behind her as quietly as she could. There was no sign of anyone, though she could hear a TV playing in the common room. Cautiously, she opened the door to the next room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonnie was sitting up in bed, grinning from ear to ear. She was wearing grey sleep shorts and a pink tank top with no bra. Her nipples poked excitedly through the cotton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Marcy grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right?” Bonnie agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Babe, I heard someone come down the hall and go into the bathroom. Do you think it was Amy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe?” Bonnie shrugged. “She said she was going to the bathroom, but she had this look in her eyes like she thought she was being &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; clever. I mean, she obviously went to fuck Ian, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, for sure, she was all over him today.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, so,” Bonnie bit her lip. “Can we…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy climbed onto the bed, but Bonnie put a hand on her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if we’re wrong? What if Amy comes back?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She can watch,” Marcy replied with a grin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh really?” Bonnie laughed. “Well, if we’re fantasizing, why not ask her to join us?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hell no, I’m not sharing you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good answer. What if she tells Coach Sam?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Coach Sam can watch, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hm,” Bonnie considered, a twinkle in her eyes. “Okay, but for real, that’s super hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Marcy moved closer, nuzzling her neck. “You like the idea of an audience?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe… I’ve never really thought about it before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seems like you’re thinking about it now,” Marcy murmured, brushing Bonnie’s hair back and kissing her earlobe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yesss,” she purred, tilting her head back as Marcy kissed down her neck. “I’m imagining them sitting across from us, getting more and more turned on until they start touching themselves. Sam squeezing her tits. Amy with a hand down her shorts. Both of them staring at us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mm-hmm. But I don’t want to keep thinking about them. I want you to do what you were telling me about.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought you’d never ask.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giggling, Marcy pulled Bonnie’s top over her head and pushed her down on the bed. Her laughter turned to quiet moans as Marcy settled her weight between her thighs, grinding against her as they kissed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shifted downward, trailing kisses. She took Bonnie’s breasts in her hands and pulled a nipple into her mouth, rolling the other between her fingers. Bonnie gasped and squirmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shifting to the other breast, Marcy looked up, meeting Bonnie’s desire-filled eyes. As she moved her tongue in lazy circles, Bonnie moaned and dropped her head back onto the pillow, savoring the sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a minute, Bonnie wrapped her legs around her and pulled her back up into a kiss. Marcy ground against her pelvis, making her squeal. Frantically, Bonnie tugged at the black fabric of Marcy’s shirt, pulling it up. Marcy helped remove it and pulled Bonnie’s face into her cleavage. The blonde moaned happily, kissing and squeezing Marcy’s breasts through her bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, teasingly, Marcy moved back down Bonnie’s body, kissing her chest and stomach until finally reaching the waistband of her shorts. Bonnie nodded eagerly and lifted her hips to let Marcy pull them off, revealing polka-dot panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dropping the shorts on the floor, Marcy kissed along Bonnie’s thigh, stopping just short of her underwear to tease her, then getting to her feet and shimmying out of her lounge pants. Bonnie grunted in frustration and followed, dropping to her knees to kiss Marcy’s hips. Marcy gasped as Bonnie buried her face between her thighs, pressing into the fabric of her underwear. She felt a surge of lust and pulled Bonnie back up, kissing her deeply. Bonnie giggled and allowed herself to be pushed back down on the bed, pulling Marcy with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped and eagerly spread her legs as Marcy kissed slowly down her front to her hips. As promised, Marcy pulled down the fabric just far enough to brush her lips over Bonnie’s cleft. She made eye contact, the elastic straining under her chin as she kissed lower, nuzzling her nose into the triangle of well-trimmed hair, and flicking her tongue out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Bonnie gasped, running her fingers through Marcy’s hair. She rolled her hips, trying to adjust the angle, but her panties were in the way. Marcy’s eyes gleamed, and she kept teasing her mercilessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” Bonnie begged, gripping her hair tighter, and grinding against her chin. “Please, take them off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, since you asked so nicely,” Marcy purred as she backed up on her knees, pulling the panties with her, before crawling seductively up to kiss her deeply. Bonnie moaned around her tongue and wrapped her legs around Marcy’s ass, trying to pull her tighter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then Marcy was moving down again, kissing and licking as she went. She could tell Bonnie was excited, squeezing her breasts and squirming as she anticipated what came next. Finally, Marcy settled between her spread legs, licking slowly up her thigh, teasing her before moving inward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yes,” Bonnie purred, pinching her nipples as Marcy finally reached her goal, pushing her tongue between her girlfriend’s lips. Eagerly, she lapped up Bonnie’s creamy arousal before rolling her tongue into a tube and licking deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, yes,” Bonnie moaned, rocking back and forth as Marcy fucked her with her tongue. “My clit, ah! Please lick my clit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy moved up to trace tight circles around the erect bud. She slipped one, and then two fingers inside Bonnie’s pussy. She was moaning and panting, squirming and tensing, tangling her fingers in Marcy’s hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god! Yeah, right there, just like that!” Bonnie tightened her grip, pulling more urgently. Marcy curled her fingers, beckoning Bonnie’s orgasm as she arched her back, thrusting her pelvis against Marcy’s face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, oh fuck, I’m cumming!” Bonnie groaned as her pussy clenched around Marcy’s fingers over and over, until she collapsed back on the pillow, gasping for breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, Marcy worked her way up, kissing and licking, before rolling onto her back, pulling Bonnie on top, into a passionate kiss. Their tongues danced, and Bonnie moaned with pleasure at the taste of her own cum on Marcy’s lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God, you’re so fucking sexy,” Bonnie growled. Marcy arched her back to pull off her sports bra, eagerly tossing it to the floor. She moaned as Bonnie pulled her breast into her mouth. The blonde looked up at her with eyes full of desire, lips locked around her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You look so fucking hot like that,” Marcy purred. She rocked her hips, pushing upwards against Bonnie’s weight between her legs. “But take my underwear off, I want to feel you—ah!” She gasped as Bonnie immediately shimmied lower, rubbing and kissing through her panties. Her hot breath on the damp fabric made Marcy squirm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie, please,” she begged, until Bonnie took pity and hooked fingers under her waistband and pulled them down. She wasted no time, practically diving back between Marcy’s thighs, licking and kissing and rubbing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, that feels so good, babe!” Marcy was already groaning and tense, running her fingers through Bonnie’s hair, and pulling her closer. She realized that the long day of teasing had kept her on the edge, and her first orgasm was fast approaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, yeah,” she gasped, squeezing her breast as she rocked in place, grinding her pussy against Bonnie’s face. “Fuck, you’re gonna make me cum in your mouth so hard.” Bonnie moaned eagerly, thrusting her tongue deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh my god!” Marcy’s entire body tensed. She felt a release, and Bonnie squealed wetly. Waves of sensation rolled through her body, radiating from her core. Flares of color erupted behind her closed eyes as she rocked in place, holding Bonnie against her, until with a shudder, she pushed her away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have such a tasty pussy,” Bonnie giggled, wiping her chin as she sat back on her knees. Marcy could only breathe, shivering as the aftershocks rolled down her spine. She purred as she felt Bonnie moving up, swinging one leg over her hip to scissor her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you doing?” Marcy laughed, then let out a satisfied sigh as Bonnie pressed against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wanna try this,” Bonnie giggled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on—ah,” Marcy gasped as Bonnie started moving. “No one actually does this, it’s just a porn thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Says you,” Bonnie replied, a thoughtful expression on her face as she shifted, trying to find the right angle. “Just let me try, I’m curious.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It—oh!—It does feel nice, I guess,” Marcy conceded as their lips glided against each other. “I’m still all sensitive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, you came so fast, babe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s—oooh—it’s your fault, you kept me so turned on all day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here, like this,” Bonnie mumbled, grabbing one of Marcy’s legs and pulling it up onto her shoulder. “Oh, that feels good.” She held Marcy’s ankle and began grinding more urgently, thrusting against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, I like it when you rub your pussy on my clit like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not—ah!—Not bad for a porn move, huh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up, just—ooh—just keep doing that,” Marcy groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Roll your hips, babe, move like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah! Fuck yeah. Oh! This is going to make me cum…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it, cum all over my pussy,” Marcy urged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Oh. Uh. Ah!” Bonnie’s staccato gasping increased as she leaned into Marcy’s upright leg, rolling her hips, grinding and rubbing. Everything was slick and juicy and hot and sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, do it. Cum for me. Cum &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; me,” Marcy moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh… Fuck!” Bonnie cried out as she went rigid, then swore as her knee slipped, and she fell off the bed with a crash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bon!” Marcy yelped, rolling over. “Are you okay? Did you hurt yourself?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just my pride,” Bonnie groaned. She was sprawled on the floor, rubbing her elbow. “Fucking porn makes it look so easy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy stifled a giggle, but Bonnie met her eyes and they both started laughing. She climbed off the bed and pulled Bonnie into a hug. They held each other, laughing at the absurdity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, there was a knock at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Quick,” Bonnie hissed, “Get in the other bed!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frantically, they both dove into opposite beds, pulling the covers up just as the door opened to reveal Coach Sam. Marcy buried her face in the pillow, praying the dim moonlight was too dark for Sam to recognize her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girls, I know you’re excited, but you’ve got to go to sleep. I need you up and ready to rock first thing in the morning, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stunned, they could only mumble in agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright. Get some good rest.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam closed the door and they heard her footsteps moving away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh. My. God,” Bonnie whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Marcy agreed, sitting up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like, just for a second, I thought maybe she was here to, uh…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To watch?” Marcy snickered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Like, we were &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; talking about it, and then she shows up right when I’m about to cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe she didn’t notice it was me instead of Amy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can,” Bonnie giggled and sat up, throwing her blanket aside. “Did you see her shirt?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I had my face hidden in the pillow. What about it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The buttons were done up wrong and it looked like her bra was unhooked.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You don’t think…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah. Her hair was messed up, too. I bet she was getting lucky with Coach Jake when she came to see what the noise was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With Jake? Ew.” Marcy crossed over to sit next to Bonnie, who shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’s cute enough for a guy. And he clearly thinks she’s great.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever. Gross.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, alright,” Bonnie chuckled. “What would you rather talk about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Marcy considered, leaning in and kissing her neck. “You said you were about to cum before you fell over?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Bonnie purred. “I was so close. Your pussy felt really good on mine. But you know what I really want?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your fingers again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then turn around,” Marcy replied. Bonnie turned away and dropped onto her hands and knees. Marcy moved behind her, running her hands over her hips and ass. Bonnie arched her back to give Marcy better access and gasped as two fingers dipped inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” she purred, reaching between her legs to rub her clit. Marcy started moving in and out, coating her fingers in Bonnie’s wetness. She quickly increased her tempo, and Bonnie matched her pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” she gasped. “Fuck, that feels so good, babe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Marcy felt her fingers being squeezed. “You like getting fucked from behind?” Bonnie squealed as Marcy slapped her ass, squeezing and spreading her cheeks as she kept fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, you’re gonna make me cum again,” Bonnie moaned into the pillow. “Oh! Oh my god!” She started shaking, her insides clenching as her fingers rubbed tight, urgent circles around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh right there, right there, OH MY GOD, FUUUCK,” Bonnie screamed, muffled by the pillow. Marcy grinned and kept her fingers in place until Bonnie pulled away, still squirming and panting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, babe, that was so good,” Bonnie gasped, turning and kissing her. Marcy laughed and let herself be pushed onto her back. Bonnie grinned at her and moved to throw her leg over Marcy’s head in a 69 position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy gasped as Bonnie immediately started licking her clit. She responded in kind, wrapping her lips around Bonnie’s sensitive bud and sucking. Bonnie squealed and pushed her tongue into between Marcy’s lips. They went back and forth, distracting each other, seeing who could focus more. Marcy slapped Bonnie’s ass, and she responded by slipping her thumb into Marcy’s pussy. She gasped at the sudden intrusion, and grabbed Bonnie’s ass with both hands, spreading her cheeks and sucking on her clit. She lost her focus when she felt Bonnie easing a slender finger into her ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” Marcy groaned, feeling Bonnie’s thumb and finger separated by only a thin bridge of sensitive flesh. “Fuck, yeah, oh god.” She slapped Bonnie’s ass, hard, making her squeal into her clit, but she didn’t relent, and Marcy felt her insides beginning to clench around Bonnie’s digits. She lifted her head, burying her face in her girlfriend’s wetness, but immediately dropped back down, gasping as she felt the pressure building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you’re making me cum!” She squeezed Marcy’s ass and squirmed, rocking her hips, fucking against her fingers. Marcy was saying something, urging her on, but she couldn’t hear. She was only aware of the stimulation between her legs, the tongue lashing her clit, the pressure of their bodies against each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, yeah, oh, oh, oh god, oh fuck,” Marcy cried into Bonnie’s thigh. “Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me!” Fireworks were going off inside her brain. Lightning crackled through her nervous system. She came long and hard until she collapsed. Bonnie moved to snuggle up at her side, resting her head on Marcy’s shoulder and kissing her cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They lay together like that for a long time, kissing and caressing each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were both afraid to be the first to admit the inevitable fact that they couldn’t stay together all night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, Marcy did it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I should go.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nooo,” Bonnie protested sleepily. “Stay.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t. Amy could come back anytime.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t care.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, she’d tell Coach Sam, and she’d care.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmph,” Bonnie seemed to concede the point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reluctantly, Marcy stood up and gathered her scattered clothes. After pulling on her pants and shirt, she leaned over to kiss Bonnie goodnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm, you taste like sex,” Bonnie purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So do you, babe.” Marcy kissed her again and then went to the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she cracked it open. Just as she was about to step into the hall, she saw movement. Peeking out, she saw Rylie and Ian come down the hall. Rylie’s top was unbuttoned and billowed to reveal her bare breasts. Ian followed a step behind, and it took her a moment to realize she wasn’t holding his hand, but instead was pulling him eagerly down the hall by his erect cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blinking in surprise, she watched as Rylie led Ian to the door of the room she and Marcy shared, pulling him in after her. He had a dopey, horny expression on his face, and it was obvious they would be fucking as soon as the door was closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which meant she couldn’t go back to her room. Grinning, she closed the door and took her clothes back off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good news, babe,” she whispered as she slipped back under the blanket. “I’m staying here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yaaay,” Bonnie whispered, snuggling up to her. “Why?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just saw Rylie, and you’ll never believe who she was with.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Never mind,” Bonnie said drowsily. “Tell me in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Love you, Bon-bon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Love you too,” she mumbled, already falling back asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Ms. Sandstrom’s Assistant 5: The Coat Check Room</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/ms-sandstroms-assistant/5-coat-check-room/"/>
		<published>2024-03-15T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/ms-sandstroms-assistant/5-coat-check-room/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="submissive" />
    <category term="edging" />
    <category term="domination" />
    <category term="submission" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male submissive" />
    <category term="female submissive" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/coat-check-room-rIghmtdtB7-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Liz, stop,” I hissed, as she tried to lead me into the shareholder event on the first floor of our office building. “I can’t go in there like this!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“C’mon, Mike, no one’s gonna know.” She couldn’t quite keep a straight face as she said it, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I turned away as a small group of people in fancy clothes walked past us to the coat check. When they were gone, I gestured pointedly to my crotch. She stifled a laugh. My thin dress pants did little to conceal my erection. It twitched eagerly, as if aware of Liz’s attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s, uh,” she hesitated. “It’s not that noticeable.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come off it, if I walk in there like this I could get arrested.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh please, no one’s gonna call the cops.” She nodded politely at another couple walking up to the coat check as I turned away again. “You might end up having to talk to HR but trust me, those girls know how to party,” she laughed knowingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… That’s not the point, Liz! We need to talk to the research team about the pill!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They went home already. Besides, they said not to worry unless it lasts over eight hours.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s been seven!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Which is &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; than eight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can’t we go back upstairs to your office and take care of this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We ‘took care of it’ three times already!” She sighed. “…Look, I bought this dress special for tonight.” She gestured at the slinky red backless gown. She looked phenomenal and knew it. “Cheryl’s expecting me to make the rounds and talk to board members. I’m not gonna mess up my hair or makeup just to make you cum again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, then I’ll go take care of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, take a breath. The research team was clear. We could do it a couple times, but then we were supposed to find out how long it lasted. You’re freaking out about nothing. This can’t be the first time you’ve had a boner in public. Just, you know, cover it up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m telling you, I can’t go in there, Liz!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, fine.” She looked around and spotted the door to the coat check room. “Okay, come in here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened the door and pulled me in. The room was divided in two by a partial wall. On one side were several rolling wardrobe carts, shelves of cubbies, and a folding chair. On the other side was the coat check counter. A young blonde woman in a black dress shot us a curious look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hi Kara, thanks again for working the coat check tonight. This is Mike, he’s having a bit of a panic attack, so he’s gonna chill here while I go in, okay?” Kara nodded and turned her attention to a couple who had just walked up to hand her their jackets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike, that’s Kara. She’s the new front-desk girl. You just sit here and be calm. I bet once you get your mind off it, things will settle down and you can come to join me at the party. If not, I’ll be back to get you in a little while. Then I promise I’ll take you upstairs and it’ll be worth the wait, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded, and she gave me a quick kiss on the cheek and bustled out the door, greeting several people by name on her way into the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the next fifteen minutes, Kara hustled back and forth, hanging up coats and jackets, and handing claim tickets to partygoers. Eventually, the flow of guests slowed and stopped. Kara pulled her stool over to sit next to me and regarded me curiously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Panic attack, eh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not a panic attack,” I responded a bit too forcefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” she said, shrugging. “So, why are you hiding from your girlfriend?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s not my girlfriend, she’s my boss, and I’m not hiding, I just can’t go in there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why not?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exasperated, I pulled my hands away, so she could see the large tent in my pants, which had not settled down even a little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She grinned. “I see the problem. Does, uh, does this happen often?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I… look, you know what the company makes, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I’m aware,” she rolled her eyes. “It’s only the most famous sex toy company in the world.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right. But they’ve also got an R&amp;amp;D department, including a pharmaceutical team.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh. I never heard of that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Most people haven’t. They license stuff out or produce it through holding companies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, so I guess you took some kind of new boner pill?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not exactly. My boss, Liz, convinced me to take a pill designed to reduce the male refractory period.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you can do it again after finishing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded. “Liz told me this pill was practically ready for the market, and it would let me go several times in a row.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She laughed. “You make it sound like a work assignment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It kinda is?” I shrugged. “It’s a long story. I’m the assistant for the two women who run the company. This kinda stuff comes with the position.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So… you’re hooking up with Liz?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And Ms. Sandstrom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cheryl Sandstrom, the CEO of the company, and Elizabeth Holman, her second in command, are both fucking their shared assistant?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look, I dunno if I’m supposed to be telling anyone that. I’m kinda distracted right now. The point is, Liz had me try this pill, and it works. We did it three times in a row. Then Liz wanted to see how long it would last, I’ve been hard ever since, and I’m kinda going crazy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you just jerk off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liz told me not to. She said it’s important.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ohhh,” she nodded knowingly. “I get it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” I said. “What’s to get?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s your mistress. You have to do what she says. This is a control game.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” I scoffed. “No, it’s not like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It &lt;em&gt;sounds&lt;/em&gt; like it’s like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not, trust me.” I crossed my arms. “I’m not doing a good job explaining. I’m still figuring out how this situation works, but it’s not, like, a domination thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure.” She winked. Before I could protest, she held up her hands as if to wave my objection away. “Look, no judgment. I’ve been exploring submissive relationships myself. It can be exhilarating to give someone control. To place your trust in someone like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I frowned. My cock was throbbing desperately, and I was painfully aware of how close she was sitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The first time for me was really eye-opening.” She bit her lip. “I was on this robotics trip during my senior year of high school. My roommate snuck a guy in, and she caught me watching them fuck. I thought she’d be furious.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She crossed her legs, squirming. “But she came over and told me she knew I was watching and it turned her on. Then she started touching me and telling me what to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fuck me.&lt;/em&gt; I pressed my hand firmly against my cock, not rubbing it, but trying to get some relief. She saw, and scooted her stool closer, leaning in conspiratorially. Her breath was hot in my ear. Her breast was pressed against my arm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She sat on my face and made me lick her while she fingered me. Then she had her boyfriend fuck my mouth while she got me off, and I ended up covered in his cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Groaning, I started rubbing my cock through my pants, but she slapped my wrist and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah-ah-ah, Mike, your mistress wouldn’t like that. She told you not to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s not my…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not your mistress, I know,” she said, scoffing. “In college, I tried to explore this side of myself, but all the guys I met either didn’t really get it, or they were a little &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; into it. This one girl, though…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced behind her to make sure there was no one waiting at the counter. Then she spread her legs and lifted her skirt, revealing a simple nude thong. Slowly, she reached down and started stroking with one finger, teasing me with the shape of her lips as she pressed against the thin fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This girl, Mike, she got it. She knew what I needed. She took charge. She told me what to do. She explored my boundaries with me. She’d meet me between classes and take my underwear, or she’d make me unbutton my top until I felt exposed. She’d make out with me until I was flushed and dripping, and then make me go back to class and wait all day before she would let me cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara watched me hungrily as she rubbed herself, enjoying the effect she was having on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One time she sent me to class with a remote-control vibrator and teased me until I thought I was going to leave a puddle in my seat. I ended up running to the bathroom and rubbing one out in a stall. That night, she spanked me for the first time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara bit her lip and squeezed her legs together around her hand. After a moment, she slowly pulled her underwear down. I strained for a glimpse, but her dress fell back into place. As she straightened up, she held the soaked fabric to my face. The heady smell of her arousal filled my senses. I let out a choked groan and gripped the chair tightly. I wanted so badly to pull out my cock and start stroking, but I knew she would stop if I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I learned if I did what she asked, she would reward me. I would come back to her place flooded with desire. She would sit on the couch and drink whiskey and have me lick her pussy until she gushed in my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she talked, Kara unbuckled my belt and unbuttoned my pants. I was panting and eager as she pushed her wet panties into my boxers. I whimpered and lifted my hips to press into her hand, but she pulled away, leaving the fabric wrapped around my twitching shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then she would make me cum. I was always so turned on by that point, that it never took long. She’d bend me over the back of the couch and finger me until I was screaming. Then she would call me a good girl and clean me up and hold me until I fell asleep.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moved forward, slowly lifting her dress. Her lips glistened wetly, bright pink against her pale skin, crowned by a wispy tuft of hair. She straddled my legs, standing over my cock, which was twitching urgently and barely contained by my boxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I also learned if I disobeyed, I would be punished. She introduced me to nipple clamps, spanking, strap-ons, and more. Fuck, this is turning me on telling you all this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped as she pushed a finger between her lips, pulling it out again to spread her wetness over her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, she graduated before me and moved away. I still follow her on Instagram.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I imagined pulling out my cock, grabbing her by the hips, and pushing her down on it. She seemed to read my mind because she shook her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No touching, Mike. Your mistress wouldn’t like it. Mine wouldn’t either, for that matter,” she purred. “My new mistress actually got me the job here. Her husband is on the board. Don’t tell anyone, but I think she’s hoping I’ll be like a spy for her and get some info that would let him take control.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some part of my brain recognized this as important information, but I was in no position to process it. She pushed another finger inside herself and started thrusting her hips, enjoying making me watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She makes me flirt with her husband. She bought me a maid outfit. She has me go around with a feather duster and bend over in front of him. Sometimes she fingers me first, until there’s a big wet spot on my panties. Other times she takes them away so he can see my pussy. Then she comes in and pretends to be shocked when she catches him watching me with a hard-on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does he know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah, it’s a game for the two of them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, uh,” I was having trouble concentrating while watching her finger herself. “What does she do when she catches the two of you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She calls us names. She makes me go down on him. She says stuff like ‘Is this what you want? You want this little slut to suck your prick?’ It makes his cock so hard in my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara closed her eyes and moaned at the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She yanks down my top and pulls on my nipples until I squeal. ‘Let’s get this bitch’s tits out. That’s what you want to see, motherfucker? You get off thinking about her little tits?’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, she reached down and grabbed my hand, pulling it to her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe it’s okay if you touch me a little, Mike, but don’t touch yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded eagerly as I groped her. I could feel her nipples harden through her dress and wished I could suck on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She pushes my head down on his cock until I choke. ‘Look at this slut, she loves it. Fuck, I bet she’s dripping wet.’ Then she reaches behind and shoves a finger in me and says ‘I can’t believe how wet this cunt is right now! She’s been prancing around all day fantasizing about this instead of doing her fucking job.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” I moaned, watching her rub tight circles around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right? Sometimes she spanks me. It turns me on so much getting spanked while I suck her husband’s cock. Between swats, she fingers me, alternating pleasure and pain. ‘Listen to her moan! The little tramp is getting off on this.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I groaned, struggling to resist the urge to do more than touch her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then she makes me climb in his lap and ride him while she berates him. ‘Is this what you wanted? Is this why you got hard when she bent over and presented herself to you? Did you imagine burying your thick prick in her tight little pussy? Don’t cum in her, you dog. I know she’s a thirsty little slut who’s only good for filling with spunk, but don’t you dare.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell,” I gasped. My cock twitched, and I felt a squirt of precum soak into her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. Sometimes she fingers my ass, too. She knows it makes my pussy clench, and it gets him right to the edge.” Kara bit her lip, then laughed. “This one time, she stuck the handle of the feather duster up there while I was riding him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’d you do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I screamed and came all over him. Then he came inside me. She was &lt;em&gt;furious&lt;/em&gt; with him. Normally she makes him cum on my face or my tits. She made him lick it all out of me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” she purred, leaning into my hands. “It was so fucking hot. I think he was into it, you know. Some guys are. After that, she made him sleep on the couch while she helped me shower and let me stay the night with her in their bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara, fuck…” My cock felt like it might explode. “I need…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know. Pull down your pants. I want to look at your cock while I cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, I lifted my ass and shoved my pants and boxers down around my ankles. My cock reached straight up, still wrapped in her thong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” she exhaled. “I wish I could give you what you need. But your mistress will not be happy if I ruin her fun.” She pulled her fingers out and let me suck on them, coating my tongue with the taste of her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I groaned, and my cock twitched, straining for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But I guess it wouldn’t hurt for you to finger me if you promise not to… Ah!” Before she finished, I had two fingers inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, you’re eager,” she gasped, bucking her hips to fuck against my fingers. I pressed up, awkwardly trying to grind my palm against her clit while still fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He really is,” said Liz from behind us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara squealed and jumped away from me, tugging her dress down. Turning around guiltily, she found Liz leaning on the counter. She had a carefully neutral expression as she looked from Kara to me. My pants were bunched around my ankles, Kara’s wet panties wrapped around my cock, and I was shamelessly licking my fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calmly, Liz walked around to the door and let herself into the room. She stood there for a minute, trying to make up her mind how to handle the situation. I couldn’t help but notice her nipples were poking through her dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How long were you there, miss?” Kara whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Long enough to get interested,” Liz replied. “I see that beast hasn’t calmed down any,” she observed, as my cock continued to throb with my heartbeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t let him touch himself, or help him cum,” Kara said with a bit more confidence. “I told him you wouldn’t be happy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz nodded approvingly. “And what was it you called me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“His, um, his mistress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I don’t hate that,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liz,” I started, but she cut me off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll deal with you later.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But I didn’t do anything?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only because she stopped you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I frowned. Kara bit her lip and looked pleased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, Kara, while I’m grateful you managed to keep Mike under control, you &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; get distracted from your job. I left him here to calm down, and I come back to find you both too aroused to think straight. If someone else had come up to the coat check, we’d be having a different conversation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara hung her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Liz said after a long minute. “Mike, poor Kara here tried to be a good girl, but you distracted her. Now she’s so turned on it’s literally running down her thighs.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara’s face turned bright red, and she squeezed her knees together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you need to make it up to her. But Kara, Mike here is uncontrollably erect because of a pill I asked him to try. He was already having a hard time before you started telling him about your adventures. So you need to make it up to him a bit, first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, miss.” Kara hesitated. “What do you want me to do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To start, I want you to get on your knees and suck his cock. And don’t touch yourself. It’s not your turn, yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, miss.” Kara dropped to her knees in front of me. Her eyes glittered with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike,” Liz cautioned. “You are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; allowed to cum. If you’re getting close, I expect you to let Kara know so she can slow down. You’ll get yours later.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded vaguely, barely able to think straight as Kara licked her lips and stared at my cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike,” Liz warned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yes!” I looked Liz in the eyes. “Yes, I understand.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about the coat check, miss?” Kara asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a little late to think of that now, but don’t worry. The party’s just starting to wind down. I came out early to check on Mike. Still, you are a bit exposed.” She grabbed one of the rolling coat racks and positioned it to block the view from the counter. “Now, I’ll manage the front while you two get started.” With that, she disappeared behind the coats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I &lt;em&gt;told&lt;/em&gt; you she’s your mistress,” Kara mumbled, pleased with herself as she removed her panties from around my cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, she’s—oh!” I gasped as she wrapped her lips around my head. The heat of her mouth felt incredible after being denied any stimulation for so long, and I immediately forgot what I was protesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara quickly fell into a rhythm, one hand wrapped around the base of my shaft and the other cupping my balls. I felt a building pressure, and she moaned happily as a squirt of precum coated her tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Kara, you better slow down,” I reluctantly mumbled. Disappointed, Kara rocked back, releasing my cock to slowly lick up and down my shaft. I felt the pressure recede a bit. “You’re really fucking good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you,” she purred. “My mistress gives me a lot of practice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Was all that stuff you said true?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Every word of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You weren’t just teasing me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, I was doing that too, but it was all true. I think the reason it excited you so much is you’ve got a little submissive in you, too. I see the way you respond to Liz. Admit it, you like it when a woman tells you what to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, I guess that’s kinda true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does Ms. Sandstrom also tell you what to do when you fool around?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, sometimes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And does it turn you on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“…Yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you go,” she concluded, taking me back into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A moment later, Liz walked around the coat rack with a claim ticket and grabbed a couple items. She leaned over to whisper in Kara’s ear. “Try to go deeper.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara moaned and changed her angle until I felt my cock bump against the back of her mouth. Liz winked at me and bustled back around to the counter. I tried to keep from groaning loudly as Kara swallowed and bobbed her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara,” I gasped, wrapping my hand around the back of her head. She was determined, rocking back and forth. I grabbed her ponytail and she nodded, squeezing my thighs as I pulled her closer. Abruptly, my cock slipped deeper and we both grunted as her lips reached the base of my shaft. Her throat was hot and tight and my cock was throbbing. She gagged, but let me keep holding her in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz reappeared with another claim ticket and whispered, “Easy there, Kara. If you want that monster inside you, don’t make him cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, the pill,” I gasped, “I can go again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Control yourself, or I’ll separate you.” She was clearly enjoying herself. “Now, why don’t you trade places and show her how you got your job.” She walked toward the counter, but said over her shoulder, “And don’t touch yourself!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reluctantly, I let her go. Kara rocked back away from me, coughing and wiping drool from her chin, but with a look of triumph in her eyes. My cock was swollen large and purple as I took Kara’s spot on the floor. She excitedly hiked up her dress and leaned back in the chair, spreading her legs wide for me. Her lips were puffy with desire, and her wetness had indeed been dripping down her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I licked slowly and steadily up her legs. She bit her finger to keep from making any noise when I finally reached my goal. I traced over and between her lips and toward her clit, already standing proud. I teased around it, licking up and down repeatedly until she was quivering with need, then I closed my lips and swirled my tongue. She squeaked and grabbed the back of my head, holding me firmly in place like I had done to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara was already close to cumming, I could tell. She gasped and squirmed in the chair as I pushed my tongue deep inside before returning to suck lightly on her clit. When I slipped two fingers in, they entered easily, as if her velvety walls were pulling me deeper. I curled my fingers and she bucked her hips, trying not to cry out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt her pussy clenching and a gush of warm fluid, but she didn’t let go. Her breathing was ragged and she was cursing under her breath over and over. She tightened her grip on my hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I pushed a finger into her ass, she let out a long, low moan, and clamped her thighs around my head. I kept going, moving my fingers and my tongue as her legs shook like an earthquake around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, she released me. She gasped as I slowly eased my fingers out and covered her clit with my palm, applying firm, gentle pressure to her entire vulva. She bit her lip and squeezed her legs again around my hand for a long moment before finally pushing me away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stood up and took a step back, only to bump into Liz. “Good job, Mike.” She rested her chin on my shoulder and reached around to grip my cock, which felt so hard it might burst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now, miss?” Kara was still breathing heavily, and grinned at Liz and me, lewdly spreading her thighs as an invitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, Mike, I think you’d better fuck her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I cum?” I gulped, desperate for release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only if she asks you to.” Liz kissed my neck, and stepped away, grabbing some items before returning to the front.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara pushed the chair away and lay on the floor as I dropped to my knees again. I rubbed the head of my cock against her opening, coating it in her cream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it, Mike, fuck me please,” Kara breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, I shoved my cock rudely inside. She accepted me easily, choking back a squeal as I buried myself to the hilt. I groaned as I felt her insides clenching me already. She threw her arms and legs around me and kissed me desperately, trying to pull me even closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started fucking her. Not slow and sensual, but urgent and demanding. Forceful. She buried her face in my shoulder, biting me to stifle her yelps of pleasure. I could already feel the pressure building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara,” I gasped. But before I could ask to cum, we heard a loud woman’s voice from the counter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where is Kara? She was working the coat check. What are you doing here, Ms. Holman?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hello, Mrs. Sackwell. She, um, had to,” Liz sounded flustered as she tried to think of an answer. “She ran to the bathroom. I’m just covering for her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit,” Kara hissed in my ear. “Mike, that’s my mistress. Quick, quick, cum! Cum for me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fucked her harder. I wanted nothing more in the world than to cum with my cock buried in her pussy. Kara gave up all effort to be quiet and started crying out loudly with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara?” I heard the voice from the front say. “What’s going on here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz protested, but I didn’t care, my orgasm was imminent. Kara’s nails dug into my back as she continued to urge me to cum. “Do it—Ah!—Mike! Cum—Uh!—Fuck!—Cum inside—Ah!—Cum in me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The door to the coat check room opened. A woman in her late 40s wearing an expensive green gown with long sleeves stood aghast in the doorway. Liz followed, pushing her into the room and closing the door behind them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop fucking her this instant!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But…” I protested, knowing I was about to cum. Before I could do anything, Kara pushed me away, but I was already cumming. The first spurt happened just as I slipped out, frosting her lips and clit. The second shot high as I rocked back on my knees, arcing through the air to fall across the bosom of her dress. The third splashed onto her stomach, and the rest fell on the floor as I rocked in place, grunting and unable to control myself during my long-delayed climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus,” the woman cursed, watching Kara’s flushed face as she tried to regain her composure. “Kara, stand up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes… Mistress,” Kara panted. She got shakily to her feet, awkwardly pulling her cum-splattered dress down to cover herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Unbelievable,” the woman muttered. “I buy you a new dress and the first thing you do is get spunk all over it. You’re going to have to be punished for this, of course.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, Mistress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hand me those,” she snapped at me, gesturing to Kara’s discarded panties on the floor. I picked them up and sheepishly offered them while failing to pull up my pants. She took them and started wiping the cum from Kara’s dress, but gave up when she saw it was mostly just smearing things around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, whatever.” She dropped the soaked underwear on the floor and turned to glare at Liz while pointing at me. “If you can’t control your dog, he should be on a leash.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, mistress,” Liz replied sardonically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Humph. Kara, come with me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Mistress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara allowed herself to be led out of the room but made a “call me” gesture to Liz. There was an excited sparkle in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, Liz,” I exhaled as the door closed. “That was intense.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” Liz replied thoughtfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can we please go upstairs and fuck now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Liz looked down to see I was already hard again and laughed. “Oh! Well, unfortunately, we just lost our coat check girl. But if you sit here patiently like a good boy, I promise I’ll reward you later.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, mistress,” I replied teasingly as I sat back down in the chair, my cock twitching eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz bit her lip and went back to the counter.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
</feed>
