<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Ruby Pink Romance</title>
	<subtitle>Classy smut for classy people</subtitle>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/"/>
	<updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Ruby Pink</name>
		<email>hello@rubypinkromance.com</email>
	</author>
  <icon>https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rubypink.jpg</icon>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 5: Marcy</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/5-marcy/"/>
		<published>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/5-marcy/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="pussy eating" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Why are you sitting way over there?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy grinned at the text. It was from her girlfriend, Bonnie, who was currently sitting across from her at the airport. They were waiting at the crowded departure gate with the rest of their team to board a plane to MIT for the robotics competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry,” she texted back. “I got distracted because SOMEONE hasn’t stopped texting me since we got off the bus, and when I looked up, all the other seats were taken.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So?” Bonnie grinned. “Get over here and tell Amy to fuck off and sit somewhere else. Or just come sit on my lap.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t think Coach Sam would like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who cares what she likes, I want you on top of me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy looked around to make sure no one was looking at her phone. Bonnie’s texts had been escalating from playful to explicit, and she was a little worried someone would see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she responded, “maybe they’ll let us share a room.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, that would be amazing.” Bonnie winked at her. “I’d keep you up all night. You could send me home covered in hickeys.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re making it hard to think about anything else.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t help it, you’re so fucking hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unconsciously, Marcy ran a hand through her dark hair. She’d recently gotten an overtly queer asymmetric cut and had been worried about what Bonnie, always the more traditionally femme of the two, would think. Turns out, she had nothing to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey,” Bonnie sent, “guess what I’m wearing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing Marcy would immediately look up, Bonnie casually stretched, her crop top lifting just enough to tease a glimpse of pink lace. She was wearing the sexy longline bra they’d bought together on a memorable shopping trip that had ended with a lap dance in the dressing room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love the way that looks on you,” Marcy texted, “It turns me on so much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good, because your leather jacket gets me wet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Be patient, Bon-bon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want to be patient. I want you to pull my hair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shifted in her seat as Bonnie shot her a wicked look, licking her lips as she adjusted her ponytail, tugging her blonde hair back just a bit harder than necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop!” Marcy mouthed the word, glancing nervously at Coach Sam, a few seats away, worried they’d get caught. Bonnie just grinned and picked up her phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I need your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Bonnie.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, fuck Bonnie! Now you’re getting it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re gonna get it,” she texted, weakly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get what? Your head between my thighs?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy squeezed her legs together, uncomfortably aware of how aroused she was becoming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie, please,” she texted. “I can’t make it through the flight if you get me all worked up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shot her a pleading look. Bonnie gave her an understanding smile. Then she stood up and started walking away, tucking her phone into the back pocket of her jean shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie,” Coach Sam called, “Where are you going?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just to the bathroom,” she replied without stopping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, well, listen for our flight announcement, we should be boarding soon!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy took a deep breath and tried to clear her head. Now that Bonnie was done texting, it was time to slow things down and make it through the flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her phone buzzed again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a photo of Bonnie from the bathroom stall. She was lifting her shirt and sticking out her tongue. Her dark nipples were clearly visible through the thin lace of her bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come see how wet I am.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck. Two more texts came one after another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Push me against the wall.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Suck on my nipples.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She checked the time. Their flight would start boarding in ten minutes. They’d have to be quick. She responded with a running emoji and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Last stall, hurry.” Bonnie texted back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Marcy,” Coach Sam warned as she walked away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I know, I’ll be quick!” She broke into a jog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miraculously, the bathroom was nearly deserted. Almost all the stalls were unoccupied, and there was only one woman in a nice suit washing her hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy walked straight to the last stall. The door was closed but not locked, and she opened it to find Bonnie grinning at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They fell into each other’s arms, Marcy fumbling to lock the door, then pushing her girlfriend against the wall, urgently kissing her. They were both flooded with lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck, I’m glad you came,” Bonnie gasped, stifling a squeal as Marcy reached under her crop top to squeeze her nipples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How could I not?” Marcy whispered, “You’re so goddamn sexy, and you’ve been teasing me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wasn’t teasing, I’m yours,” she purred, reaching under Marcy’s leather jacket to caress her sides and chest. “And I need your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remembering how little time they had, Marcy unbuttoned Bonnie’s shorts and reached into her panties. She was already squirming as Marcy worked a finger between her lips. As promised, she was already wet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” Bonnie whispered. But Marcy paused, making eye contact as she reached her other hand up to grip Bonnie’s ponytail. She nodded, and Marcy pulled, gently at first, but increasingly firmly, tipping her head back, before finally slipping her finger inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonnie immediately started gasping as Marcy fingered her and sucked on her neck. She arched her back, desperate for more. Marcy felt her lust surging as she released Bonnie’s hair and added a second finger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panting with each thrust of her fingers, Bonnie tugged up Marcy’s shirt and began kissing down her chest, scooping a breast from her strappy black bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We don’t have long,” Marcy exhaled, fingers buried in her girlfriend’s soaking pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rub my clit,” Bonnie panted, closing her lips around the brunette’s nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shifted her hand, pressing her palm against the sensitive bud. Bonnie rolled her hips, grinding against the pressure, moaning into Marcy’s breast, and moving urgently towards her release. Marcy moved her hand faster until Bonnie suddenly went stiff, releasing her nipple with a wet sound and gasped into her cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling her need surging, Marcy pulled her hand out and pushed Bonnie back against the wall, frantically kissing her. Urgently, she pulled up Bonnie’s top, wet fingers squeezing her breasts through the thin fabric, leaving her moaning and grabbing Marcy’s ass to pull her closer, grinding against her thigh—when they suddenly heard the final boarding announcement for their flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughing, they pulled their clothes back into place and ran out of the stall holding hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a very long flight, not made any easier by her damp underwear and the lingering scent of Bonnie on her fingers. Their seats were far apart, and she spent most of the time watching videos on her phone, trying to distract herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they finally arrived at the dorms that MIT provided, Marcy was disappointed but not surprised that the coaches put her and Bonnie in separate rooms. She was sharing a room with Rylie, and Bonnie was next door with Amy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her first stop was the restroom, to change into a dry pair of underwear, sports bra, soft t-shirt, and lounge pants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By eleven, Rylie was already in bed wearing a sleep mask, but Marcy was still too wound up to sleep. It was hours earlier than she normally went to bed. She found herself sitting on top of the covers, screwing around on her phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It buzzed with a text from Bonnie: “Still awake?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I can’t sleep this early.” She grinned and added, “Plus, you got me all worked up earlier.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, not sorry. You look so fucking hot in that leather jacket.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When do you think we can be alone again? Sucks they wouldn’t let us share a room. No love for the gays, I guess.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Soon, I hope. I can’t stop thinking about the way you took me at the airport.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t stop thinking about you during the flight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm tell me more.” Marcy could imagine Bonnie purring as she said it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shot a look toward her roommate, trying to judge if she was asleep yet. Rylie was rolled away, facing the wall, and breathing slowly… but then she scratched her arm and adjusted her pillow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was thinking about your lips around my nipple.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re so fucking sexy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thinking about how you moved against me when I put my fingers in you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I love your fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thinking about what I would do next.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to take off your top and push you down on the bed and suck on your tits.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yesss. What then?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kiss my way down your front and pull your panties down just enough to lick you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot. I love seeing you look up at me from between my legs. I want to run my fingers through your hair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’d pull your underwear off and finger you while I lick your clit. I won’t stop until you have to scream into a pillow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, I want that so bad. When you’re done, I wa”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy blinked at the screen. The text ended abruptly, and just when it was getting good. Probably, Bonnie was typing one-handed. She grinned, and looked at Rylie, trying to judge whether she could get away with doing the same when her phone buzzed again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“OMG get over here quick. Amy just left.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy sat bolt upright. Holy shit. Amy had been flirting aggressively with Ian all day long. If she’d snuck out, it was probably to go hook up with him somewhere. Which meant Bonnie was alone in the next room!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carefully, she padded barefoot toward the door. Rylie didn’t react. She was about to open it when she heard footsteps coming down the hall. Concerned it was Amy returning, she hesitated until she heard the bathroom door open and shut. After a moment, she slipped out, closing the door behind her as quietly as she could. There was no sign of anyone, though she could hear a TV playing in the common room. Cautiously, she opened the door to the next room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonnie was sitting up in bed, grinning from ear to ear. She was wearing grey sleep shorts and a pink tank top with no bra. Her nipples poked excitedly through the cotton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Marcy grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right?” Bonnie agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Babe, I heard someone come down the hall and go into the bathroom. Do you think it was Amy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe?” Bonnie shrugged. “She said she was going to the bathroom, but she had this look in her eyes like she thought she was being &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; clever. I mean, she obviously went to fuck Ian, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, for sure, she was all over him today.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, so,” Bonnie bit her lip. “Can we…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy climbed onto the bed, but Bonnie put a hand on her shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if we’re wrong? What if Amy comes back?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She can watch,” Marcy replied with a grin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh really?” Bonnie laughed. “Well, if we’re fantasizing, why not ask her to join us?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hell no, I’m not sharing you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good answer. What if she tells Coach Sam?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Coach Sam can watch, too.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hm,” Bonnie considered, a twinkle in her eyes. “Okay, but for real, that’s super hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Marcy moved closer, nuzzling her neck. “You like the idea of an audience?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe… I’ve never really thought about it before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seems like you’re thinking about it now,” Marcy murmured, brushing Bonnie’s hair back and kissing her earlobe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yesss,” she purred, tilting her head back as Marcy kissed down her neck. “I’m imagining them sitting across from us, getting more and more turned on until they start touching themselves. Sam squeezing her tits. Amy with a hand down her shorts. Both of them staring at us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mm-hmm. But I don’t want to keep thinking about them. I want you to do what you were telling me about.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I thought you’d never ask.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giggling, Marcy pulled Bonnie’s top over her head and pushed her down on the bed. Her laughter turned to quiet moans as Marcy settled her weight between her thighs, grinding against her as they kissed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy shifted downward, trailing kisses. She took Bonnie’s breasts in her hands and pulled a nipple into her mouth, rolling the other between her fingers. Bonnie gasped and squirmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shifting to the other breast, Marcy looked up, meeting Bonnie’s desire-filled eyes. As she moved her tongue in lazy circles, Bonnie moaned and dropped her head back onto the pillow, savoring the sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a minute, Bonnie wrapped her legs around her and pulled her back up into a kiss. Marcy ground against her pelvis, making her squeal. Frantically, Bonnie tugged at the black fabric of Marcy’s shirt, pulling it up. Marcy helped remove it and pulled Bonnie’s face into her cleavage. The blonde moaned happily, kissing and squeezing Marcy’s breasts through her bra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, teasingly, Marcy moved back down Bonnie’s body, kissing her chest and stomach until finally reaching the waistband of her shorts. Bonnie nodded eagerly and lifted her hips to let Marcy pull them off, revealing polka-dot panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dropping the shorts on the floor, Marcy kissed along Bonnie’s thigh, stopping just short of her underwear to tease her, then getting to her feet and shimmying out of her lounge pants. Bonnie grunted in frustration and followed, dropping to her knees to kiss Marcy’s hips. Marcy gasped as Bonnie buried her face between her thighs, pressing into the fabric of her underwear. She felt a surge of lust and pulled Bonnie back up, kissing her deeply. Bonnie giggled and allowed herself to be pushed back down on the bed, pulling Marcy with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped and eagerly spread her legs as Marcy kissed slowly down her front to her hips. As promised, Marcy pulled down the fabric just far enough to brush her lips over Bonnie’s cleft. She made eye contact, the elastic straining under her chin as she kissed lower, nuzzling her nose into the triangle of well-trimmed hair, and flicking her tongue out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” Bonnie gasped, running her fingers through Marcy’s hair. She rolled her hips, trying to adjust the angle, but her panties were in the way. Marcy’s eyes gleamed, and she kept teasing her mercilessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” Bonnie begged, gripping her hair tighter, and grinding against her chin. “Please, take them off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, since you asked so nicely,” Marcy purred as she backed up on her knees, pulling the panties with her, before crawling seductively up to kiss her deeply. Bonnie moaned around her tongue and wrapped her legs around Marcy’s ass, trying to pull her tighter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then Marcy was moving down again, kissing and licking as she went. She could tell Bonnie was excited, squeezing her breasts and squirming as she anticipated what came next. Finally, Marcy settled between her spread legs, licking slowly up her thigh, teasing her before moving inward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yes,” Bonnie purred, pinching her nipples as Marcy finally reached her goal, pushing her tongue between her girlfriend’s lips. Eagerly, she lapped up Bonnie’s creamy arousal before rolling her tongue into a tube and licking deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, yes,” Bonnie moaned, rocking back and forth as Marcy fucked her with her tongue. “My clit, ah! Please lick my clit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy moved up to trace tight circles around the erect bud. She slipped one, and then two fingers inside Bonnie’s pussy. She was moaning and panting, squirming and tensing, tangling her fingers in Marcy’s hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god! Yeah, right there, just like that!” Bonnie tightened her grip, pulling more urgently. Marcy curled her fingers, beckoning Bonnie’s orgasm as she arched her back, thrusting her pelvis against Marcy’s face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, oh fuck, I’m cumming!” Bonnie groaned as her pussy clenched around Marcy’s fingers over and over, until she collapsed back on the pillow, gasping for breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, Marcy worked her way up, kissing and licking, before rolling onto her back, pulling Bonnie on top, into a passionate kiss. Their tongues danced, and Bonnie moaned with pleasure at the taste of her own cum on Marcy’s lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God, you’re so fucking sexy,” Bonnie growled. Marcy arched her back to pull off her sports bra, eagerly tossing it to the floor. She moaned as Bonnie pulled her breast into her mouth. The blonde looked up at her with eyes full of desire, lips locked around her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You look so fucking hot like that,” Marcy purred. She rocked her hips, pushing upwards against Bonnie’s weight between her legs. “But take my underwear off, I want to feel you—ah!” She gasped as Bonnie immediately shimmied lower, rubbing and kissing through her panties. Her hot breath on the damp fabric made Marcy squirm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie, please,” she begged, until Bonnie took pity and hooked fingers under her waistband and pulled them down. She wasted no time, practically diving back between Marcy’s thighs, licking and kissing and rubbing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, that feels so good, babe!” Marcy was already groaning and tense, running her fingers through Bonnie’s hair, and pulling her closer. She realized that the long day of teasing had kept her on the edge, and her first orgasm was fast approaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, yeah,” she gasped, squeezing her breast as she rocked in place, grinding her pussy against Bonnie’s face. “Fuck, you’re gonna make me cum in your mouth so hard.” Bonnie moaned eagerly, thrusting her tongue deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh my god!” Marcy’s entire body tensed. She felt a release, and Bonnie squealed wetly. Waves of sensation rolled through her body, radiating from her core. Flares of color erupted behind her closed eyes as she rocked in place, holding Bonnie against her, until with a shudder, she pushed her away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have such a tasty pussy,” Bonnie giggled, wiping her chin as she sat back on her knees. Marcy could only breathe, shivering as the aftershocks rolled down her spine. She purred as she felt Bonnie moving up, swinging one leg over her hip to scissor her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you doing?” Marcy laughed, then let out a satisfied sigh as Bonnie pressed against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wanna try this,” Bonnie giggled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on—ah,” Marcy gasped as Bonnie started moving. “No one actually does this, it’s just a porn thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Says you,” Bonnie replied, a thoughtful expression on her face as she shifted, trying to find the right angle. “Just let me try, I’m curious.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It—oh!—It does feel nice, I guess,” Marcy conceded as their lips glided against each other. “I’m still all sensitive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, you came so fast, babe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s—oooh—it’s your fault, you kept me so turned on all day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here, like this,” Bonnie mumbled, grabbing one of Marcy’s legs and pulling it up onto her shoulder. “Oh, that feels good.” She held Marcy’s ankle and began grinding more urgently, thrusting against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm, I like it when you rub your pussy on my clit like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not—ah!—Not bad for a porn move, huh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up, just—ooh—just keep doing that,” Marcy groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Roll your hips, babe, move like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah! Fuck yeah. Oh! This is going to make me cum…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it, cum all over my pussy,” Marcy urged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Oh. Uh. Ah!” Bonnie’s staccato gasping increased as she leaned into Marcy’s upright leg, rolling her hips, grinding and rubbing. Everything was slick and juicy and hot and sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, do it. Cum for me. Cum &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; me,” Marcy moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh… Fuck!” Bonnie cried out as she went rigid, then swore as her knee slipped, and she fell off the bed with a crash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bon!” Marcy yelped, rolling over. “Are you okay? Did you hurt yourself?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just my pride,” Bonnie groaned. She was sprawled on the floor, rubbing her elbow. “Fucking porn makes it look so easy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy stifled a giggle, but Bonnie met her eyes and they both started laughing. She climbed off the bed and pulled Bonnie into a hug. They held each other, laughing at the absurdity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, there was a knock at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Quick,” Bonnie hissed, “Get in the other bed!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frantically, they both dove into opposite beds, pulling the covers up just as the door opened to reveal Coach Sam. Marcy buried her face in the pillow, praying the dim moonlight was too dark for Sam to recognize her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girls, I know you’re excited, but you’ve got to go to sleep. I need you up and ready to rock first thing in the morning, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stunned, they could only mumble in agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright. Get some good rest.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam closed the door and they heard her footsteps moving away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh. My. God,” Bonnie whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Marcy agreed, sitting up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like, just for a second, I thought maybe she was here to, uh…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To watch?” Marcy snickered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Like, we were &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; talking about it, and then she shows up right when I’m about to cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t believe she didn’t notice it was me instead of Amy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can,” Bonnie giggled and sat up, throwing her blanket aside. “Did you see her shirt?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I had my face hidden in the pillow. What about it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The buttons were done up wrong and it looked like her bra was unhooked.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You don’t think…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah. Her hair was messed up, too. I bet she was getting lucky with Coach Jake when she came to see what the noise was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With Jake? Ew.” Marcy crossed over to sit next to Bonnie, who shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’s cute enough for a guy. And he clearly thinks she’s great.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Whatever. Gross.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, alright,” Bonnie chuckled. “What would you rather talk about?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Marcy considered, leaning in and kissing her neck. “You said you were about to cum before you fell over?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Bonnie purred. “I was so close. Your pussy felt really good on mine. But you know what I really want?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your fingers again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then turn around,” Marcy replied. Bonnie turned away and dropped onto her hands and knees. Marcy moved behind her, running her hands over her hips and ass. Bonnie arched her back to give Marcy better access and gasped as two fingers dipped inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” she purred, reaching between her legs to rub her clit. Marcy started moving in and out, coating her fingers in Bonnie’s wetness. She quickly increased her tempo, and Bonnie matched her pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” she gasped. “Fuck, that feels so good, babe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?” Marcy felt her fingers being squeezed. “You like getting fucked from behind?” Bonnie squealed as Marcy slapped her ass, squeezing and spreading her cheeks as she kept fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, you’re gonna make me cum again,” Bonnie moaned into the pillow. “Oh! Oh my god!” She started shaking, her insides clenching as her fingers rubbed tight, urgent circles around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh right there, right there, OH MY GOD, FUUUCK,” Bonnie screamed, muffled by the pillow. Marcy grinned and kept her fingers in place until Bonnie pulled away, still squirming and panting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, babe, that was so good,” Bonnie gasped, turning and kissing her. Marcy laughed and let herself be pushed onto her back. Bonnie grinned at her and moved to throw her leg over Marcy’s head in a 69 position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcy gasped as Bonnie immediately started licking her clit. She responded in kind, wrapping her lips around Bonnie’s sensitive bud and sucking. Bonnie squealed and pushed her tongue into between Marcy’s lips. They went back and forth, distracting each other, seeing who could focus more. Marcy slapped Bonnie’s ass, and she responded by slipping her thumb into Marcy’s pussy. She gasped at the sudden intrusion, and grabbed Bonnie’s ass with both hands, spreading her cheeks and sucking on her clit. She lost her focus when she felt Bonnie easing a slender finger into her ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” Marcy groaned, feeling Bonnie’s thumb and finger separated by only a thin bridge of sensitive flesh. “Fuck, yeah, oh god.” She slapped Bonnie’s ass, hard, making her squeal into her clit, but she didn’t relent, and Marcy felt her insides beginning to clench around Bonnie’s digits. She lifted her head, burying her face in her girlfriend’s wetness, but immediately dropped back down, gasping as she felt the pressure building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you’re making me cum!” She squeezed Marcy’s ass and squirmed, rocking her hips, fucking against her fingers. Marcy was saying something, urging her on, but she couldn’t hear. She was only aware of the stimulation between her legs, the tongue lashing her clit, the pressure of their bodies against each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, yeah, oh, oh, oh god, oh fuck,” Marcy cried into Bonnie’s thigh. “Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me!” Fireworks were going off inside her brain. Lightning crackled through her nervous system. She came long and hard until she collapsed. Bonnie moved to snuggle up at her side, resting her head on Marcy’s shoulder and kissing her cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They lay together like that for a long time, kissing and caressing each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were both afraid to be the first to admit the inevitable fact that they couldn’t stay together all night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, Marcy did it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I should go.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nooo,” Bonnie protested sleepily. “Stay.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can’t. Amy could come back anytime.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t care.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, she’d tell Coach Sam, and she’d care.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmph,” Bonnie seemed to concede the point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reluctantly, Marcy stood up and gathered her scattered clothes. After pulling on her pants and shirt, she leaned over to kiss Bonnie goodnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm, you taste like sex,” Bonnie purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So do you, babe.” Marcy kissed her again and then went to the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she cracked it open. Just as she was about to step into the hall, she saw movement. Peeking out, she saw Rylie and Ian come down the hall. Rylie’s top was unbuttoned and billowed to reveal her bare breasts. Ian followed a step behind, and it took her a moment to realize she wasn’t holding his hand, but instead was pulling him eagerly down the hall by his erect cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blinking in surprise, she watched as Rylie led Ian to the door of the room she and Marcy shared, pulling him in after her. He had a dopey, horny expression on his face, and it was obvious they would be fucking as soon as the door was closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which meant she couldn’t go back to her room. Grinning, she closed the door and took her clothes back off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good news, babe,” she whispered as she slipped back under the blanket. “I’m staying here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yaaay,” Bonnie whispered, snuggling up to her. “Why?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just saw Rylie, and you’ll never believe who she was with.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Never mind,” Bonnie said drowsily. “Tell me in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Love you, Bon-bon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Love you too,” she mumbled, already falling back asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Ms. Sandstrom’s Assistant 5: The Coat Check Room</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/ms-sandstroms-assistant/5-coat-check-room/"/>
		<published>2024-03-15T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/ms-sandstroms-assistant/5-coat-check-room/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="submissive" />
    <category term="edging" />
    <category term="domination" />
    <category term="submission" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male submissive" />
    <category term="female submissive" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/coat-check-room-rIghmtdtB7-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Liz, stop,” I hissed, as she tried to lead me into the shareholder event on the first floor of our office building. “I can’t go in there like this!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“C’mon, Mike, no one’s gonna know.” She couldn’t quite keep a straight face as she said it, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I turned away as a small group of people in fancy clothes walked past us to the coat check. When they were gone, I gestured pointedly to my crotch. She stifled a laugh. My thin dress pants did little to conceal my erection. It twitched eagerly, as if aware of Liz’s attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s, uh,” she hesitated. “It’s not that noticeable.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come off it, if I walk in there like this I could get arrested.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh please, no one’s gonna call the cops.” She nodded politely at another couple walking up to the coat check as I turned away again. “You might end up having to talk to HR but trust me, those girls know how to party,” she laughed knowingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… That’s not the point, Liz! We need to talk to the research team about the pill!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They went home already. Besides, they said not to worry unless it lasts over eight hours.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s been seven!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Which is &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; than eight.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can’t we go back upstairs to your office and take care of this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We ‘took care of it’ three times already!” She sighed. “…Look, I bought this dress special for tonight.” She gestured at the slinky red backless gown. She looked phenomenal and knew it. “Cheryl’s expecting me to make the rounds and talk to board members. I’m not gonna mess up my hair or makeup just to make you cum again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, then I’ll go take care of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, take a breath. The research team was clear. We could do it a couple times, but then we were supposed to find out how long it lasted. You’re freaking out about nothing. This can’t be the first time you’ve had a boner in public. Just, you know, cover it up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m telling you, I can’t go in there, Liz!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, fine.” She looked around and spotted the door to the coat check room. “Okay, come in here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened the door and pulled me in. The room was divided in two by a partial wall. On one side were several rolling wardrobe carts, shelves of cubbies, and a folding chair. On the other side was the coat check counter. A young blonde woman in a black dress shot us a curious look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hi Kara, thanks again for working the coat check tonight. This is Mike, he’s having a bit of a panic attack, so he’s gonna chill here while I go in, okay?” Kara nodded and turned her attention to a couple who had just walked up to hand her their jackets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike, that’s Kara. She’s the new front-desk girl. You just sit here and be calm. I bet once you get your mind off it, things will settle down and you can come to join me at the party. If not, I’ll be back to get you in a little while. Then I promise I’ll take you upstairs and it’ll be worth the wait, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded, and she gave me a quick kiss on the cheek and bustled out the door, greeting several people by name on her way into the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the next fifteen minutes, Kara hustled back and forth, hanging up coats and jackets, and handing claim tickets to partygoers. Eventually, the flow of guests slowed and stopped. Kara pulled her stool over to sit next to me and regarded me curiously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Panic attack, eh?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not a panic attack,” I responded a bit too forcefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright,” she said, shrugging. “So, why are you hiding from your girlfriend?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s not my girlfriend, she’s my boss, and I’m not hiding, I just can’t go in there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why not?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exasperated, I pulled my hands away, so she could see the large tent in my pants, which had not settled down even a little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She grinned. “I see the problem. Does, uh, does this happen often?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I… look, you know what the company makes, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I’m aware,” she rolled her eyes. “It’s only the most famous sex toy company in the world.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right. But they’ve also got an R&amp;amp;D department, including a pharmaceutical team.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh. I never heard of that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Most people haven’t. They license stuff out or produce it through holding companies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, so I guess you took some kind of new boner pill?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not exactly. My boss, Liz, convinced me to take a pill designed to reduce the male refractory period.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you can do it again after finishing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded. “Liz told me this pill was practically ready for the market, and it would let me go several times in a row.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She laughed. “You make it sound like a work assignment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It kinda is?” I shrugged. “It’s a long story. I’m the assistant for the two women who run the company. This kinda stuff comes with the position.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So… you’re hooking up with Liz?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And Ms. Sandstrom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cheryl Sandstrom, the CEO of the company, and Elizabeth Holman, her second in command, are both fucking their shared assistant?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s hot,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look, I dunno if I’m supposed to be telling anyone that. I’m kinda distracted right now. The point is, Liz had me try this pill, and it works. We did it three times in a row. Then Liz wanted to see how long it would last, I’ve been hard ever since, and I’m kinda going crazy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you just jerk off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liz told me not to. She said it’s important.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ohhh,” she nodded knowingly. “I get it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” I said. “What’s to get?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s your mistress. You have to do what she says. This is a control game.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” I scoffed. “No, it’s not like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It &lt;em&gt;sounds&lt;/em&gt; like it’s like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not, trust me.” I crossed my arms. “I’m not doing a good job explaining. I’m still figuring out how this situation works, but it’s not, like, a domination thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure.” She winked. Before I could protest, she held up her hands as if to wave my objection away. “Look, no judgment. I’ve been exploring submissive relationships myself. It can be exhilarating to give someone control. To place your trust in someone like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I frowned. My cock was throbbing desperately, and I was painfully aware of how close she was sitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The first time for me was really eye-opening.” She bit her lip. “I was on this robotics trip during my senior year of high school. My roommate snuck a guy in, and she caught me watching them fuck. I thought she’d be furious.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She crossed her legs, squirming. “But she came over and told me she knew I was watching and it turned her on. Then she started touching me and telling me what to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fuck me.&lt;/em&gt; I pressed my hand firmly against my cock, not rubbing it, but trying to get some relief. She saw, and scooted her stool closer, leaning in conspiratorially. Her breath was hot in my ear. Her breast was pressed against my arm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She sat on my face and made me lick her while she fingered me. Then she had her boyfriend fuck my mouth while she got me off, and I ended up covered in his cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Groaning, I started rubbing my cock through my pants, but she slapped my wrist and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah-ah-ah, Mike, your mistress wouldn’t like that. She told you not to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She’s not my…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not your mistress, I know,” she said, scoffing. “In college, I tried to explore this side of myself, but all the guys I met either didn’t really get it, or they were a little &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; into it. This one girl, though…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced behind her to make sure there was no one waiting at the counter. Then she spread her legs and lifted her skirt, revealing a simple nude thong. Slowly, she reached down and started stroking with one finger, teasing me with the shape of her lips as she pressed against the thin fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This girl, Mike, she got it. She knew what I needed. She took charge. She told me what to do. She explored my boundaries with me. She’d meet me between classes and take my underwear, or she’d make me unbutton my top until I felt exposed. She’d make out with me until I was flushed and dripping, and then make me go back to class and wait all day before she would let me cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara watched me hungrily as she rubbed herself, enjoying the effect she was having on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One time she sent me to class with a remote-control vibrator and teased me until I thought I was going to leave a puddle in my seat. I ended up running to the bathroom and rubbing one out in a stall. That night, she spanked me for the first time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara bit her lip and squeezed her legs together around her hand. After a moment, she slowly pulled her underwear down. I strained for a glimpse, but her dress fell back into place. As she straightened up, she held the soaked fabric to my face. The heady smell of her arousal filled my senses. I let out a choked groan and gripped the chair tightly. I wanted so badly to pull out my cock and start stroking, but I knew she would stop if I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I learned if I did what she asked, she would reward me. I would come back to her place flooded with desire. She would sit on the couch and drink whiskey and have me lick her pussy until she gushed in my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she talked, Kara unbuckled my belt and unbuttoned my pants. I was panting and eager as she pushed her wet panties into my boxers. I whimpered and lifted my hips to press into her hand, but she pulled away, leaving the fabric wrapped around my twitching shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then she would make me cum. I was always so turned on by that point, that it never took long. She’d bend me over the back of the couch and finger me until I was screaming. Then she would call me a good girl and clean me up and hold me until I fell asleep.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moved forward, slowly lifting her dress. Her lips glistened wetly, bright pink against her pale skin, crowned by a wispy tuft of hair. She straddled my legs, standing over my cock, which was twitching urgently and barely contained by my boxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I also learned if I disobeyed, I would be punished. She introduced me to nipple clamps, spanking, strap-ons, and more. Fuck, this is turning me on telling you all this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gasped as she pushed a finger between her lips, pulling it out again to spread her wetness over her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, she graduated before me and moved away. I still follow her on Instagram.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I imagined pulling out my cock, grabbing her by the hips, and pushing her down on it. She seemed to read my mind because she shook her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No touching, Mike. Your mistress wouldn’t like it. Mine wouldn’t either, for that matter,” she purred. “My new mistress actually got me the job here. Her husband is on the board. Don’t tell anyone, but I think she’s hoping I’ll be like a spy for her and get some info that would let him take control.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some part of my brain recognized this as important information, but I was in no position to process it. She pushed another finger inside herself and started thrusting her hips, enjoying making me watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She makes me flirt with her husband. She bought me a maid outfit. She has me go around with a feather duster and bend over in front of him. Sometimes she fingers me first, until there’s a big wet spot on my panties. Other times she takes them away so he can see my pussy. Then she comes in and pretends to be shocked when she catches him watching me with a hard-on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does he know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah, it’s a game for the two of them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, uh,” I was having trouble concentrating while watching her finger herself. “What does she do when she catches the two of you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She calls us names. She makes me go down on him. She says stuff like ‘Is this what you want? You want this little slut to suck your prick?’ It makes his cock so hard in my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara closed her eyes and moaned at the thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She yanks down my top and pulls on my nipples until I squeal. ‘Let’s get this bitch’s tits out. That’s what you want to see, motherfucker? You get off thinking about her little tits?’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, she reached down and grabbed my hand, pulling it to her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe it’s okay if you touch me a little, Mike, but don’t touch yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded eagerly as I groped her. I could feel her nipples harden through her dress and wished I could suck on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She pushes my head down on his cock until I choke. ‘Look at this slut, she loves it. Fuck, I bet she’s dripping wet.’ Then she reaches behind and shoves a finger in me and says ‘I can’t believe how wet this cunt is right now! She’s been prancing around all day fantasizing about this instead of doing her fucking job.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” I moaned, watching her rub tight circles around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right? Sometimes she spanks me. It turns me on so much getting spanked while I suck her husband’s cock. Between swats, she fingers me, alternating pleasure and pain. ‘Listen to her moan! The little tramp is getting off on this.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I groaned, struggling to resist the urge to do more than touch her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then she makes me climb in his lap and ride him while she berates him. ‘Is this what you wanted? Is this why you got hard when she bent over and presented herself to you? Did you imagine burying your thick prick in her tight little pussy? Don’t cum in her, you dog. I know she’s a thirsty little slut who’s only good for filling with spunk, but don’t you dare.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell,” I gasped. My cock twitched, and I felt a squirt of precum soak into her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. Sometimes she fingers my ass, too. She knows it makes my pussy clench, and it gets him right to the edge.” Kara bit her lip, then laughed. “This one time, she stuck the handle of the feather duster up there while I was riding him.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’d you do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I screamed and came all over him. Then he came inside me. She was &lt;em&gt;furious&lt;/em&gt; with him. Normally she makes him cum on my face or my tits. She made him lick it all out of me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah,” she purred, leaning into my hands. “It was so fucking hot. I think he was into it, you know. Some guys are. After that, she made him sleep on the couch while she helped me shower and let me stay the night with her in their bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara, fuck…” My cock felt like it might explode. “I need…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know. Pull down your pants. I want to look at your cock while I cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, I lifted my ass and shoved my pants and boxers down around my ankles. My cock reached straight up, still wrapped in her thong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” she exhaled. “I wish I could give you what you need. But your mistress will not be happy if I ruin her fun.” She pulled her fingers out and let me suck on them, coating my tongue with the taste of her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I groaned, and my cock twitched, straining for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But I guess it wouldn’t hurt for you to finger me if you promise not to… Ah!” Before she finished, I had two fingers inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, you’re eager,” she gasped, bucking her hips to fuck against my fingers. I pressed up, awkwardly trying to grind my palm against her clit while still fucking her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He really is,” said Liz from behind us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara squealed and jumped away from me, tugging her dress down. Turning around guiltily, she found Liz leaning on the counter. She had a carefully neutral expression as she looked from Kara to me. My pants were bunched around my ankles, Kara’s wet panties wrapped around my cock, and I was shamelessly licking my fingers clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calmly, Liz walked around to the door and let herself into the room. She stood there for a minute, trying to make up her mind how to handle the situation. I couldn’t help but notice her nipples were poking through her dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How long were you there, miss?” Kara whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Long enough to get interested,” Liz replied. “I see that beast hasn’t calmed down any,” she observed, as my cock continued to throb with my heartbeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t let him touch himself, or help him cum,” Kara said with a bit more confidence. “I told him you wouldn’t be happy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz nodded approvingly. “And what was it you called me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“His, um, his mistress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I don’t hate that,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liz,” I started, but she cut me off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll deal with you later.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But I didn’t do anything?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only because she stopped you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I frowned. Kara bit her lip and looked pleased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, Kara, while I’m grateful you managed to keep Mike under control, you &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; get distracted from your job. I left him here to calm down, and I come back to find you both too aroused to think straight. If someone else had come up to the coat check, we’d be having a different conversation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara hung her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Liz said after a long minute. “Mike, poor Kara here tried to be a good girl, but you distracted her. Now she’s so turned on it’s literally running down her thighs.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara’s face turned bright red, and she squeezed her knees together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you need to make it up to her. But Kara, Mike here is uncontrollably erect because of a pill I asked him to try. He was already having a hard time before you started telling him about your adventures. So you need to make it up to him a bit, first.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, miss.” Kara hesitated. “What do you want me to do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To start, I want you to get on your knees and suck his cock. And don’t touch yourself. It’s not your turn, yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, miss.” Kara dropped to her knees in front of me. Her eyes glittered with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike,” Liz cautioned. “You are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; allowed to cum. If you’re getting close, I expect you to let Kara know so she can slow down. You’ll get yours later.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I nodded vaguely, barely able to think straight as Kara licked her lips and stared at my cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike,” Liz warned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yes!” I looked Liz in the eyes. “Yes, I understand.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about the coat check, miss?” Kara asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a little late to think of that now, but don’t worry. The party’s just starting to wind down. I came out early to check on Mike. Still, you are a bit exposed.” She grabbed one of the rolling coat racks and positioned it to block the view from the counter. “Now, I’ll manage the front while you two get started.” With that, she disappeared behind the coats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I &lt;em&gt;told&lt;/em&gt; you she’s your mistress,” Kara mumbled, pleased with herself as she removed her panties from around my cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, she’s—oh!” I gasped as she wrapped her lips around my head. The heat of her mouth felt incredible after being denied any stimulation for so long, and I immediately forgot what I was protesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara quickly fell into a rhythm, one hand wrapped around the base of my shaft and the other cupping my balls. I felt a building pressure, and she moaned happily as a squirt of precum coated her tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, Kara, you better slow down,” I reluctantly mumbled. Disappointed, Kara rocked back, releasing my cock to slowly lick up and down my shaft. I felt the pressure recede a bit. “You’re really fucking good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you,” she purred. “My mistress gives me a lot of practice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Was all that stuff you said true?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Every word of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You weren’t just teasing me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, I was doing that too, but it was all true. I think the reason it excited you so much is you’ve got a little submissive in you, too. I see the way you respond to Liz. Admit it, you like it when a woman tells you what to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, I guess that’s kinda true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does Ms. Sandstrom also tell you what to do when you fool around?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, sometimes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And does it turn you on?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“…Yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you go,” she concluded, taking me back into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A moment later, Liz walked around the coat rack with a claim ticket and grabbed a couple items. She leaned over to whisper in Kara’s ear. “Try to go deeper.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara moaned and changed her angle until I felt my cock bump against the back of her mouth. Liz winked at me and bustled back around to the counter. I tried to keep from groaning loudly as Kara swallowed and bobbed her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara,” I gasped, wrapping my hand around the back of her head. She was determined, rocking back and forth. I grabbed her ponytail and she nodded, squeezing my thighs as I pulled her closer. Abruptly, my cock slipped deeper and we both grunted as her lips reached the base of my shaft. Her throat was hot and tight and my cock was throbbing. She gagged, but let me keep holding her in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz reappeared with another claim ticket and whispered, “Easy there, Kara. If you want that monster inside you, don’t make him cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But, the pill,” I gasped, “I can go again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Control yourself, or I’ll separate you.” She was clearly enjoying herself. “Now, why don’t you trade places and show her how you got your job.” She walked toward the counter, but said over her shoulder, “And don’t touch yourself!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reluctantly, I let her go. Kara rocked back away from me, coughing and wiping drool from her chin, but with a look of triumph in her eyes. My cock was swollen large and purple as I took Kara’s spot on the floor. She excitedly hiked up her dress and leaned back in the chair, spreading her legs wide for me. Her lips were puffy with desire, and her wetness had indeed been dripping down her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I licked slowly and steadily up her legs. She bit her finger to keep from making any noise when I finally reached my goal. I traced over and between her lips and toward her clit, already standing proud. I teased around it, licking up and down repeatedly until she was quivering with need, then I closed my lips and swirled my tongue. She squeaked and grabbed the back of my head, holding me firmly in place like I had done to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara was already close to cumming, I could tell. She gasped and squirmed in the chair as I pushed my tongue deep inside before returning to suck lightly on her clit. When I slipped two fingers in, they entered easily, as if her velvety walls were pulling me deeper. I curled my fingers and she bucked her hips, trying not to cry out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt her pussy clenching and a gush of warm fluid, but she didn’t let go. Her breathing was ragged and she was cursing under her breath over and over. She tightened her grip on my hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I pushed a finger into her ass, she let out a long, low moan, and clamped her thighs around my head. I kept going, moving my fingers and my tongue as her legs shook like an earthquake around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, she released me. She gasped as I slowly eased my fingers out and covered her clit with my palm, applying firm, gentle pressure to her entire vulva. She bit her lip and squeezed her legs again around my hand for a long moment before finally pushing me away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stood up and took a step back, only to bump into Liz. “Good job, Mike.” She rested her chin on my shoulder and reached around to grip my cock, which felt so hard it might burst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What now, miss?” Kara was still breathing heavily, and grinned at Liz and me, lewdly spreading her thighs as an invitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, Mike, I think you’d better fuck her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I cum?” I gulped, desperate for release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only if she asks you to.” Liz kissed my neck, and stepped away, grabbing some items before returning to the front.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara pushed the chair away and lay on the floor as I dropped to my knees again. I rubbed the head of my cock against her opening, coating it in her cream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it, Mike, fuck me please,” Kara breathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, I shoved my cock rudely inside. She accepted me easily, choking back a squeal as I buried myself to the hilt. I groaned as I felt her insides clenching me already. She threw her arms and legs around me and kissed me desperately, trying to pull me even closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started fucking her. Not slow and sensual, but urgent and demanding. Forceful. She buried her face in my shoulder, biting me to stifle her yelps of pleasure. I could already feel the pressure building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara,” I gasped. But before I could ask to cum, we heard a loud woman’s voice from the counter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where is Kara? She was working the coat check. What are you doing here, Ms. Holman?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hello, Mrs. Sackwell. She, um, had to,” Liz sounded flustered as she tried to think of an answer. “She ran to the bathroom. I’m just covering for her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit,” Kara hissed in my ear. “Mike, that’s my mistress. Quick, quick, cum! Cum for me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fucked her harder. I wanted nothing more in the world than to cum with my cock buried in her pussy. Kara gave up all effort to be quiet and started crying out loudly with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara?” I heard the voice from the front say. “What’s going on here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz protested, but I didn’t care, my orgasm was imminent. Kara’s nails dug into my back as she continued to urge me to cum. “Do it—Ah!—Mike! Cum—Uh!—Fuck!—Cum inside—Ah!—Cum in me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The door to the coat check room opened. A woman in her late 40s wearing an expensive green gown with long sleeves stood aghast in the doorway. Liz followed, pushing her into the room and closing the door behind them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stop fucking her this instant!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But…” I protested, knowing I was about to cum. Before I could do anything, Kara pushed me away, but I was already cumming. The first spurt happened just as I slipped out, frosting her lips and clit. The second shot high as I rocked back on my knees, arcing through the air to fall across the bosom of her dress. The third splashed onto her stomach, and the rest fell on the floor as I rocked in place, grunting and unable to control myself during my long-delayed climax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus,” the woman cursed, watching Kara’s flushed face as she tried to regain her composure. “Kara, stand up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes… Mistress,” Kara panted. She got shakily to her feet, awkwardly pulling her cum-splattered dress down to cover herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Unbelievable,” the woman muttered. “I buy you a new dress and the first thing you do is get spunk all over it. You’re going to have to be punished for this, of course.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, Mistress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hand me those,” she snapped at me, gesturing to Kara’s discarded panties on the floor. I picked them up and sheepishly offered them while failing to pull up my pants. She took them and started wiping the cum from Kara’s dress, but gave up when she saw it was mostly just smearing things around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, whatever.” She dropped the soaked underwear on the floor and turned to glare at Liz while pointing at me. “If you can’t control your dog, he should be on a leash.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, mistress,” Liz replied sardonically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Humph. Kara, come with me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Mistress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara allowed herself to be led out of the room but made a “call me” gesture to Liz. There was an excited sparkle in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fucking hell, Liz,” I exhaled as the door closed. “That was intense.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” Liz replied thoughtfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can we please go upstairs and fuck now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Liz looked down to see I was already hard again and laughed. “Oh! Well, unfortunately, we just lost our coat check girl. But if you sit here patiently like a good boy, I promise I’ll reward you later.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, mistress,” I replied teasingly as I sat back down in the chair, my cock twitching eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liz bit her lip and went back to the counter.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Temporary Futa: a futa-on-female erotic romance</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/temporary-futa/"/>
		<published>2024-03-10T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/temporary-futa/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="futanari" />
    <category term="transgender" />
    <category term="lesbian" />
    <category term="science fiction" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/temporary-futa-UGqFM8XP2c-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Olivia and Trish are best friends. But when Trish orders a “temporary futanari” pill from a Russian catalog to “see how the other side lives,” in addition to growing a rather impressive member, she also develops an unstoppable libido. Now she needs Liv’s help to get out of the office before anyone notices there’s something extra under her skirt. But they’ll have to make it through a crowded elevator, a stimulating Uber ride, and past a room full of hotties. And once they get to the apartment… will the things they’ve experienced on the way change their friendship into something more?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This intense story of overwhelming arousal and public stimulation builds to a &lt;em&gt;well-hung&lt;/em&gt; climax.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CXQ8QKTC"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Lunch Buddies: a friends to lovers erotic romance</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/books/lunch-buddies/"/>
		<published>2024-03-07T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-03-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/books/lunch-buddies/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="books" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/lunch-buddies-edAtVNR7sP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hot new book from Ruby Pink!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Ashley was excited to get lunch with her old college friend Tony while he was in town for work. But when he walked into her office, a rather awkward situation arose… in his pants. The new medication he was taking had some unexpected side effects, including an enhanced libido. Now, there’s no way they can leave her office with him in this state. Lucky for Tony, Ash has a plan…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This smoking hot five-part story features escalating intensity and desire between Ash and Tony with each passing day, a well-earned climax on Friday, and a romantic epilogue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0CXJQ2XCF"&gt;Buy it now on Amazon!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Lunch Buddies 5: Friday</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/5-friday/"/>
		<published>2024-02-09T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-02-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/5-friday/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="work" />
    <category term="cowgirl" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="no panties" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/lunch-buddies-edAtVNR7sP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The morning seemed to drag on forever. Meeting after meeting after meeting. Ash kept checking the clock, astonished at how slowly time was passing. She was restless and distracted, and all she could think about was how long she had to wait until lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, shortly before noon, Tony texted: “On my way!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She responded with a biting lip emoji and went back to pretending to listen as the other department heads droned on. The meeting was almost over. Just a few more minutes. The engineering manager was making an uninspired point at great length. She tapped her fingernail against her laptop impatiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One minute left. He showed no sign of wrapping up. She made eye contact and looked pointedly toward the clock on the wall. He nodded and gestured for her to wait a moment. She glared at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few minutes past noon, another employee knocked on the glass conference room door and gestured at his watch. The engineering manager laughed and said, “I guess someone else has the room booked. I’ll write up the rest of my thoughts and email everyone.” Ash was already walking out the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She found Tony waiting by her office, awkwardly holding his bag in front of him. He smiled as she came bustling up. Her assistant caught her eye, glanced at Tony, and winked as she picked up her bag to go to lunch. Ash tried not to blush as she pushed him inside, closing the door behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry I’m late,” she said, taking off her cardigan and draping it over the back of her chair. “That meeting just would not end.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s fine,” he said amicably. “I just got here, like, thirty seconds ago.” He dropped his bag and grinned sheepishly as she checked out the rather dramatic hard-on struggling to be contained by his jeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wow,” she laughed, arms crossed over her chest. “Were there lots of hot women on your walk over here today? Or did that girl at the office let you look down her top again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Actually, no.” He hesitated for a moment. “I mean, I’ve still been turned on all morning, but, it’s all you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ash, I can’t stop thinking about you. After yesterday, it was a struggle to get through the rest of the work day. When I got back to my hotel room, I had to go rub one out immediately. I came so hard that I got light-headed. And then again, when I woke up at three AM from a dream about you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s funny,” she smiled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why’s that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Me too.” She closed the distance quickly, pushing him back against the wall and kissing him urgently. He wrapped her in his arms, pulling her tight. She moved her hands up his chest and released a small moan as his tongue slipped into her mouth. He ran his hands down her back to grab her ass. She felt his erection against her hip and pushed into it. He grunted and let go, breaking the kiss as he fumbled with the buttons on her blouse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip and helped him, anticipating his reaction. He groaned appreciatively as she opened her top, and he realized she wasn’t wearing a bra. Immediately, he turned around so she was against the wall and lowered his head to her chest. She gasped as he pulled her nipple into the heat of his mouth. It stiffened quickly as his tongue swirled. He squeezed both breasts, alternating sides until she was squirming and panting from the stimulation. He moved his hand down to reach under her skirt, but she brushed it away, not ready yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pushing away from the wall, they staggered toward the couch. She kissed him awkwardly, walking and unbuckling his belt at the same time. When his calves bumped into the couch, she was already unbuttoning his jeans. He did an eager little shimmy to help her tug them down his legs, leaving them bunched around his ankles. His cock sprang free, almost slapping her in the face, and she laughed as she pushed him down and dropped to her knees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stifled a loud groan as she wrapped her lips around him. She eagerly reached one hand up under his shirt, touching his chest, the other wrapped around the base of his shaft. She licked and sucked, tracing around the rim of his head. He worked his fingers into her hair, and lifted his hips, whispering her name. She fell into an easy rhythm, her hand and mouth moving in tandem along the length of his shaft, pumping him into her mouth. A squirt of precum coated her tongue, and she moaned happily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Ash… Oh fuck, I love that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything was happening fast. The arousal that had been smoldering all morning had erupted into a blazing inferno. Knowing that he felt the same desire she did, the same burning need, only made it more intense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She squeezed her legs together and felt a little trickle drip down her thigh. She still had one more surprise for him, and if she wasn’t careful, he’d cum before discovering it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She released him and rocked back on her heels, producing a groan of disappointment from him. His cock pointed straight up, glistening wetly, bobbing with his heartbeat, and demanding attention. She wiped her mouth with the back of her hand and got to her feet. Her shirt had fallen off one shoulder, and his eyes were locked on her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“God damn, you are so fucking sexy,” he exclaimed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She smiled and squeezed her breasts together for him. She didn’t dance, exactly, but slowly gyrated a bit, holding his attention and making him wait. She wanted to slow him down just a bit, make him last longer. He didn’t seem to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tony, do you want to suck on my nipples some more?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded emphatically, and she moved toward him, swaying her hips seductively. His cock twitched eagerly as she climbed on top, knees on either side of him, lifting her skirt as she did so it wouldn’t get trapped between them. Hands on his shoulders, she settled her weight onto his lap. He was so distracted by her tits in his face that it took him a moment to realize his cock was pressed against her wet lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit, you’re not wearing any panties,” he gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I took them off in the bathroom between meetings.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s fucking hot,” he groaned as she rocked against him, sliding up and down the length of his shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My nipples,” she reminded him, pulling his head to her chest. He enthusiastically started licking and sucking as she continued to roll her hips. His cock was firm and unyielding under her skirt. Her lips parted around him, and she felt her slick juices coating him. She adjusted her angle to put more pressure on her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm! Mmm-hmmm…” He seemed to be enjoying himself. She gripped his shoulders harder, digging her fingernails in as she rocked faster. His tongue lashed against her breast, and his cock swelled urgently between her lips. He tried to shift lower, wanting more, wanting to be inside her. She moved with him, still slipping along the lower half of his shaft, not letting his tip near her opening yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tony,” she gasped, “you’ll make me cum.” The pressure was building. She buried her face in his hair, panting as she rode him. “Ah! Please, make me cum.” She bucked her hips, relentlessly grinding her clit against the throbbing heat of his erection. “Make me cum!” He sucked harder, pinching and rolling her other nipple, still doing his best to thrust against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” She squealed as she felt her insides start clenching. “I’m cumming, I’m cumming!” Tony groaned into her breast as a gush of hot liquid washed over him. He released her nipple with a wet pop and dropped his head onto the back of the couch, staring into her eyes as she climaxed on top of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, Ash,” he pleaded, “let me fuck you.” She nodded eagerly, and finally lifted herself enough to reach the top of his cock, let it slip in, and slowly lower herself onto him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Your pussy feels so good,” he gasped. She could only groan in agreement. His cock filled her perfectly, her lips wrapped around the base of his shaft. She leaned forward and kissed him deeply, shivering as his cock twitched inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she started rocking, raising herself up and then dropping back down into him. She closed her eyes and moaned into his mouth as she fucked him. She felt his hands move under her skirt to grab her ass, moving her more emphatically. She broke the kiss and buried her face in his neck, panting with each thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, fuck me, Ash, I’m close…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He dug his fingers into her ass, gripping her firmly and fucking her against him. Her aftershocks were still coming, or maybe just more, smaller orgasms, one after another after another. Her soaking pussy repeatedly tightened around him, making him groan and fuck her even harder. The wet sounds of their fucking seemed like it was so loud the entire floor would hear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ash, oh fuck, oh fuck, I want to cum,” he grunted, his cock swelling inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Do it, do it, cum for me,” she begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Inside?” He gasped out the question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yesss!” She barely said the word before his entire body went rigid. His cock was throbbing inside her, and she felt his hot cum. “Oh my god, Tony, cum in me, cum in me, cum in me…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He came for a long time, it seemed. She slowed down as he relaxed, and stopped moving entirely when he let go of her ass. She wrapped her arms around his shoulders and nuzzled his ear. After a minute, he grunted as she squeezed his softening cock, and it slipped out of her with a squelch. She squeaked as she felt his cum drip out of her, and he laughed, then kissed her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” she purred happily. “I’ve been waiting for that all week.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really?” He sounded surprised, but not unhappy. “Why didn’t you say something?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, I didn’t know I was waiting for &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; specifically. But as soon as you showed up on Monday, I knew something was coming.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To think, we could have been doing this since college.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, it wouldn’t have been this good in college.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You think?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, we weren’t ready.” She nuzzled his neck. “We both had to learn some things, I think.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm.” He considered that for a moment. “So, what now?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was thinking pizza.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No,” he laughed, playfully smacking her ass. “I mean, what now with us?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know,” she said, giving him a kiss. “I guess we’ll see.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three Months Later…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ash smiled as she stretched in bed. She’d had some very enjoyable dreams. Still pleasantly groggy, she reached for her phone. She wasn’t surprised to see a text from Tony. They’d been talking every day since his visit. He was a few time zones ahead of her, so she often had messages waiting from him when she woke up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first, it had been mostly sexual. She had an impressive collection of his dick pics, which she’d been surprised to find she didn’t hate when they weren’t unsolicited. She’d sent him some sexy pics as well, which he was always appreciative of. And then it wasn’t long until they were masturbating together on video calls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But even after he finally talked to his doctor and changed his meds (at her prompting), they’d kept talking. Flirting and sexy messages were easy and fun, but increasingly there were some real conversations. Sometimes they talked late into the evening, about everything and nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked forward to telling him about the funny things that happened to her and hearing about his. He was quickly becoming the first person she thought of when she had something to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were both aware of the growing intimacy, but they hadn’t talked about it. As long as he lived on the other side of the country, it felt dangerous to acknowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rubbed her eyes and read the text three times, her smile growing wider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey Ash, remember that client I was working with when I visited? They offered me a full-time position. It would mean moving over there. What do you think? 🤔😅”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think that sounds great. 💋”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Lunch Buddies 4: Thursday</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/4-thursday/"/>
		<published>2024-02-08T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-02-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/4-thursday/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="work" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/lunch-buddies-edAtVNR7sP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Ash had been up late with a confusing mix of thoughts. On the one hand, there was the kiss. They’d never kissed like that before. There had been a few experimental kisses back in college, while they were still exploring their boundaries. But those never had the heat or the passion they’d shared yesterday. What did it mean? Was she catching feelings? Was he? How would happen when he flew home after this week? Was this still strictly casual, or was she overthinking it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, her body was still crackling with desire whenever she thought about him. The way he watched her. The way he touched himself for her. The way his thighs tensed up when he was getting close to an orgasm. The way his cock felt in her mouth. The way her pussy clenched when he started cumming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even after she fell asleep, her dreams had been a confusing mess of maybe-feelings and unbridled lust. Tony was everywhere, touching her, holding her, kissing her, pulling down her underwear. His hands squeezing her breasts, caressing her sides, grabbing her ass, and spreading her thighs. His mouth moving down her body, sucking on her nipples, licking her hips, lower and lower. She opened her lips for his cock, but it remained frustratingly out of reach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d woken up tangled in her shirt from tossing and turning, with a wet spot on her panties. She still wasn’t sure if the kiss meant anything, but she knew what she wanted for today, at least. Going down on him had been both unplanned and surprisingly hot. She wanted him to return the favor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before even getting out of bed, she texted him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Today it’s my turn.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He responded immediately with a thumbs-up. She grinned and pulled her covers higher, scrunching lower for a few more minutes of cozy time before showering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Ash.” He knocked on her door frame, grinning as she jumped up from her desk, pulled him into her office, and shut the door firmly behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was ready for him. She’d chosen a flirty sundress that wasn’t quite appropriate for the office but was passable with the cardigan that was currently draped over the back of her chair. Below the low neckline, she wore the demi bra that she normally hated because her boobs had a tendency to fall out of the cups, but today that was an advantage. The skirt was flirty and twirly and would be easy to pull up so he could remove her thong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She leaned against the door and bit her lip as he dropped his bag. It might have been her imagination, but his erection seemed more noticeable than yesterday. She dragged a finger along her neckline, teasing him with a peek of lace as she sauntered towards him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, it’s your turn today,” he winked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I think it’s only fair,” she replied, standing very close. She ran her hand down the buttons of his shirt, past his belt buckle, and lower, to trace the outline of his shaft. “If you can handle that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Depends if you keep doing that,” he said, eyes locked on her cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Doing what?” She cupped her hand over his straining cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Getting me all worked up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm,” she responded. “I dunno about that. Seems like you were already worked up.” He twitched under her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ash…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes?” She leaned in, pressing her chest against him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should stop,” he breathed, closing his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should make me stop,” she purred, squeezing his cock firmly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned, grabbed her shoulders, and turned her around. She laughed and let go, but leaned back against him. He lowered his hands to her hips, half-heartedly holding her away. She felt his hot breath on the back of her neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s… uh,” he paused as she pushed back more firmly, grinding her ass into his groin. “It’s supposed to be your turn…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh,” she agreed, enjoying the effect she was having on him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then, why…” He trailed off as she moved his hands to her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told you,” she said, helping him scoop her breasts out of her top. “I want you to make me stop.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” he said, distracted by her hard nipples under his palms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” He said again, getting it. “I see.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let go of her chest, put one hand on her hip, and wrapped the other around her ponytail. She gasped excitedly as he pushed her forward, taking the pressure off his cock and pulling her head so she was looking up at the ceiling. She felt his stubble against her neck and his lips against her ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Today,” he growled, in a way that made her knees go a little wobbly. “Is going to be your turn. You’re going to stop distracting me and give me a chance to do for you what you did for me yesterday, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip and nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go put your hands on your desk.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He released her hair, and she walked to her desk. Slowly, she put her palms on top. She heard him take a few deep breaths, centering himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, lift up your dress.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited, she lifted the hem, holding it up above her waist. She heard a sharp intake of breath when he saw her thong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bend over.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gathered the fabric in one hand, holding it in place as she leaned on her elbows. She felt deliciously exposed. Her heart raced as she felt him approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Spread your legs.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She did as he asked, and felt him drop to his knees behind her. His hands caressed her ass, then moved slowly over her hips and down the outside of her legs, before traveling back up her inner thighs. She inhaled with anticipation, but he pulled his hands away at the last moment. He did that several more times until she was quivering and desperate for more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She gasped excitedly when she felt a finger brush against the thin fabric that was the only thing separating them. Still moving slowly and touching lightly, he traced the edges of her thong. He moved past her lips, reaching under to brush against her mound, then pulling back and allowing a knuckle to graze against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just as she was about to demand more, he increased the pressure. His hands gripped her cheeks, pushing them together and spreading them apart. He rubbed his long fingers over her underwear, describing a broad circle around her clit before dragging back up, sending sparks up her spine as his fingertips teased against her opening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He touched her gently but firmly, increasing the pressure until she purred. His fingers explored everywhere, rubbing and caressing. She could tell by the way the fabric clung to her lips that she was getting wet. She knew he could feel it, too, by his increasing focus on her cleft. Her breath was coming quicker now, and she gripped the fabric of her dress tightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he roughly pulled her thong down, leaving her exposed. He helped her step out of her underwear and threw it carelessly toward the couch. Then he grabbed her with two hands, thumbs on her lips, and spread her open. She gasped as she felt his hot breath against her wet skin. He seemed to be savoring the sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He made her wait for what felt like long minutes but was probably only seconds. Her heart was pounding. She forced herself to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At last, he licked the full length of her. The sensation made her knees buckle for a moment, but he was holding her up. His tongue pushed between her spread lips to her opening and probed deep. He moaned happily as he began to lap up her cream. He licked everywhere, tracing her swollen lips and pulling them into his mouth. She arched her back to give him better access, encouraging him to move toward her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, my god,” she purred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He took the hint and focused on her most sensitive spot, teasing around her bud, and closing his lips around her. She grunted as he slipped a finger inside. She pushed her keyboard and other desk stuff away so she could drop from her elbows, laying her chest directly on the desktop. The wood was cool against her exposed breasts. She gripped the edge with one hand and brought the other to cover her mouth, not trusting herself to keep quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony’s head pressed firmly forward, licking and sucking and rubbing. The room seemed to be filled with the wet sounds of her pleasure. His finger moved insistently inside her, another bumping invitingly against her back door. She was rolling her hips without meaning to, mashing her pussy against his face. There was a quickly building pressure in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah fuck, Tony,” she gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned in reply, which sent vibrations through her. She bucked as his tongue flicked insistently on her clit. The movement caused his finger, already slick with her wetness, to slip into her ass. She barely managed not to squeal loudly. It felt good, but the stimulation was getting intense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanting something to suck on, she put her own fingers into her mouth. His tongue swirled urgently around her clit, licking up her dripping arousal. She squirmed, tensing her thighs and moving her knees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His fingers were thrusting into her now, coated with her juices. She moaned and matched his pace, fucking her mouth, imagining it was his cock. She groaned as she felt her climax approaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Gonna make me cummm,” she murmured around her fingers. Her entire body was tensing, her insides starting to clench. Desperately, she reached back, grabbing a handful of his hair and holding him firmly against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sparks and flashes of color flared behind her tightly closed eyelids. Tony grunted in surprise as she gushed in his mouth, but eagerly swallowed and kept moving with her. She squeezed tightly around him with each wave of pleasure that rolled through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she let go. He rocked back, gasping for breath. He removed his fingers, causing a nearly overwhelming wave of sensation that made her gasp, and then collapse, trying to catch her breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For several minutes she lay there on her desk, face buried in her arm, unaware of anything beyond the soft aftershocks of her orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, it took a moment for her to realize what she was hearing. Tony was standing behind her, desperately stroking himself with the hand he’d been fucking her with, using her cum as lubrication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still aroused, she rolled over on her back so she could see. He stepped forward, between her spread legs, the tip of his cock nearly touching her lips. Her juices were dripping from his chin, and there was an intense look in his eyes. She knew he was ready to cum. Knew that getting her off had left him right on the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They stared at each other as the moment stretched. His cock was right there, slick with her cream and his precum. Her cunt was thrumming and eager. He could enter her in a heartbeat. She knew he would thrust inside and immediately climax. One stroke into her velvety heat, and he’d fill her with cum. She gasped at the intensity of the image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He must have been thinking the same thing. He moved his hips forward just enough to rub against her clit. She jumped, and he groaned. He retreated, still stroking his cock, then did it again. As he pulled back, a squirt of precum fell on her skin like a promise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck. She wanted this. It wasn’t what she’d planned for today, but now she wanted to take him. To see the look on his face as he entered her. To feel his cock twitching and pumping deep in her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Urgently, she reached down, intending to grab him and put him between her lips. But as soon as she touched his cock, he groaned and started cumming. She gasped as she felt hot cum splash through her fingers and drip onto her lips. All she could do was squeeze and milk him as he thrust repeatedly into her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, he groaned and fell forward, head on her chest. He panted, heart pounding against her as his cock softened and slipped from her fingers. She savored his weight on top of her, as his cum dripped slowly down her ass onto the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh well, she thought, grinning and biting her lip. There was still tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Lunch Buddies 3: Wednesday</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/3-wednesday/"/>
		<published>2024-02-07T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-02-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/3-wednesday/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="work" />
    <category term="phone" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/lunch-buddies-edAtVNR7sP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;When Tony arrived at her office the next day, she was stuck on a never-ending phone call. She waved him into the room, motioning for him to shut the door, and making a “won’t stop talking” gesture at the phone. He nodded knowingly and wandered over to the couch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, Linda, I’ve gotta wrap this up. I’ve got… Yes… Uh-huh.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linda was the HR rep in the Springfield office. She was a very nice person, and great at her job, but she also was completely incapable of ending a phone call on time. Sighing inwardly, Ash watched Tony check out the view from her window. Her own gaze was drawn to the clear shape of the erection straining against his slacks. As if aware of her attention, it twitched, and he reached down to adjust it. She very badly wanted Linda to stop talking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Linda, I understand your concerns, but we can talk about that in our next one-on-one, because… Sure, no, I get that… Right…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony looked away from the window and caught her staring. He winked and started exaggeratedly rubbing his hard-on through his pants. She stifled a laugh and made a wanking gesture back at him. He pretended to look shocked, and then shrugged and started slowly unbuckling his belt, clearly expecting her to tell him to stop. She didn’t. She’d been looking forward to this all morning. He pulled his cock out, and she grinned encouragingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, we’ve gotta put a pin in this conversation, because it’s time for… No, no, of course it matters, but… No… Sure.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’d seen a lot of his cock in the last two days, but it still gave her a thrill. The idea that she was encouraging him to jerk off in front of her, in her office, during the workday, was so wildly inappropriate it got her blood pumping. Sure, it was lunchtime, so most people were out, and it was true no one would open her door without knocking, but still. It wasn’t locked or anything. Someone &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; walk in. She’d been completely topless on Monday! And yesterday, someone could have found her covered in spunk. It was embarrassing how much that thought turned her on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip and watched him touch himself as Linda kept talking about some job postings that needed to be filled. (That’s not the only thing that needs filling, she thought, and then had to stop herself from laughing.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Linda, I… No, not at all…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;God, this was getting confusing. Linda was chattering away about work stuff in her ear, and she was watching Tony masturbate for her. He seemed to sense that her being on the phone made this even riskier than normal, and was doing his best to stay quiet. She crossed and uncrossed her legs, restless with growing arousal. Without thinking about it, she idly caressed her breast with her free hand. He watched, drawn as always to any indication she was getting excited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I understand, but seriously, can this wait… No, I mean I’ve got…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck this. Tony was moving full speed ahead, and she was missing it. She beckoned him to come closer, wanting a better view. As he stood up and walked toward her, hand still moving along his shaft, she slouched lower in her chair and awkwardly hiked her skirt up with one hand. He followed her lead and moved to stand between her spread legs, masturbating over her. She shivered, a wave of lust rolling down her spine as she started stroking herself over her underwear. There was already a damp spot on the gusset. He watched eagerly as she traced her fingers over her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm… I mean, uh, Linda, I’ve got lunch plans…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She started touching herself more firmly, pressing against her slit. Tony’s hands moved aggressively, pumping along his shaft, thumb caressing his helmet. It was really turning her on having him standing over her like this, with her legs spread wantonly. She slipped her hand into her underwear, teasing a finger between her juicy lips. He choked back an excited sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, I, uh… I’ve gotta, um, excuse me, Linda.” She held the receiver away for a moment and whispered to Tony, “Help me take these off,” then put the phone back to her ear. Linda was still talking. “Right. Yes, I see…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony immediately dropped to his knees and helped pull her underwear down as she lifted her hips. He bit his lip as he slipped them past her knees, and helped her pull one foot out, leaving them hanging around one ankle. Normally, that would bother her, but right now, she didn’t care. She spread her legs wide again, inviting Tony closer as she pushed two fingers inside, stifling a gasp. He got back to his feet and moved as close as he could, until their thighs were pressed together. She started fucking herself as she stared hungrily at his cock, bobbing in front of her as he jerked off over her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously, Linda, I, uh…” A bead of precum glistened on his tip. She licked her lips. Any second now, it would roll down and get wiped away. “I need to put something in my mouth, er, I mean, I’m famished…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unable to resist, Ash abruptly leaned forward and licked up the precum. Tony made a startled noise but didn’t stop masturbating or move away. She sat on the edge of her chair, two fingers buried in her pussy, his cock right in front of her mouth. She parted her lips, moving closer until he groaned softly at the heat of her breath against his skin. Her heartbeat was pounding so loud she could barely hear Linda. She gave him another lick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… um… I just… I need…” She looked up, meeting Tony’s eyes. He was watching her with clear desire, praying she would go further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please,” he mouthed. Feeling a surge of lust, she took him into her mouth, sealing her lips around his head. Slowly, she pulled him deeper. She started moving her fingers in her now-dripping pussy, fucking herself as she sucked his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god,” he whispered, nearly overwhelmed. “Your mouth is so hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm-hmm,” she agreed for both his and Linda’s benefit and started bobbing her head, sliding him in and out. He unconsciously matched her pace, moving his hips to meet her. He put a hand on top of her head but didn’t push or pull, just encouraging her, showing her that he was into it. Not that she had any doubt. His cock was throbbing, and a squirt of precum coated her tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She couldn’t believe she was doing this. It was one thing to close her door and fool around on her lunch break. It was another to have fingers in her pussy and a cock in her mouth during a work call. Her entire system seemed to be crackling with desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“MMMmmm-hmm,” she said, trying to make her involuntary moan sound like a response to whatever Linda was still talking about. She felt her insides clench and a small gush of hot liquid run over her fingers to soak into the cushion of her chair. She didn’t care. He was thrusting more eagerly now. She tried to relax her throat so she wouldn’t gag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Agh!” Tony grunted as he pushed forward. She wanted to take him deeper but tensed up, choked, and had to pull away. He slipped from her mouth with an embarrassingly loud wet sound. Even Linda couldn’t miss that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, No, I’m sorry, Linda,” she coughed. “I had to start eating my lunch, and I choked on… a bit of cucumber.” Fuck. Her eyes were watering. She squeezed her thighs around her hand, her insides tightening around her fingers. “But I really do need to go now, and get something to wash this down, I’ll talk to you later, bye!” She said the whole last bit in a rush, before Linda had a chance to start talking again, and dropped the receiver back onto the base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked up at Tony, still trying to catch her breath and feeling very wet. He stared at her with awe and lust in his eyes as she dropped to her knees. Now that she wasn’t holding the phone, she had a free hand to grab his cock and pull him closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus, Ash, this is so goddamn hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of answering, she just took him into her mouth. He groaned, and his cock twitched as she started swirling her tongue around the ridge and flicking against the tip. She gripped him firmly near the base of his shaft, stroking up every time she bobbed her head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly they fell into a rhythm. This wasn’t flirtatious or teasing anymore. They were both on the edge. She wanted to make him climax. She wanted to feel his cock pulsing, taste his cum, and swallow him as deeply as she could. They moved as one, him thrusting forward, and her taking him. One hand wrapped around his cock, and the other urgently fucking herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh shit, Ash, oh fuck, please make me cum,” he begged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She moaned in agreement. Her juices were dripping down her hand. His taste seemed to saturate her: musky, a little bitter… pure lust. His hand wrapped around the back of her head, more firmly this time, grabbing her hair, and pulling her forward as he pushed in. She swallowed him, felt him slip deeper than ever, fully into her throat, and start twitching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m cumming, I’m cumming, I’m cumming,” he groaned over and over. His cock was throbbing, pumping hot cum. She wanted it all, wanted to take everything he would give her. She moaned with pleasure, her pussy clenching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, he staggered back, leaning against the wall and panting with exertion. She stifled a cough, and slipped her fingers out of herself, shivering at the now overwhelming sensation. Her hand was coated with her slick, creamy juices, and almost before she knew she was doing it, she stood up and pushed her fingers into his mouth. She gasped as he licked up every bit of her cum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then she surprised herself again by leaning in and kissing him deeply. He made a surprised sound but eagerly kissed her back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’d never kissed back in college. Somehow that had felt more intimate than masturbating together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She broke away and rested her head on his shoulder. He wrapped his arms around her and held her as they came down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he ventured. “Do you… want to talk about that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not yet,” she answered simply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” he said, wisely. “Want to go get lunch?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Lunch Buddies 2: Tuesday</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/2-tuesday/"/>
		<published>2024-02-06T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-02-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/2-tuesday/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="work" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/lunch-buddies-edAtVNR7sP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Ash wasn’t surprised when Tony texted the next day asking if she wanted to get lunch again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’d had a very nice time together. He paid for her food with his per diem. They chatted about college. He gave her a polite hug, the kind you’d give to an old friend you were just seeing briefly while you were in town. He said goodbye as if he wouldn’t see her again anytime soon. She smiled, kissed him on the cheek, and didn’t believe it for a second.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And now here he was again in her doorway, holding his bag in front of himself and looking nervous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey there, stranger,” she smiled, “Come on in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thanks, I, uh…” He stepped in, and gestured uncertainly at the door, closing it behind him when she nodded. “My other lunch plans fell through, and I wasn’t sure if you had plans of your own…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Tony,” she cut him off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to put your bag down?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, uh, sure.” He dropped his bag by the wall and stood awkwardly, not covering the erection tenting his pants, but not fully confident of her reaction, either. “So, you know, like I said, my lunch plans fell through…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She crossed her legs and raised an eyebrow at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And, uh…” He looked flustered. “It was so great to see you…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sighed. “It was great to see me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes?” He was confused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, Tony.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? I…” he stammered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When did you get this timid?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Timid?” He frowned. “I’m just trying to be polite.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, look, sit down,” she said, gesturing at the couch. “Do you remember yesterday you were telling me how exciting it was in college to go back to my dorm between classes? How I’d act like I was doing you a favor, and then I’d get into it? And knowing that I was into it made it hotter?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The part you’re leaving out, or maybe forgetting, is that &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; were into it too. Like, I knew what was going to happen every time I invited you up. You weren’t pushy about it. You weren’t a dick. I knew I could draw a line, and you’d respect it. You were eager. You were &lt;em&gt;enthusiastic&lt;/em&gt; about anything we did. That’s what excited me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That makes sense,” he agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But now you come in here all hesitant, dancing around the point, acting like you just happened to find yourself free, and wouldn’t it be nice to get lunch again?” She laughed. “Fuck, I bet you were about to try some line like ‘Oh, I couldn’t stop thinking about you last night.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No? Maybe you were hoping that I’d lick my lips and stick out my tits and tell you &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; couldn’t stop thinking about &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; last night?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ash, fuck, I’m sorry if I misread the situation…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because I couldn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wait, what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I went to bed and tossed and turned and couldn’t stop thinking about you. About you masturbating in my office. About the hunger in your eyes when I touched myself for you. It was fucking electric. When I finally pulled out my vibrator, I came &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; hard.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Really.” She laughed. “I had to get a towel.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, wow.” She leaned back and smiled at him. “And now you walk in here with this,” she gestured dismissively, “soft romantic bullshit. Well, I’m sorry, but that’s not why I said yes when you texted.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” he laughed. “How can I make it up to you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you start by telling me why you really texted me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, I can do that. There’s this girl at the office—cute, red hair. After a meeting, she was picking up some papers that fell on the ground and I could see down her top. She was wearing a red bra.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s all it took?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No. She had kinda small boobs, and as she leaned further down, the cup of her bra kinda pushed out, and I caught a glimpse of her pierced nipple.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm, interesting. Was she flirting with you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I think she was genuinely unaware. I tried not to stare, and she picked up the papers and walked away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But it was too late for you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah. I had to sit there for a while. And even after I managed to stop thinking about her nipples, I started thinking about yours.” Unconsciously, his hand drifted to his lap, rubbing against his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And that’s when you texted me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. It seemed like we had fun yesterday, and I was hoping you’d, uh,” he hesitated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Say it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was hoping you’d help me out again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Try again,” she encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was hoping you’d show me your nipples and let me jerk off to you again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s more like it,” she purred. “See, all you had to do was ask. Now why don’t you show me how hard you are.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony undid his belt, opened his pants, and shifted them a bit lower. His cock jutted proudly upward, head swollen, eager to be touched. He wrapped his hand around the shaft and started slowly stroking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I see your tits?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smiling, she slowly pulled her top open. She felt pleased with herself that she’d thought to wear a wrap top and soft lace bralette that could be easily moved out of the way without having to take her whole top off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He exhaled happily as she massaged her breasts. When she teased her nipples, he quickened his stroke. She savored his attention and the effect she was having on him. The heat growing between her thighs seemed to match the intensity of his gaze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she spread her legs for him. She teased her skirt a bit higher, enough to let him see that her underwear matched her bra. He watched eagerly as she ran her hands up the inside of her thighs and back down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ash,” he suddenly said in a husky voice, “Will you let me suck on your nipples?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh!” She laughed. “Look who’s comfortable asking for things all of a sudden!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You said you wanted me to be more direct.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I did, didn’t I?” She stood up and bit her lip as she moved closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She couldn’t deny the excitement she felt as she knelt next to him on the couch. She reached out, sliding one hand behind his shoulder, along the back of the couch. He kept touching himself as she leaned in, putting her breasts right next to his face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go ahead,” she said and gasped as he wrapped his lips around her nipple. He moaned happily, pulling more of her into the heat of his mouth, tracing his tongue in circles. The sensation seemed to shiver through her body, dancing down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, that’s good,” she exhaled as he flicked his tongue. She squirmed, squeezing her thighs together, watching as he continued to masturbate. Clearly, he was enjoying this. She saw a drop of precum glisten for a moment before he rubbed it into his skin. She bit her lip as she imagined licking it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He released her nipple with a wet pop, and she shifted closer so he could suck on the other one. Now, more of her body was pressed against him, and she could feel his arm moving against her stomach. She wanted to feel more. Without quite realizing she was doing it, she swung her leg over his and straddled his thigh. With her body pressed against him like this, he couldn’t move his hand as much, but she didn’t mind slowing him down for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sensing what she needed, he shifted his leg, lifting it a bit to press more firmly against her while still licking and sucking. He squirmed, trying to adjust so he could move his hand more freely. She moaned and rolled her hips, rubbing against his thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You feel so good between my legs,” she murmured. “Keep going, keep going.” There seemed to be lightning arcing between her nipple in his mouth and the pressure against her clit. She buried her face in his hair and leaned harder against him, straddling his thigh, grinding, his arm straining between them, her tits out, nipples hard, pressure building…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” He grunted around her nipple. “Ash, please, I’m close, let me finish…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With some reluctance, she rolled off his thigh and lay back on the couch next to him. She held her breasts, firm pressure covering her sensitive nipples. His hand was flying frantically on his cock. She squeezed her thighs together, wanting more, but fighting the urge to climb back on top of him because she wanted to watch him finish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, fuck that was so hot, you’re so sexy when you ride me like that and let me suck on your tits while you grind on me…” He was babbling, and his head was swelling, large and purple, and smeared with precum. She bit her lip and stared, eager to see thick globs of hot, creamy cum coating his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly he was groping for the tissue box. “Ash! I’m gonna cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I want to see,” she protested, reaching for him. “Come here!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where?” He was already rolling toward her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cum on my tits!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clumsily, he got onto his knees, still stroking, and thrust his hips forward just in time for the first shot to arc up onto her neck and collarbone. She gasped at the sensation of hot cum on her skin. Then he groaned and pointed his cock towards her tits, each spurt falling across her chest, until he was rubbing the tip against her breast, milking the last drops directly onto her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, that was hot,” she purred as he collapsed onto his back next to her. He was still breathing too heavily to answer, but he nodded emphatically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Idly, she traced a fingertip through the sticky fluid already cooling on her chest. The heat in her core was beginning to fade, but she knew the embers of her arousal would continue smoldering. It would be a long afternoon of meetings until she could finally go home, get in bed, and replay the image of him about to cum all over her again and again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Ash,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmmm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can I see you again tomorrow?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You better,” she grinned.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Lunch Buddies 1: Monday</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/1-monday/"/>
		<published>2024-02-05T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2024-02-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/lunch-buddies/1-monday/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="office sex" />
    <category term="masturbation" />
    <category term="mutual masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="office" />
    <category term="work" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/lunch-buddies-edAtVNR7sP-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Knock-knock!” The man standing in her doorway had tousled hair, a crooked grin, and twinkling eyes that she knew well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tony!” Ash jumped up from her desk, pulled him into her office, and closed the door. “You’re here! It’s so good to see you!” She wrapped her arms around him for a hug, but he stiffened in surprise, and she felt something firm poking against her hip. “What’s…?” She looked down and grinned. “Oh! Well, &lt;em&gt;hello&lt;/em&gt;, sir.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, I’m so sorry, Ash!” Tony took a quick step backward, turning bright red and trying to cover his erection with his bag. “I didn’t mean to… You hugged me so quickly, I didn’t have a chance to…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, alright,” she laughed. “It’s not a big deal. Sit. breathe.” She gestured to the couch by the window behind her desk and turned her chair to face him. “I take it from your reaction that wasn’t the plan when you texted to say you were in town for the week and wanted to get lunch?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, of course not!” He collapsed onto the couch with his bag in his lap, looking mortified. “I’m so sorry, I swear I didn’t have any intentions like that, I really am in town for business…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Long flight for a booty call, all I’m saying,” she teased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, okay,” he smiled, trying to follow her lead and laugh it off. “Look, I’m on this new medication, and it, uh… well, a side effect is…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It may cause a monster throbbing erection when you meet a friend for lunch?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“First of all,” he objected, “it’s not ‘throbbing.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Could have fooled me,” she snorted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And second, yes! One of the side effects is an enhanced libido.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I have &lt;em&gt;so many&lt;/em&gt; questions about these pills, but go on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s gorgeous out, right, so I walked over here from my client’s office, and because it’s summer, women are walking around in short skirts and low-cut tops…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And then you got here and saw I was wearing a skirt too?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, I mean, no! I’m saying I had a, you know, an involuntary reaction before I got here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, a &lt;em&gt;reaction&lt;/em&gt;,” she laughed. “Is that what we’re calling it? Do these &lt;em&gt;reactions&lt;/em&gt; happen often?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um…” He laughed and shrugged. “A few times a day?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I see.” She raised an eyebrow at him. “And what do you do when you can’t grind your reaction against a girl you used to hook up with in college?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There was no grinding! And I said I was sorry, you surprised me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I know, I’m just poking fun at you.” She paused, then added, “I mean, you already poked something at me, so it’s only fair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But for real,” she said, leaning in conspiratorially. “What do you do when it happens?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, uh,” He looked deeply awkward. “If I’m at home, I can just, you know, take care of it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Right, right, right. What about at work?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I try not to draw any attention. I stay seated at my desk or hold my bag in front of me. I just think about something else and hope it goes away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How long does that take?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Depends. Sometimes an hour?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously? You don’t, like, go rub one out in a bathroom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have shared restrooms in the office. There’s not enough privacy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh.” She sat back and looked thoughtful. “That sounds really uncomfortable.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One day it got really bad…” He hesitated for a moment. “And I snuck into the director’s private office while she was at lunch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seriously. Felt like it took forever. I was terrified someone would come in before I finished.” He sighed. “Most days, it’s not too bad. After a couple weeks, I adapted. But then I had to travel here to work on-site with a client for a week. I don’t have a desk or anywhere I can hide out, so it’s super awkward. And it’s only Monday! I was barely able to keep myself distracted this morning, and then the walk over here… Again, I’m so sorry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s alright, this is easily the most interesting thing that’s happened in this office all month. But it does raise a question.” She leaned closer. “What are you going to do &lt;em&gt;now&lt;/em&gt;? We can’t go get lunch with you in this condition.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um. Do you have a bathroom I can visit?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, same problem as you. This floor shares the one bathroom. Lots of stalls, but not private enough for you to take care of business.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I could wait for it to calm down?” He looked flustered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t have &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; long a lunch break,” she smirked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I… uh… I guess I could go back to my hotel and…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You should do it here,” she blurted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You,” she gestured at him. “Should take care of that,” she gestured at his crotch. “Here in my office!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like… you’d leave?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, no,” she shook her head. “Sorry, I’m the head of HR, there’s too much protected information in this room. Legally, I can’t leave you alone in here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So, you want me to do it in front of you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wouldn’t be the first time,” she winked. “Or have you forgotten that we used to get off together between classes?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I haven’t forgotten,” he said, blushing and shifting awkwardly. “But what if someone comes in?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Again, I’m the head of HR. People know not to come in if my door is closed. Think of it like your boss’s office if that helps.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um…” He regarded her intently, trying to make sure she was serious. “I mean, it &lt;em&gt;would&lt;/em&gt; take the pressure off for when I go back to my client’s office after lunch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There you go! You can’t pop a stiffy in front of your client, that’d be a disaster!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re really okay with this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, little Tony already said hello. It’d be rude not to let him out to play.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please don’t call it that, and be serious for a second. I don’t want you to feel like I’m taking advantage of the situation or anything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I’m definitely okay with this.” She chuckled, handing him a box of tissues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um.” He put his bag on the floor, took the tissues, and sat back. “Okay, then.” Slowly, he unbuckled his belt, watching her as he opened his pants, still unsure if he could trust the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She grinned and made no effort to pretend not to watch as he pulled out his cock. “Ah, there he is.” It looked larger than she remembered. Do penises grow as guys get older? She made a mental note to look it up later. He was fully erect, even twitching a bit as he shifted his pants lower and wrapped his hand around the shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She made eye contact with him again, smiling encouragingly. He grinned sheepishly, looked away, and started stroking. Before long, he let out a stifled little grunt and tensed his legs. She’d forgotten all the ways he moved when he masturbated. The building tension, his whole body clenched as he worked toward a release. She crossed her legs, squeezing them together as she remembered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’d always go to her dorm room because they had an hour between classes and hers was closer. Sometimes they sat across from each other, just like this, eyes locked, hands down their pants. Sometimes they sat together on the couch, legs spread to let each other see. Sometimes they lay next to each other on her bed, shoulders touching, an electric thrill as they matched tempos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And sometimes he stood over her. Something about that always did it for her. She shivered as she remembered looking up at him. The hunger in his eyes. Her fingers rubbing tight circles around her clit as he stroked his cock just above her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes she let him cum on her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes they missed their next class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For several minutes he moved rhythmically, quickly looking away every time their eyes met. She felt her pulse quickening, remembering the old thrill, and eager to see him cum again. But abruptly, he let go and made a frustrated sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuuuck, I dunno about this, Ash.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh?” She frowned, disappointed. “What’s wrong? You’ve never had a problem jerking off in front of me before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was different. We were young and bored and &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; horny.” He hesitated. “And…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And, you, uh,” he met her eyes quickly. “You were into it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There was a… I dunno,” he said, looking away again, speaking quickly. “Like, an electricity. We’d get to your dorm, and you’d always start out pretending like you were doing me a favor, like you were just watching because you were bored. But then you’d start touching yourself, and fuck it always got me so hot seeing how turned on you were.” He gestured helplessly, struggling for words. “You were &lt;em&gt;into&lt;/em&gt; it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tony?” She waited until he met her eyes again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m still into it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You are?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I am.” She slowly traced a finger down her neckline, leaning forward and undoing two buttons to give him a peek at her bra. She bit her lip as she pushed her breasts together. “I really am.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without thinking about it, his hand gripped his cock again, slowly stroking as she teased him. She finished unbuttoning her shirt, letting it fall open so he could watch as she pinched her nipples through the soft fabric of her bra. He moved faster as she let her hands roam, caressing her sides and rubbing her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He watched excitedly as she pulled her arms from the sleeves and tossed her top on the arm of the couch. He gasped, his fingers circling his swollen head as she unhooked her bra and let it fall on top of her purse. She licked her lips and squeezed her breasts, savoring the sensation rolling through her body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His breath was coming quicker and she could tell he wasn’t going to last much longer. She leaned back in her chair and hiked her skirt up around her waist. He let out a small moan as she spread her thighs to slip a hand into her underwear. Excited by the intensity of his attention, she traced her lips, finding herself wet and eager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, Ash, please…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please what, Tony?” She purred, wanting him to say it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Please, let me see you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smiling, she pulled the fabric to one side and let him watch as she slipped a finger inside. His hand was a blur on his cock, his legs straining, his entire body tense. She lazily curled her finger, reaching deep, then sliding out. In, then out. In. Out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Aaaaaahhhhh fuck, Ash, that’s so hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you gonna cum for me, Tony?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yessss,” he groaned. He scrambled to grab a tissue and curled forward, wrapping it around the tip of his cock, eyes still locked on her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it. Cum. Cum for me. Cum hard. Do it now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His body rocked with an orgasm, gasping with the intensity, throbbing over and over. The heat in her core blossomed at the sight. Gradually his rocking slowed and he collapsed back on the couch, eyes closed and breathing hard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few moments, she stood up, languidly adjusting her underwear and letting her skirt fall into place as she sauntered toward him. He had a tissue full of cum in one hand, the other still holding his receding erection as she stood over him. Slowly, she traced a finger coated in her juices along his lower lip. His eyes opened in surprise, and he eagerly licked it clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” she grinned, turning away and picking up her bra. “That was an unexpected treat, but now I’m hungry. Get yourself together and we’ll go get some Pad Thai.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 4: Amy</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/4-amy/"/>
		<published>2023-04-10T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2023-04-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/4-amy/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="college sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="cumshot" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Head to the bathroom on your side. Take off your clothes, blindfold yourself, and wait for me in the shower. I’ll be there soon. Be ready for me! 💋”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy grinned as she texted Ian. He was cute enough, though a bit vanilla for her taste. She’d been teasing him all day and he was sure to jump at the chance to hook up with her. The coaches had said it was time for bed more than an hour ago, and old people went to sleep early, so it had to be safe to sneak across by now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She walked to the door and glanced at her roommate. She was on her phone too, probably texting her girlfriend in the room next door. The coaches had been quick to separate them when assigning rooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bonnie, I’m going to the bathroom.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh,” she responded, completely uninterested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy stepped out, closed the door, and paused. The building they were in had a communal kitchen in the middle, with hallways on either side leading to the bedrooms and bathrooms. Ian and Wally were in a room down the other hallway, and she just had to walk across to the bathroom on that side. But adjoining the kitchen was a common room, and she could hear the TV playing. Shit, were the coaches still awake? Well, whatever. She was just going to the bathroom, after all. They couldn’t possibly object to that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She confidently strolled down the hall and into the kitchen, intending to walk straight through to the other hallway without even looking towards the couches where the coaches were sitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up, Amy?” Coach Sam immediately turned to face her. Her arms were crossed, and the impatient expression on her face made Amy hesitate for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m, uh,” she cleared her throat and tried to sound nonchalant. “I’m just going to the bathroom.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh.” Coach Sam looked down the opposite hall like she somehow knew Ian was waiting there. “Any reason you can’t use the one by your room?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh…” Amy’s mind blanked as she tried to think of a reason. “I left my… hairbrush in the other bathroom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’m pretty sure someone’s in there right now. I think your hairbrush can wait for morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, uh… sure, that makes sense.” Amy stalled, trying to think of another reason, but came up with nothing. After a moment she turned around, inwardly seething, and walked back down her hall to the bathroom on her side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, if she couldn’t get to Ian, he’d just have to come to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stupid Coach Sam saw me and sent me to the other bathroom. Sneak over here and join me. 😛🍌”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There, now it was Ian’s problem. She was confident he was motivated enough to find a way past the coaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy turned her attention to the mirror. Her bleached blonde hair was pulled back into a ponytail. There were clear bikini tan lines on her shoulders. She was wearing a green cami over a leopard-print bra. She took a moment to adjust her breasts and nodded approvingly at her cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deciding that it would be sexier to already be partly undressed when Ian walked in, she removed her shorts and top. For a moment, she frowned at her reflection. The black panties with pink trim were cute, but it annoyed her that they didn’t match her bra. Whatever, it was fine. A guy like Ian didn’t need her A-game. He’d be grateful she tapped him at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of, where was he? It had been like ten minutes already.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on, I’m ready for you! 🍆🌮💦”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Confident in her appearance, she lounged against the wall and spent a while going through her Insta. Lots of likes on her photo from the beach. After liking all her friend’s posts, she blocked a couple of pests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leaving her phone on the counter with her clothes, Amy wandered into the shower. There was a bench that looked promising if they pulled it away from the wall. She could imagine pushing him back until he was laying full-length, and then straddling him…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If he ever got here. Scowling at the door, she picked up her phone again and texted him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s taking so long? 🤨”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tried to kill a few minutes playing a game on her phone, but her annoyance at Coach Sam made her mess up. Ugh, what was her problem? The coaches were treating them all like they were kids, sneaking around after curfew. Sure, she actually &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; sneaking around, but they didn’t &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; that, and it felt condescending to be treated this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where the fuck are you? 😖”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exhaling her frustration, Amy turned back to the mirror and tried on some seductive poses. She arched her back. She stuck her butt out. She squeezed her breasts together. But her irritation at being kept waiting was growing by the minute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“NOT a good idea to keep me waiting. 😤”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If he’d been caught by the coaches he could have at least texted her. It’d been like a half hour by now, that was plenty of time, even if he’d had to crawl through the kitchen on his hands and knees to stay out of sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, it dawned on her that she’d been stood up. What the actual fuck! This boy had no idea how lucky he was that she’d taken even a moment of interest in him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your loss! 🤬”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuming, Amy got dressed and left the bathroom. She was about to go back to her room when she realized that the TV was much quieter than before. Maybe the coaches were asleep now? She decided to try to sneak across again and go to Ian’s room to tell him off and remind him what he’d missed out on by not even trying to reach her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creeping slowly to the end of the hallway, she peeked into the common room. A late-night show was playing. Coach Jake was alone on the couch. It looked like he’d fallen asleep, head lolled back, and slouched low under a blanket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where was Coach Sam? Nervously, she looked around but didn’t see anything. Then she noticed the blanket move, and he quietly moaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holy shit! Jake wasn’t asleep, and that must be Sam under the blanket blowing him! Amy bit her knuckle to keep from squealing. Her shock quickly gave way to outrage. Of course, they were hypocrites. They were only stopping &lt;em&gt;her&lt;/em&gt; from hooking up because it got in the way of &lt;em&gt;their&lt;/em&gt; action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As quickly as she dared, she crept through the dark kitchen, keeping an eye on the couch and prepared to drop to the floor if they moved. Thankfully, they were completely distracted and she made it across without being noticed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Filled with equal parts triumph and annoyance, she opened Ian’s door without knocking and slipped inside, shutting it quietly behind her. The room was only dimly lit by moonlight and it took her eyes a moment to adjust. When they did, she realized with confusion that only one bed was occupied. Ian’s best friend Wally was asleep on his back and snoring softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where the fuck was Ian? Was he still in the bathroom? No, he would have seen all her texts. There was only one possible explanation. Not only had he blown her off, but he’d done it to fuck some other girl! She practically saw red at the idea. Not that she cared if he slept with anyone else, of course. This was always going to be a one-time thing. But the idea that he’d choose someone else over a chance with her? Outrageous. Well, she’d show him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitation, she walked over to Wally’s bed, lifted the covers, and climbed on top of him. He was sleeping in only boxers, and his skin was hot to the touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, whassat?” Wally murmured. He blinked at her in confusion, trying to focus on her face. “Amy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shhh, yeah it’s me.” She ran her hands over his shoulders and down his chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s going on? I thought you and Ian were hooking up?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, well, I’m hooking up with you instead.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh?” He shook his head and adjusted his position under her. “No, no, I can’t do that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why not?” As she asked, she reached down and felt the shape of his cock through his boxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ian’s my bro!” He tried to pull her hand away. “You don’t hook up with a chick your bro likes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you being serious right now?” She pushed her hand back down and started rubbing him, noting that despite his protests, he was starting to get hard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, no, stop that!” He got up on one elbow and tried to push her away. “Why are you here? Where’s Ian?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, fine!” She sat up, still straddling him, but no longer trying to grope him. “Your &lt;em&gt;bro&lt;/em&gt; stood me up, alright?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He did?” Wally looked confused. “So you’re here to, what, fuck me to get back at him?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” Amy responded defiantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, cool,” a slow grin replaced the confusion on his face. “Why didn’t you say so?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What? Seriously?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah! If he blew you off, then I’m in the clear!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re saying he’d be fine with me fucking you instead of him?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, no way, it’ll piss him off. But it’s not a violation of the bro code, you know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s idiotic. You’re both idiots.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wally just shrugged, and she felt his cock twitch under her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine. Whatever.” She peeled off her top and unhooked her bra, to his obvious delight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Excellent!” Wally grinned and sat up to bury his face in her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite her annoyance with the situation, she soon found herself squirming in his lap as his tongue circled her nipples and his cock grew until it was pressing against her. Slowly, her irritation melted away, replaced by a growing heat wherever his body touched hers. She gasped, rolling her hips to grind more firmly against him as he squeezed her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get undressed,” she breathed in his ear. She climbed off and slid her shorts down her hips with exaggerated slowness. She could feel his eyes on her ass as she bent over in front of him, stepping out of her panties with unnecessarily exaggerated movements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she turned around, he had kicked the blanket and his boxers away. He was sitting expectantly on the edge of the bed, his cock pointing proudly toward the ceiling. He had a big cheesy grin on his face. It was dumb, but his obvious gratitude made her feel better. &lt;em&gt;This&lt;/em&gt; was how guys were supposed to react to her attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She lowered herself to her knees and wrapped her lips around his cock. He groaned and immediately grabbed her ponytail, using it like a handle to push her deeper. Offended, she swatted his hand away. She didn’t need any “help.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although giving a blowjob didn’t do much for her, she took a certain amount of pride in knowing how to give a good one. Her tongue flicked against the tip, and her lips slipped wetly over the rim of his head. One hand moved along his shaft with growing intensity, while the other teased the sensitive skin behind his scrotum. Before long he was gasping and moaning, his legs tense on either side of her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, she let him go with a wet smack. He collapsed back on the bed, one arm over his eyes, trying to catch his breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Damn, Amy, you’re a good cocksucker.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you,” she replied, wiping her mouth and sitting on the edge of the bed next to him. “Now it’s your turn.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, nah, I don’t like doing that,” he responded without even looking at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Annoyed, she flicked his cock. He jumped up, looking shocked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, like I love the taste of dick?” She glared at him as he shrugged. “Ugh, fine, whatever, you’re probably terrible at it anyway. Give me a second to get ready.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy laid down on his bed, adjusting his pillow and getting comfortable. She took a few deep breaths, trying to let the annoyance fade away, and focused on the gently glowing ember of arousal in her core. Licking her lips, she cupped her breasts. Her nipples were still sensitive from Wally’s tongue. Slowly, she let one hand slide down her stomach and over her hip, spreading her legs. Her finger eased between her lips, finding the wetness hidden inside. Sighing, she dipped in and spread her lubrication over her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wally made an approving sound and she glanced over to see him standing by the bed, eagerly stroking his cock at her. Biting her lip, she gestured for him to join her. He climbed onto the bed, kneeling between her legs, still masturbating, as he watched her tease her clit. He inched forward until his thighs pressed against hers. She felt the heat of his body, his hand brushing against hers as they both touched themselves with increasing urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, that’s hot,” he groaned. “I’ve never watched a girl get off before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want you in me, now,” she gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy grabbed his cock and positioned him against her opening. He dropped onto his elbows and settled his weight between her thighs. They both moaned as he slipped inside. Slowly, he started moving his hips, gently and lazily fucking her. She closed her eyes to focus on the sensation, then sputtered as he tried to stick his tongue in her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry,” he said sheepishly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, I just wasn’t expecting that,” she tried to explain. “Sorry, but I’m not here for kissing. That’s not what I’m looking for.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah, yeah, okay.” He looked confused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want sweet and slow and rainbows and unicorns right now, okay? I want you to &lt;em&gt;fuck&lt;/em&gt; me. Yeah? Can you do that, Wally?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she said his name, she felt his cock throb inside her, and then he started moving against her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes! That’s it, I want—Uh!—I want to feel your—Ah!—cock…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He buried his face against her neck, pulled almost all the way out, and slammed his weight back onto her in a way that caused sparks at the edge of her vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh yeah, like that, fuck me like that—Ah!—fuck me hard—Ah! Ah!—harder!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every time she spoke, he thrust harder into her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Yeah, Wally, fuck—Oh! God!—Your dick is so hard in my pussy — Ah Ah AH!—fuck me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wally began thrusting away with abandon. He was grunting in her ear. She wrapped her legs around him and clawed at his back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god! Oh god! Oh god! Keep fucking me like that!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A stream of filthy porn nonsense spilled from her lips. Each statement made him grunt and thrust, rutting away like an animal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jesus, yes, fuck, that’s it, fuck, fuck, fuck, Wally, god your cock is going so deep, you’re filling me up, my cunt is so wet!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was everything she wanted. She felt the pressure building in her core. She heard the ocean roaring in her ears and her vision began to blur, replaced by auras of color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, abruptly, he rolled off her. She groaned at the sudden loss of his cock and the weight of his body. He was panting hard, and she was vaguely aware that he was apologizing, saying he was close but needed a minute to rest his arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shut up, just lie there,” she murmured as she climbed on top of him, determined to reclaim her orgasm. “Don’t do anything, just let me ride you until I cum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock slid back in like it belonged to her. This angle was different, but maybe better. She rolled her hips, feeling where the pressure hit. Quickly, she found a groove, rocking back and forth on top of him. Her hands were on his chest, fingernails digging into his skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened her eyes and saw him looking up at her with awe and lust. He watched her tits bounce in time with her movements and she felt him swelling. Fuck! He was going to cum before she could finish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, stop it,” she groaned, shoving her hand over his face to cover his eyes. “Let me cum first, I’m so close.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He moaned, and she pushed her fingers into his mouth. He sucked, hard, and she felt her pussy starting to clench. She leaned forward to put a bit more pressure on her clit and suddenly cried out as the pressure released.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wave after wave of sensation radiated out from her pussy and all she could see were fireworks. She rocked back and forth, letting it roll through her until she felt his cock swelling again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Amy!” He choked around her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She jumped off him and quickly wrapped her hands around his cock, covered in her creamy juices. His entire body went rigid as she urgently stroked his shaft. Hot sticky cum spilled over her fingers, spurting onto his stomach. He grunted with each throb of his cock, thrusting into her hands over and over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, it passed and she collapsed down on his side, both of them breathing heavily. Her arm was draped over his body, still idly playing with his cum as his cock softened. Her other hand moved between her thighs, palm pressed against her clit, which felt too sensitive to leave uncovered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A long time passed as their heartbeats slowed and their breathing regulated. Finally, he took a deep breath and wrapped his arm around her, pulling her in close with her head on his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, that was hot. Let me know if there’s anyone else you want to get back at.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy laughed and half-heartedly swatted him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I still think this bro code of yours is idiotic.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re probably right,” he agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I should go back to my room.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, you should stay,” he said, sleepily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why,” she teased, “are you falling in love with me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, it’s just, Ian’ll probably come back soon. If you really wanna make him jealous, won’t it be better for him to &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt; us together instead of just hearing about it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s a good point.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She relaxed against him, savoring the heat of his body. She didn’t want to admit it, but at the moment she didn’t particularly care about Ian.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 3: Kara</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/3-kara/"/>
		<published>2023-01-13T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2023-01-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/3-kara/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="college sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="cum on tits" />
    <category term="male masturbation" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Kara stepped into the hall and shut the bedroom door behind her. For a moment, she paused, feeling giddy. Then she realized she was holding her shorts, not wearing them. She hustled to the bathroom before anyone came along and she had to answer awkward questions like, “Why are your underwear soaking wet,” or, “Is that cum on your face?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the door swung shut behind her, she walked to the counter and tried to catch her breath. Wow! She’d never done &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; like that before. One minute she was secretly touching herself as Lucia and Carlos fucked, and then…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip as a blur of sexually-charge memories played in her mind’s eye. Lucia calling her out, and eagerly offering to show her how wet she was. The sight of her teammate’s pussy as she straddled her face. Lucia asking her to lick her clit. Carlos’ cock in her throat. Lucia’s fingers in her pussy. Cumming so hard she thought she would pass out. Carlos’ hot cum falling on her face. Kissing Lucia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studying her reflection in the mirror, the girl who looked back was flushed and grinning. Kara thought she looked hot. Her hair was disheveled. Her eyes had been watering from gagging on cock. There was cum splashed across her cheek. She looked like someone who knew what she wanted. Someone who wasn’t afraid to say “yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…Also like someone whose underwear was increasingly uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, she rinsed her face off and walked into one of the toilet stalls. She slipped off her sopping panties and cleaned herself up a bit. Her lips were puffy and slick, and her clit was very sensitive. She was about to step into her sleep shorts when she noticed a quiet, repetitive, oddly familiar sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was coming from the direction of the shower stall. This was a multiple-person bathroom, with two stalls, a broad counter with two sinks, and a curtained area with a shower and a bench. She had assumed she was alone in here since it was so late, but clearly, there was someone in the shower. And the shower wasn’t running. What were they doing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abruptly, she recognized the sound. It was someone stroking their cock! She’d just heard it up close just a few minutes ago as Carlos stood over her face, rubbing himself. Oh my god, she realized with a sudden thrill, I caught one of the guys having a midnight wank! He must have heard me come in, right? But he’s still going, even though he knows he’s not alone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She considered the possibilities. It could be Coach Jake… but ew, she hoped not. He was scruffy and old and she didn’t want to think about him naked. Plus, she figured he’d have more self-control. No, it had to be one of the two younger guys on the trip, her teammates Wally and Ian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Could it be Wally? He was cocky and self-assured, with a bit of scruffy facial hair he was overly proud of. He did seem like the type to jerk off in a shared bathroom, but not really the type to be quiet about it. She’d once overheard him loudly bragging about getting head under the bleachers. He was so unashamed about everything, she couldn’t imagine him slowing down just because someone came in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which meant it was probably Ian! Hmm, that was interesting. She’d had a bit of a crush on him lately. She’d fantasized about making out, running her fingers through his curly hair… imagining him pressing her against the wall, his thigh between hers. He ran cross-country and had &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; nice legs. Without thinking about it, her hand drifted down to lightly caress her lips as she imagined Ian rubbing his cock. She wondered what it looked like. She wondered what it would feel like in her hand. Or her mouth. Or her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was surprised to realize that she badly wanted to peek. She would never have dreamed of doing something like that before tonight. But the Kara she’d just looked at in the mirror? The Kara with the taste of cum in her mouth and a newfound sense of confidence? &lt;em&gt;She&lt;/em&gt; would take a look for sure. And maybe more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before she could think better of it, she pulled up her shorts and left the stall, leaving her panties behind. She crept to the shower curtain and teased it open enough to see inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ian was leaning against the wall by the bench. She bit her lip. He was completely naked except for an improvised blindfold made from a bandana. His cock was smaller than Carlos’, and it matched the color of his pale skin except for the tip, which was darker, almost purple. His hand was moving rapidly along the length of his shaft, which was pointing toward her. His legs were tense, making the muscles stand out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holy shit, this is hot, she thought. Slowly, she opened the curtain and slipped inside, standing in front of him. He didn’t stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is that you?” He gasped, turning his head when he heard the curtain move. “Where have you been? I was worried you wouldn’t come. I’ve been waiting, ready for you. I’ve… ah… I’ve been thinking about you all day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara bit her finger and squeezed her thighs together. He was waiting for someone. Probably Amy. They’d been obnoxiously flirting all day. She watched his hand move, his thumb rubbing over the glans, a glistening drop of precum dripping from the tip. She very badly wanted to taste it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just for a moment, she considered dropping to her knees and taking him in her mouth. Let him keep the blindfold on, and assume she was who he was waiting for. Make him cum, and leave without saying a word. It was tempting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…But it wouldn’t be right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorry,” she cleared her throat, “but I don’t think I’m the one you’re waiting for.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Huh?” He quickly tore the blindfold off, eyes wide with embarrassment. “Kara?! Oh fuck, I’m so sorry, I thought you were Amy! She, uh, told me to meet her here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I can see that,” Kara grinned, trying not to laugh as he struggled to find a way to conceal his twitching erection. “Do you two do this often?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no,” he stammered. “This is the first time I’ve ever… uh, I mean, the first time with Amy, you know?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But you have done this with other women?” Kara raised her eyebrow. “The blindfold and all that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No! I mean… Fuck.” He looked painfully awkward. “I mean, um, I’ve never done anything like this before.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I’m sorry,” Kara smiled. “I don’t mean to tease you. I’ve never rubbed one out in public either.” (That’s not strictly true anymore, she thought to herself.) “Anyway, uh, where is she? You said you were worried she wasn’t coming?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, she texted me to meet her here like a half hour ago.” His cheeks flushed. “She said to put on a blindfold and make sure I was ready for her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Kara made a show of looking around. “I think she might’ve blown you off, dude.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck.” Ian looked crushed. “You think so?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, I don’t know for sure,” Kara admitted. “But I once heard her bragging about setting up three hookups in one night in case the first two were duds.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, I should have known better. She’s too hot. She’s out of my league.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Kara said, taking a step towards him. “I don’t know about that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, what do you mean?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean,” Kara said, getting very close, “that I was just watching you and thinking that you have really nice legs.” Slowly, she pulled his hand away from his erection. “And &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; isn’t bad either.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh… yeah?” Ian’s nervousness and embarrassment receded, as he finally registered the desire in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” Kara wrapped her fingers around his cock and gently squeezed. “And I was thinking…” She leaned forward, pressing her chest against him. “It seems like you were hoping to have a hookup with a hot girl on this trip?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” Ian breathed, his cock throbbing in her palm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, really, it’s very rude of Amy to leave you all hot and bothered like this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Y-yeah…” he stammered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And since I’m feeling a bit hot and bothered myself…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah!” His cock twitched in her hand, and she felt a squirt of precum on her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How about you let me be your hot girl tonight?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god, yes,” he blurted, eyes full of lust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Excellent,” Kara purred as she released his cock and stepped back. He looked confused as she licked his precum from her fingers. “But if I start by going down on you, you’ll cum too fast, and I want to enjoy this, too. So…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, teasingly, she removed her shorts and shirt, dropping them on the bench near his discarded clothes. She let him stare at her for a moment, biting her lip as his hungry gaze roamed her body. Then she moved in close and helped him turn around until she’d taken his spot against the wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, come closer. I want you to push me against the wall.” He eagerly obeyed. “Good. Now, put your leg like this…” She positioned his thigh between hers. “And kiss my neck.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tile was cool against her back, but his skin was hot. She gasped as he sucked on her neck. His erection prodded her hip, and he started to grind against her, sending waves of sensation radiating from where his thigh pressed on her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She ran her fingers up and down his back, tangled in his hair, and grabbed his ass, pulling him tighter against her. The pressure of his body on hers quickly reignited the smoldering coals of her desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached for his hand and pulled it to her chest, encouraging him to squeeze her breasts. She was still so sensitive from her encounter with Lucia and Carlos. Everything felt delicious. She could feel her wetness coating his leg where he continued to push it between hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My nipples,” she gasped. “Suck on my nipples.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without a word, he dropped to his knees. He wrapped his lips around her breast and sucked hard, pulling more than just her nipple into the heat of his mouth. She gasped, still squeezing his hand on her other breast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, that feels good,” she murmured, pulling his head to the other side. She reached down and started to rub near her clit. It was still too much to touch directly, but caressing the area around it sent little bolts of lightning crackling along her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ian,” she gasped, pushing him away suddenly. “I want to go down on you.” He nodded enthusiastically, one hand wrapped around his cock. “But you have to promise not to cum yet!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” he agreed eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She got down on her knees as he stood back up, stroking his cock in front of her face. She moved her head to the side, nestling her face against his curly mass of hair and licking slowly along the length of the shaft, pushing his hand away. She flicked her tongue against the tip, then licked around the rim of his head. When she finally took him into her mouth, he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She let him slide down the length of her tongue. She felt his hand lightly touch her hair, encouraging her to bob her head. She challenged herself to take him a bit deeper each time, relaxing her throat until she was on the edge of gagging. She noted with interest that it was easier to swallow him than Carlos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara! Kara, stop,” he gasped, stepping back and pulling his cock abruptly away from her. “Holy shit, you were about to make me cum.” He looked at her, breathing heavily, trying to regain control. Clearly, he was waiting for her to tell him what was next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come over to the bench, I want to sit on you.” She grinned. It was kind of fun to take control of a sexual encounter. He dropped onto the bench, his cock glistening wet and inviting. She bit her lip and moved forward to straddle him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The moment when he entered her was almost too much. She was so wet that he slipped in effortlessly, and so swollen that she felt every inch of him. She rocked her hips, experimenting to see which angle put pressure in the best spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the bench was awkward. It was mounted to the wall, so there wasn’t really room for her knees unless he slouched down in a way that seemed painfully awkward. And her being so wet was a double-edged sword, since he popped out of her as easily as he slipped in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tried turning around, sitting on him like a chair. She’d seen that in porn, but it was even harder to make that angle work. He tended to slip &lt;em&gt;past&lt;/em&gt; her opening and end up nestled against her ass, which she wasn’t quite ready for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few frustrating moments, she grabbed him by the hand and dragged him out of the shower to the counter. It was just the right height for her to lean forward and rest her elbows on it. She caught his eye in the mirror and grinned as he stepped up, and gasped as he entered her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This angle was delicious. His cock was rubbing every sensitive spot inside her, and he could reach deep. He grabbed her hips and started fucking her with urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara found herself gasping with each thrust, trying not to start moaning or crying out, for fear of someone hearing. She watched him in the mirror, loving the effect she was having on him. His eyes were wide with desire, staring at her tits, swaying in time with their motions. She stifled a laugh of recognition, realizing he was staring at her chest the same way she’d stared at Lucia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Pull my hair!” She growled, surprising herself. It had looked so hot when Carlos did it to Lucia, she wanted to feel what it was like. Tentatively, Ian grabbed a handful of her hair and tugged gently. “Harder! Pull my head back! It’s okay!” Clearly a bit unsure, Ian did as she asked and pulled back until she was forced up off her elbows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh! Fuck! Yes!” Kara felt a climax approaching, the pressure growing around his cock. With one white-knuckled hand, she gripped the counter. The other was flying in tight circles around her clit. She and Ian both stared at her tits, bouncing as his hips slapped against her ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The orgasm seemed to crash over her body, rolling from the pain in her scalp as he yanked on her hair down to the tight erect buds of her nipples, through her core, clenching around his cock, and crackling as she jammed her palm tightly against her clit. Her vision seemed to blur, replaced by radiating sparks of colors. She rocked back and forth, gasping for breath as he relentlessly continued fucking her through wave after wave of pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara!” He gasped, “Kara, fuck… Gonna cum.” He met her eyes. “Where…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” Quickly, she spun around, dropping to her knees and squealing when he popped out of her. “Do it, do it, cum on my tits,” she panted, leaning back and squeezing them while looking up at him eagerly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a long groan, he closed his eyes and stepped closer. Thick ropes of hot cum erupted as he stroked his cock, splashing across her breasts and hands. Laughing, she licked some of his cum from her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aftershocks of her orgasm were still rolling through her body. She was giddy with excitement, her newfound confidence leaving her reeling. Fucking hell, was it really this easy to get what she wanted? What a revelation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ian turned around to lean against the counter. He grinned down and her and then closed his eyes, trying to catch his breath. He looked thoroughly satiated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She ducked into a stall and grabbed some toilet paper to wipe up. Ian watched as if trying to memorize the curves of her body. She recovered her wet underwear from the floor and practically skipped into the shower to pull her shorts and shirt back on. God, she felt incredible!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She sauntered out, deliberately rolling her hips as she walked, savoring his eyes on her as she approached and gave him a kiss on the cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, Ian, how was that for a hookup on our big trip?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” he beamed. “You were… you are…” He seemed at a loss for words. “Thank you. That was so fucking hot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heh. Yeah, it was. Remind me to thank Amy when I see her.” She laughed at the panicked expression on his face. “Don’t worry, I’m joking. It’ll be our little secret.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picking up her phone, she saw a text from Lucia letting her know she could come back. She gave Ian a quick kiss on the cheek. “Sleep well.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He nodded, still a bit dazed, as she winked at her reflection in the mirror and walked out the door.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 2: Lucia</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/2-lucia/"/>
		<published>2023-01-02T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/2-lucia/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="college sex" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="threesome" />
    <category term="exhibitionism" />
    <category term="voyeur" />
    <category term="ffm" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="creampie" />
    <category term="roommate" />
    <category term="student" />
    <category term="exhibitionist" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Roommate finally asleep. Come to the window and I’ll let you in.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia bit her lip as she sent the text to Carlos. The rest of the robotics team would flip if they knew she was fooling around with the captain of a rival team. She’d be lying if she said that didn’t make it more fun. Sure, Carlos was an absolute snack, and she’d have been into him regardless… But only seeing each other at meets? Finding excuses to sneak away from their teams? Looking for isolated stairwells where they could have a quickie? That was hot, no doubt about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, her entire team was staying in a quad dorm on the MIT campus for a competition. Coach Sam had immediately paired them off into rooms, and she’d ended up with Kara. As a teammate, Kara was great. Smart, passionate, always finding clever solutions and pushing the team to do more. As a roommate? Well, Lucia might have been able to convince Amy or one of the other girls to let her sneak a guy in. But she had a feeling Kara wouldn’t be so understanding, especially if the guy was an opponent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So when Kara said they should get a good night’s sleep, Lucia agreed. They’d put on their pajamas, turned off the light, and climbed into their beds. Then Lucia pretended to go to sleep while watching Kara like a hawk. Only after what felt like hours did her breathing slow enough that Lucia could text Carlos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she slipped out of her bed and tiptoed to the window, thanking the universe that their room was on the ground floor and had a window that opened fully. Looking across the parking lot, she could see Carlos standing under a light, looking at his phone. He must have already been waiting a while. She grinned. The anticipation was good for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quietly, she slid the window open and waved him over. He was wearing joggers and a tight t-shirt that showed off his broad shoulders. Climbing in was complicated by a large prickly bush under the window, but he managed it without making too much noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then, finally, he was there. He pulled her against him and opened his mouth to say something, but she pressed a finger to his lips and pointed at Kara, mercifully still asleep. He nodded, and she led him to the bed, pulling him down on top of her. No need to talk anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their hands explored each other’s bodies with increasing urgency. He squeezed her breasts through her tank top and settled his weight between her thighs. She grabbed his ass and pulled him tighter against her. She kissed him aggressively, biting his lower lip and pushing her tongue into his mouth. He responded in kind, and she felt a heat kindle in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He started pulling the hem of her shirt up. She shifted her weight to let him lift it high enough to expose her breasts and tried not to gasp as the heat of his mouth closed around her nipple. She felt it stiffen against his tongue, and he rolled her other nipple between his thumb and forefinger. A lazy wave of heat rolled down her spine to where his weight still rested between her legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She thought she saw a movement across the room but was distracted immediately by Carlos getting up on his knees to pull down her shorts. She raised her hips to help and grinned as he discovered she wasn’t wearing any underwear. He parted her legs slowly, reverently. She’d shaved everything this morning, knowing how the sight excited him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He leaned down to keep sucking on her nipple as his hand slid up her thigh. She bit her lip as his warm fingers teased her folds, gently at first, but with increasing enthusiasm. She let him tease a fingertip between her lips but gently pushed his hand away as he moved toward her clit. He meant well, but he had a tendency to be too aggressive, treating her most sensitive spot like it was a miniature cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She appreciated the effort, but what really got her wet was sucking his cock. Carlos was blessed. His shaft was a lovely shade of brown, and just on the edge of too large for her. He kept clean and trimmed, and she loved seeing how deep she could swallow him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She got up onto her hands and knees, and he was already tugging down his pants. He also wasn’t wearing underwear, and she eagerly took his cock into her mouth, where it stiffened quickly. He bit his knuckle and tried not to make any noise as she let her tongue dance against his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She grinned when she felt him gently push his hips forward, and let him go deeper. When he bumped against the back of her mouth, she tried to relax her throat. She loved swallowing him this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a moment, she felt his hand cradling the back of her head and he started to move his hips more insistently. Trying not to gag, she followed his lead, allowing him to start slowly fucking her mouth as a surge of desire washed over her. Gradually, his pace quickened as he got more excited, thrusting deeper each time until her forehead was resting against his taut stomach. Her eyes watered, and she felt her throat tighten, which made his breath catch as he tried not to cry out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, sputtering and nearly choking, she had to pull away. Carlos shuddered, trying to quietly catch his breath. Still kneeling, his cock jutted towards her, glistening wet and twitching. Wiping her mouth and grinning, she turned around and dropped onto her elbows, shaking her upturned ass at him. She’d had plans for a long, slow, quiet night of lovemaking, but right now all she wanted was him behind her, burying his cock in her now-dripping pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She buried her face in the pillow to avoid making a sound as he rubbed his head between her lips and pushed just a little way inward. She felt him grip her hips and shivered, knowing he was about to start fucking her. They both paused, savoring the anticipation. She had no idea how they would keep from making any noise that would wake Kara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glancing in her roommate’s direction, Lucia was shocked to make eye contact. Just for a fraction of a second, until Kara quickly shut her eyes. It was over so quickly, she wondered if she’d imagined it. Even so, it caused a complicated mix of emotions to wash over her. Surprise. Embarrassment. Confusion. Worry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But mostly? Lust. Because she could have sworn that Kara’s eyes were filled with arousal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, Carlos thrust forward, burying himself deep inside her. She gasped, and for a moment, all thoughts were driven from her mind. She had to bite the pillow to keep from crying out. God, she loved this. Knowing she’d turned him on this much, gotten him this hard, and now he was &lt;em&gt;fucking&lt;/em&gt; her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was Kara really watching? How long had she been watching? Had she been awake the whole time? Or had she woken up to the wet sounds of her sucking Carlos’ cock? Why hadn’t she said anything? Was she getting off right now? Lucia gasped at the idea of Kara with her hand in her underwear, trying just as hard as they were to be quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos reached down between her thighs to rub her clit. Normally she would have stopped him, but now she wondered if it would turn Kara on to see it. She risked another quick peek and once again made eye contact for a heartbeat before Kara shut her eyes, still pretending to sleep. There was no longer any doubt. Kara was awake, watching, and into it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Involuntarily (mostly), Lucia moaned as Carlos removed his hand from between her thighs and grabbed a handful of her hair instead. He pulled firmly backward, forcing her up off her elbows, arching her back until she had to put her hands on the headboard. He was fucking her hard now, slamming against her enough to make her tits bounce. Tension was building deep in her core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another glance, another brief moment of eye contact. Lucia was almost certain she could see movement below the covers. Kara &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; be masturbating as she watched them fuck. Carlos pulled her hair tighter and she whimpered, gripping the headboard tightly. Did Kara like girls? Was she staring at her tits or his cock? Maybe both? Was she thrusting fingers into her pussy, matching their pace, imagining how it would feel if Carlos was fucking her?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia was gasping from the excitement of the situation. Finally, she looked directly at Kara. Not a glance, but prolonged contact. She wanted to see Kara watching. No more pretending to be asleep. Kara’s eyes showed a moment of shock, but this time she didn’t close them or look away. The movement under the covers seemed to quicken. Her pussy clenched with excitement. Carlos was fucking her while Kara watched. She was right on the edge, and Kara was getting off watching her!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara mouthed the word “cum,” and Lucia didn’t know if that meant Kara was cumming, or she knew Lucia was about to, or if she was giving an order. Regardless, all her muscles contracted and she cried out as a gush of warm fluid ran down her thighs. Carlos released his grip on her hair, allowing her to collapse onto the pillow as he held her hips, keeping his cock deep inside through her orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When her vision cleared, Kara was still staring right at her. She looked impressed, embarrassed, and jealous all at the same time. A sense of relaxed bliss came over Lucia as she kept looking at Kara. She knew the two of them would never understand each other more clearly than they did at this moment. They both knew, without any need to speak, that Kara would close her eyes and continue pretending to sleep while Lucia finished Carlos off and sent him back the way he came. They would never speak about this, but it would be a secret they shared, communicated only by a sly smile now and then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And so Lucia wasn’t sure who was more surprised when, instead of all that, she found herself saying aloud, “Do you like watching Carlos fuck me, Kara?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, uh, what?” Carlos stammered, completely oblivious to all that had happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck!” Kara squeaked and tried to hide her face under the covers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia climbed off the bed, leaving Carlos behind as she crossed the room. Gently, she pulled the covers from Kara’s face. Her eyes were wide with shock and alarm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, hey, don’t worry,” Lucia reassured, sitting on the edge of the bed and touching Kara’s cheek. “It’s okay, You like to watch, I get it. Did you like seeing me go down on him?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara seemed hesitant to answer, but her eyes said yes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that was sexy, huh?” Lucia bit her lip and let her fingertips slowly wander down Kara’s neckline. “What about when he got behind me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still unsure how to react, Kara gave a tiny nod.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmm… Yeah, I bet that looked hot. Did you see the way he pulled my hair? How he made my tits bounce ‘cause he was fucking me so hard?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara nodded and shivered as Lucia leaned in close to whisper in her ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m glad you were watching, it got me off. Do you want to see how wet it made me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah…” Kara responded quietly. Then, with more determination: “I do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia smiled encouragingly as she stood up. Kara watched with aroused curiosity as Lucia slipped a finger between her lips, then showed her the lubrication coating it. Unconsciously, Kara licked her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to see closer?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eyes wide, Kara nodded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Here, come this way.” Lucia gently touched Kara’s shoulder, encouraging her to turn so she was laying sideways with her head over the edge of the mattress. As she did, the covers pulled away, revealing a deep v-neck and pink bikini briefs. She seemed unsure of what to do with her hands, timidly adjusting the hem of her shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia moved to straddle Kara’s head. “Look at me, Kara,” she purred. She could feel Kara’s hot breath on her thighs. “Does it turn you on to see my pussy like this?” Kara nodded and squirmed, squeezing her thighs together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You told me to cum, right? Well, I did,” Lucia reached down and spread her lips, letting Kara see how creamy she was. “Do you want to taste it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes,” Kara gasped. Lucia lowered herself to slide her wet lips over Kara’s. She purred as her roommate’s tongue moved against her, tracing her folds and dipping inside. She rocked against her mouth and chin. Kara’s hands moved from fidgeting with her shirt to grabbing Lucia’s ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It got me so hot to see you watching me… Were you touching yourself?” In answer, Kara spread her legs, letting Lucia see the wet spot on the gusset of her panties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck, that’s hot… Can I touch you, Kara?” She felt a nod between her thighs and leaned forward, planting her hands on either side of the brunette’s hips. Shifting her weight to one arm, she slipped her free hand into Kara’s underwear. Her fingers brushed past a neatly trimmed patch of hair to feel wet lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ooh, &lt;em&gt;chica&lt;/em&gt;, you’re dripping!” Kara nodded enthusiastically as Lucia easily slipped a finger in. As she hooked upward, the brunette let out a moan of pleasure. That sent surprising vibrations through Lucia’s pussy, and she gasped and pushed deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, Kara, lick my clit, please,” Lucia begged, as she felt her tongue push deeper between her lips. “How… ah! How many fingers did you have inside? One?” The head between her thighs shook and then moaned as Lucia added a second finger. “Two?” Urgent nodding. Lucia started fucking her with two fingers, her palm pressing against Kara’s clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When did you start touching yourself? Did you wait until he got behind me?” Kara shook her head again and traced tight little circles around her clit. “Ooooh, that feels good. Was it when I was sucking his cock?” Nodding. “Yeah, he’s got a really nice &lt;em&gt;cock&lt;/em&gt;.” Every time she said it, Kara’s pussy clenched. “Sucking his &lt;em&gt;cock&lt;/em&gt; always gets me wet.” She hooked her fingers, feeling for Kara’s g-spot, and savored the way the brunette spread her thighs, begging for more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to see it?” Lucia felt Kara’s cunt clench around her fingers. “Heh, I’ll take that as a yes.” She looked behind her and saw Carlos sitting on the edge of her bed, lazily stroking himself as he watched the two of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come over here, babe, she wants to see you up close.” Dutifully, Carlos walked closer, standing directly behind her. She couldn’t see, but she knew Kara must be distracted by the sight. Her tongue slowed, and her pussy began squeezing excitedly around Lucia’s fingers. Fuck, she must be right on the edge, Lucia realized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somewhat reluctantly, Lucia raised herself away from Kara’s mouth. She looked down between her thighs and saw her roommate gasping with pleasure. Her chin was covered in Lucia’s wetness. Her eyes were locked on Carlos’ long brown shaft. Her body was tense, ready to cum any second.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to suck his &lt;em&gt;cock&lt;/em&gt;?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, yes,” Kara groaned, panting as Lucia kept her palm pressed against her clit and Carlos rubbed his cock right next to her face. Her pussy was clenching rapidly. There was no denying her imminent orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do it, babe,” Lucia blurted, as Kara parted her lips. “She’s about to cum!” Carlos wrapped his hands around the back of her head, supporting her neck as she eagerly sucked half his length into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” Carlos grunted, “You’re so hot! Can I go deeper?” Kara moaned in agreement and reached out with both hands to grab his ass, pulling him closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, babe, she wants to swallow you,” Lucia exclaimed. Kara groaned and choked as he pushed forward, but at the same time, her body shook with wave after wave of pleasure. Lucia felt a gush of hot fluid around her fingers as Kara’s thighs suddenly squeezed shut around her hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shit, she’s cumming so hard right now! She loves having her mouth stuffed with your cock.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, fuck! Her throat is so tight, I’m gonna cum too,” Carlos exclaimed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No!” Lucia ordered, “That’s mine, put your cock back in my cunt.” Kara coughed and groaned deliriously as both Carlos’ cock and Lucia’s fingers pulled out abruptly. “UGH, fuck yeah,” Lucia groaned as he slipped effortlessly back into her. “Fuck me hard, I want her to watch as you shoot that load in my pussy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos wasted no time, grabbing Lucia’s hips and roughly fucking her. She dropped back onto her elbows, pressing her face against Kara’s stomach, grunting with each thrust. She felt Kara’s hands grip her cheeks, spreading them for a better view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos let out a strangled cry of triumph as he thrust deep and held there, his cock twitching inside her as he came hard. After a moment, he pulled out and staggered back, collapsing on the other bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moaning happily, Lucia pushed herself upright. She swayed gently in place, catching her breath, and still straddling Kara’s head. The brunette’s shirt was twisted to one side, the v-neck revealing the sex flush across her chest. Her visibly wet panties were slid partway down her hip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kara,” Lucia giggled, as she felt thick, hot liquid begin to slip from her lips. “See how full of cum I am?” Kara looked up, eyes still wide with arousal as Carlos’s cum dripped across her chin and cheek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;Dios mío, chica!&lt;/em&gt;” Laughing deliriously with excitement, Lucia took her hand and pulled her up into an embrace. Kara hugged her back, laughing as Lucia stepped back and looked into her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That was… unexpected?” Kara said uncertainly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, but good, right?” Lucia beamed. “Can I kiss you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, yeah, please,” Kara said, and then Lucia pressed against her. The kiss was long and heated. Lucia savored the mingled taste of both her and Carlos’ cum on Kara’s lips. She felt a heat growing in her core again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breaking the kiss, Lucia shot a quick glance at Carlos. Unsurprisingly, the sight of the two of them kissing had reignited the spark of desire in his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know, Kara,” she whispered conspiratorially, “I can get him hard again. Maybe… we could trade places this time? I could get under you and you can finger me while I watch him fuck you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Kara looked hesitant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, don’t worry, I won’t let him cum inside you! He can cum in my mouth. I just think it’d be hot to watch you get fucked… That’s not it, is it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kara bit her lip and stepped back, pulling her underwear up and adjusting her shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, um, I mean, I had a lot of fun. Like, a surprising amount of fun?” The words came tumbling out of her. “I didn’t even know I liked girls. I came here with a crush on Ian, and he’s been flirting with Amy the whole time, and then I saw you two, and it got me so turned on, and then, you know, this all happened, and like… I’m glad? But also I think I need to go like get some air…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, hey, that’s fine.” Lucia smiled and reached out and squeezed her hand. “I get it, this all happened really fast. Let me know if you ever want to talk about it, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Kara nodded, “I’d like that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cool… Um, are you okay if I still fool around with Carlos for a bit?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, yeah, of course, I mean, I’m not trying to stop you guys, I just need to slow down a bit?” Kara picked up her phone and shorts and moved to the door. “Just text me when you’re done, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The door closed with a quiet click and they heard her footsteps pad down the hall. A long moment passed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is she gonna be okay?” Carlos asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia felt a warm glow in her chest. Abruptly she turned, pushed him down on the bed, and lay down beside him. “You’re sweet.” She gave him a kiss and threw a leg over him. “She’s fine, she just needed some air.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh good,” he nodded, “I was worried we scared her off.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Worried you scared her off with your &lt;em&gt;huge cock&lt;/em&gt;?” Lucia laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I can’t help how big I am.” He grinned, and she felt him twitch under her thigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You better help &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt; with how big you are,” Lucia growled playfully, reaching down to caress his quickly stiffening shaft. “I’ve been looking forward to this for weeks, and I need you to make me cum again before I kick your ass out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmmmm, will you go down on me for a minute?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course,” she purred, scooting down and taking him in her mouth. He tasted of cum, and before long he was pressed against the back of her mouth, and she came up gasping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you …ah!” Carlos gasped as she straddled him, slipping his cock back inside her. “Oh, that feels good… You don’t think she’ll tell the coaches about us, do you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah,” Lucia purred, rolling her hips and savoring the way he filled her. “I think she was just a little overwhelmed by how into it she was and how fast things went. I bet…ah… ah…” Lucia arched her back, losing her words for a moment. “Yeah, like that babe… Um, she’s just realized some new things about herself. She’ll be fine.” She leaned forward, putting her hands on the headboard and her tits in his face. “Now stop talking about Kara and suck on my nipples.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucia gasped as his lips closed around her breast. She ground her pelvis against him, savoring the pressure on her clit and the way his cock filled her. Everything was sensitive and lights were dancing on the edge of her vision again. Her body felt like it was crackling with electricity. Having Carlos under her felt like the most natural thing in the world, and she never wanted to get off. She wondered if she could stay at this level all night, just riding this wave of arousal…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmm! Oh, fuck,” Carlos groaned, his face buried in her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, baby, keep going, you’re so fucking hot,” she breathed. He responded by switching to her other nipple and reaching back to squeeze her ass. She squealed as he thrust his hips, lifting her off the bed and somehow reaching deeper inside her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, they found their groove, moving as one, Lucia rocking forward and back as he gripped her tightly, pulling her against him as he pushed up. He released her nipple with a loud wet smack and dropped his head onto the pillow. His eyes locked with hers, and she saw nothing but his desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah! Lucia! Please!” She felt his body stiffen, and his cock swell. He was going to cum again. She was going to make him cum again. The thought was enough to push her over the edge. She dropped down, burying her face in his neck, and squeezing him between her thighs. Her climax radiated from her core, from his cock, in waves of pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, Carlos, Carlos! Do it, please, cum for me!” She squeezed her eyes shut and bit his shoulder, flashes of orange and yellow as her orgasm rolled on and on. He wrapped his arms around her and held her tightly as his entire body rocked. She felt a spreading heat as his cock throbbed in her clenching pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For several minutes, they were speechless. She breathed against his neck and savored the lingering aftershocks. Eventually, his cock softened enough to slip out of her with a squelching sound that made them both laugh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He pulled her into a long, lazy kiss before letting his arms drop limply to his sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, that was amazing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, it was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You think Kara’s coming back soon?” She could feel him grinning as he asked, and playfully smacked him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dummy. Shut up or I’ll make you climb out through that thorn bush before you get dressed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh hell no, I’m not touching that bush again. Your coaches have gotta be asleep by now. When I leave, I’ll just sneak out the front door.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, but stay here with me awhile longer.” She sighed happily and nuzzled against him as he lazily caressed her back.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Truth or Dare</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/truth-or-dare/"/>
		<published>2021-09-01T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2021-09-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/truth-or-dare/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="group sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="pussy eating" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="female masturbation" />
    <category term="spanking" />
    <category term="ffm" />
    <category term="threesome" />
    <category term="roommates" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/truth-or-dare-Xr5Sv_Gog3-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It was clear to Julie that nothing would happen unless she got involved. The party wound down a while ago, and everyone had gone home except Alice’s friend Dan. There was chemistry between him and the two roommates, but he seemed reluctant to act on it. Julie could tell that Alice fancied him, but was hesitating because she could also sense a spark between him and Julie. Alice sometimes suffered from limited imagination, Julie thought, as she grabbed three beers from the fridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the living room, Alice was on the couch, telling a story while gesticulating wildly with a now-empty bottle. Dan reclined in the loveseat across from her, laughing and holding a beer he’d already peeled the label from. Julie handed them each a fresh drink and sat down next to Alice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let’s play truth or dare,” she suggested casually when Alice finished talking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice shot her a look that said, “I see what you’re doing,” but didn’t object.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan leaned forward. “I’m game. Alice, you start.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, okay,” Alice smiled. “Dan, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who’s your celebrity crush?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Scarlett Johansson.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie rolled her eyes. “Boooooring.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, I like her!” Dan protested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everyone &lt;em&gt;likes&lt;/em&gt; her,” Julie retorted. “She wears a leather catsuit in comic book movies. Try harder.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine,” Dan laughed. “Julie, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who’s &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; celebrity crush?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jason Momoa,” she purred. “Especially back when he had dreads. But I wouldn’t kick Rihanna out of my bed,” she trailed off. “…Okay, Dan, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ever fooled around in public?” Julie leaned forward, arching her eyebrows at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” he hesitated, taking a sip of his beer. “I got a BJ in a movie theater once.” He turned to Alice. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth, please.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have you ever gone commando in public?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes in the summer,” Alice said with a smile. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have you…” she hesitated, trying to match the spirit of his question, “ever gone streaking?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In high school, my shorts fell off at the pool, and the girl I had a crush on saw me, does that count?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice laughed. “I’ll allow it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan turned back to Julie and asked, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What age did you lose your virginity?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sixteen, to a guy on the soccer team. Really nice legs, but surprisingly little stamina.” Alice laughed, and Julie asked her, “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What kind of panties are you wearing?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice shot a nervous glance in Dan’s direction, but answered the question. “A black mesh thong.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nice, date night underwear!” Julie laughed, giving Dan a thumbs-up as Alice blushed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, I see how it is,” Alice said with bravado. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth, babe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Describe your bra to Dan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Gladly!” Julie winked at Dan while cupping her breasts. “It’s my favorite, blue satin with lace at the top of the cups. Super cute.” He nodded approvingly, raised his beer to her, and they both took a drink. Julie looked back at Alice. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you tell Dan,” she said with a knowing grin, “what you wear to sleep?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um,” Alice stammered, “just some shorts and a tank top.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s a lie,” Julie snorted. “You sleep nak—ow!” She rubbed her arm where Alice had elbowed her. “Dan, truth or dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you sleep in?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just boxers,” Dan said, clearly still savoring the thought of Alice sleeping naked. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” Julie grinned, knowing what was coming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; sleep in?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice’s bed, if I’m drunk,” She paused for a moment to savor the surprise on his face. Alice hid her face in her hands and groaned. Ignoring this, Julie leaned conspiratorially towards Dan. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, truth,” he answered, still trying to decide if she was joking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does that excite you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean… yeah,” he nodded. “Yeah, it does. Alice, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” she answered reluctantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does she really get in your bed?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice let out a long sigh and sat up straighter, as if resolving not to feel embarrassed. “Yes. Now and then. Usually, she just wants to make out a bit, and sometimes…” She looked at Julie, smiling despite herself. “I don’t mind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan looked like he wanted to ask a million follow-up questions, but instead, he nodded thoughtfully and took a sip of his beer. “Well, alright.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth or dare?” Alice asked him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have you ever made out with a roommate?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I’ve only had male roommates. When they’re drunk, they’re more likely to pass out playing Madden in the living room than climb into my bed.” Dan turned his attention back to Julie. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” she grinned, starting to really enjoy herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Drunk roommate make-out sessions aside, have you ever hooked up with a woman?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t threaten me with a good time!” They all laughed. “More girls than guys, to be honest.” She waited for Dan to take an awkwardly long sip of his beer and asked, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Drunk roommate make-out sessions aside,” she echoed his question back to him, “have you ever hooked up with a man?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, not my thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Too bad, guys making out gets Alice hot,” she replied, ducking a pillow Alice threw at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice, truth or dare?” Dan asked, picking up the pillow and handing it back to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you, and truth.” She smirked at Julie, who stuck her tongue out at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It sounds like Julie’s bisexual,” he started, getting a big thumbs up from Julie. “What about you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I mean, who isn’t at least a bit bi?” Alice shrugged and took a big drink. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” Dan answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s your manscaping situation?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan raised an eyebrow as Alice tried to play it cool. “Short and tidy. Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth, please.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s your ladyscaping situation?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just trim. Hair’s there for a reason, and I can’t be bothered to shave all the time.” Sensing Julie’s eagerness, she turned and with exaggerated formality said, “Julie, would you like a truth or a dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I already know the answer, but I don’t want you to feel left out of the grooming discussion. Would you like to share with the class?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know I take it all off, babe!” Julie blurted. “I keep offering to refer you to my waxer!” Turning to Dan, she explained, “she’s this great old Hungarian lady, fantastic technique. Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you prefer smooth as silk,” she said, gesturing toward her lap, “or classic 70s bush?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I do not have a 70s bush!” Alice protested, swatting Julie’s hand away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan looked nervous and held up both hands as if to ward off the choice. “You know, regardless of the landscaping, I’m just happy to get a tour of the garden. Julie, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you like to masturbate?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright, Dan!” Julie laughed, “now you’re getting into the spirit of the game! Yeah, I go through my share of batteries. Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” Dan grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How often do you rub one out?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Daily, before I go to sleep. Alice, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When did you last get off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice took a slow sip of her beer, hesitating before answering. “In the shower this morning. Julie, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” Julie beamed. She felt this was going extremely well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What do you think about when you masturbate?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Two guys at once!” She answered with no hesitation, and Alice nearly choked. Dan looked impressed. “Sometimes it’s dudes I saw at the gym. Sometimes it’s old crushes. But they always make me a Julie sandwich.” She waggled her eyebrows at Dan as he and Alice both laughed. “Alice, truth or dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have you ever thought of Dan while masturbating?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice blushed and avoided looking at Dan. “Um, on second thought, can I have a dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, then. Take off your bra.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice set down her beer, deftly unhooked her bra, and slipped it out her sleeve. She handed it to Julie, who nodded approvingly at the black mesh fabric and threw it to Dan. He jokingly held it up to his chest like he was trying it on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice giggled and asked, “Dan, truth or dare?” She made no effort to cover her nipples pushing through the thin fabric of her shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth,” Dan answered, draping her bra over the back of the loveseat and doing his best not to stare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; ever thought about &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt; while masturbating?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan grinned, and let the question hang in the air before simply replying: “Dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take off your shirt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He did, leaving Julie nodding approvingly at his rather nice chest. She was starting to get what Alice saw in this guy. Meeting her gaze, he asked, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have you ever had a threesome?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Once.” Julie glanced meaningfully towards Alice in a way that Dan couldn’t miss. “Not with two guys yet, but I’m working on it. Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What about you? Ever had a threesome?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s… on my list.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie winked at Alice, who took a sip of beer and pretended not to notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice,” Dan asked, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s your favorite position?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I like to be on top,” she replied confidently. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you one of those guys who won’t go down on a woman?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, I’ve been told I’m quite good at it.” Alice tried to hide her smile as Dan turned to Julie. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you a screamer?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh, yeah,” Julie grinned. “I’ve been known to get a bit vocal.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s an understatement,” Alice laughed. “I can clearly hear her through the wall whenever she brings someone home.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie turned to Alice. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you ever touch yourself when you hear me getting fucked?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes…” Alice blushed a deep red. “Truth or dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Does it turn you on to know that I listen to you getting fucked?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie smiled and took a drink, but did not answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, then, a dare for you. Take off your top.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan watched eagerly as Julie peeled her top off, exposing her favorite bra. She winked at him. “Truth or dare, Dan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you circumcised?” She didn’t actually care, but the exchange with Alice had flustered her more than she cared to admit, and shifting the attention back to Dan seemed easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I am. Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you and Alice really have a threesome?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah.” Julie grinned at Alice, who grinned back. “And it was fucking hot.” She waited a long moment before saying, “Alice, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Were you thinking about giving Dan head in the shower this morning?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice blushed furiously and nearly choked on her beer. “Dare!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine, take off your pants.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice stood up, unzipped her jeans, and shimmied them down her hips before kicking them off. A neatly trimmed triangle of pubic hair was visible through the black mesh of her thong. Dan tried not to gawk as Alice asked him, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you stick around after the party hoping to get lucky?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gave a sheepish grin. “Dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, now take off &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; pants.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He let his jeans drop to the floor and sat back down, kicking them aside and trying to look casual while wearing only boxers. “Alice, truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Were you hoping I’d stick around to get lucky?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice grinned, took a big drink, and said “Dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Show me your tits.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice slowly lifted the hem of her shirt. Dan and Julie both stared. Alice had great breasts and knew it. After a few seconds, she covered up again, grinning and turning to Julie. “Truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did you start this game so you could have another threesome with me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie took a long sip of beer and held her gaze for what felt like a very long time. “Dare.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Take off your skirt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She stood up, unzipped, and let the skirt slip down to the floor before kicking it out of the way. The blue cotton didn’t quite match her bra, but Dan’s hungry stare made it clear he didn’t care. She caught his eyes and asked, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“…Dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Go kiss Alice.” As he stood up, she clarified: “A &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; kiss, not a peck on the cheek!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He sauntered closer and bent down to give Alice a slow, gentle kiss. His hands cupped her face, and she leaned into him. Even so, the kiss seemed to end just a bit too quickly, as if he was afraid of overstaying his welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He returned to the loveseat before asking Julie, “truth or dare?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’d also like to know if you started this game so you could have another threesome with Alice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie looked away and made a point of finishing her beer before answering. “You know, I think we’re done with truths for now. Let’s just play dares.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fine,” Dan grinned, “now &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; give Alice a &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; kiss.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie turned to Alice, who was smiling in anticipation. She climbed into Alice’s lap and kissed her deeply. Her fingers traced up Alice’s neck and into her hair. Their lips parted, and their tongues danced together. Alice whimpered and arched her back as Julie’s hands strayed lower, over Alice’s breasts, feeling her nipples stiffen under her palms. When she finally pulled away, Alice’s cheeks were flushed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie gave her a minute before saying, “Alice, let Dan take off your shirt.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice bit her lip, then smiled and nodded at Dan. He dropped to his knees in front of her, and she lifted her arms as he pulled her shirt up. As he did, he made a point to slowly slide his hands over her breasts, teasing her nipples. It seemed to take a very long time. Eventually, Dan sat back down, laying Alice’s shirt next to her bra on the back of the loveseat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay,” Alice murmured as she crossed her legs. Her nipples had contracted into hard buds. “Alright.” She let out a breath and took a long sip of her beer. After a moment, she turned to Julie and said, “Let Dan take off your bra.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grinning, Julie sat forward as Dan got to his knees in front of her. As he reached behind her, she leaned into him, brushing her lips against his stubble. He slowly unhooked the clasp and ran his fingers up and down her spine, making her shiver. She buried her face in the warmth of his neck as he slipped the straps from her shoulders. Finally, she leaned back, allowing him to pull her bra away from her chest. He stared hungrily at her dark nipples before returning to the loveseat, laying her bra next to Alice’s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice?” Julie purred, “go suck on Dan’s…” She paused, letting Dan’s anticipation build. “…fingers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice grinned and dropped to her knees in front of Dan. She lifted his hand to her lips. He watched, spellbound, as she began to kiss and lick his first two fingers. When she finally took them into her mouth, he inhaled sharply. Quickly, she began sucking with practiced ease. Julie felt a growing heat in her core as she watched Alice simulate a blowjob. When she finally moved back to the couch, Dan was clearly having difficulty slowing his breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Dan,” Alice began, speaking softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes?” He tried not to sound flustered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Wanna hand over that pillow?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprised, he glanced down and seemed to realize for the first time that he was holding a pillow in his lap as if he was afraid it would fly away. Laughing, he relaxed his grip. “Oh, uh, sure, here you go.” He gently tossed it to her and draped his arms across the back of the loveseat, a prominent erection tenting his boxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You know,” he said, turning to Julie. “We both kissed Alice. It seems only fair that you should kiss me now.” As she got up to do so, Dan echoed her words: “But please, make sure this is a &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; kiss, not a peck on the cheek!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Julie approached Dan, she leaned over him, planting her hands on the back of the loveseat to either side of his head. She wasn’t quite ready to climb into his lap, knowing that once she started grinding against him, it’d be hard to stop. Instead, she slowly and deliberately arched her back to drag her breasts down his face as she came in to kiss him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their lips parted immediately, and the steamy open-mouthed kiss that followed left her heart pounding. He kept his hands to himself, accepting what she offered but not pushing for more. She appreciated his restraint, but pulled his hand to her chest anyway. She shivered as he gently squeezed her nipple. With some reluctance, she broke away and returned to the couch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice?” She turned to her friend, who grinned excitedly. “Show Dan if you’re wet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice only briefly hesitated before reaching into her panties. Julie and Dan watched eagerly as her legs parted and her fingers moved below the mesh fabric. When she withdrew her hand, her index finger was glistening wet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh dear,” she teased Dan, “there seems to be some cream on my finger. Would you mind licking it off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a heartbeat, Dan was on his knees with her finger in his mouth. He looked as though he was savoring the most delicious flavor in the world. Alice giggled and squirmed until he released her finger with a wet pop and returned to his seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan turned his attention eagerly to Julie. “Show me if &lt;em&gt;you’re&lt;/em&gt; wet?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie grinned and simply spread her legs wide to reveal the dark wet spot on her panties. Dan stared hungrily at this evidence of her arousal until she crossed her legs again and turned to Alice. “Can I have your panties, please?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice stood up and shimmied them off, but instead of handing them to Julie, she walked over to Dan. He watched with a grin on his face as she pulled open his waistband and reached in to wrap her thong around his erection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Releasing his waistband with a snap, she straightened up and turned away. Clearly savoring their attention on her naked body, she swayed her hips as she walked back to the couch. She looked at Julie and said teasingly, “Why don’t you go get them?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie laughed and went to stand over Dan. He watched with a big grin as she made a point of reaching into his boxers and rummaging around without looking. She played it up, as if unsure where to find Alice’s underwear. In reality, she firmly gripped his cock, rubbing the damp fabric against his swollen head. Finally, she made a surprised face as she “found” them and pulled them out with a flourish like a magician.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They gave her a polite round of applause, and she gave an exaggerated curtsey. Instead of returning to the couch, she sat down on the loveseat next to Dan. She leaned against him, draping her arm over his shoulder and winking conspiratorially at him. Then she looked at Alice and said, “why don’t you spread your legs and let Dan get a good look at you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice blushed, her cheeks matching the growing flush across her chest, but scooted lower on the couch and opened her thighs. Slowly, she reached down with two fingers and spread herself. At the sight of her pink inner lips, slick with her juices, Dan’s hand unconsciously drifted to his erection. Julie leaned closer and whispered in his ear, “do you see how wet she is for you?” He nodded, unable to look away as Alice started to trace a finger in lazy circles around her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps inspired by Julie whispering in his ear, Alice said, “why don’t you climb in his lap and tell him about our last threesome?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagerly, Julie moved to straddle him, with her hands on his shoulders. He gasped as she lowered herself against his erection. She rolled her hips, grinding her clit along his shaft. She could clearly feel the heat of his cock through the two thin layers of fabric that separated them. Finally, she leaned forward, pressing her chest against his, arms wrapped around his neck. His skin was hot, and she felt an answering heat inside her. She started whispering in his ear, knowing his eyes remained locked on Alice’s pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So Alice was on her hands and knees, and the guy was behind her, fucking her.” Julie felt his cock throb as she said that. “I was under her, with my head between her thighs. I had the best view of his cock thrusting in and out. She’d already made me cum from eating me out,” (throb) “but now she was distracted by his cock. Fuck, it was hot. I started licking her.” (throb) “Every time he pulled out, I would lick the length of his shaft.” (throb) “When he pushed deeper, I would circle her clit.” (throb) “It didn’t take long before she came. She gushed around his cock, into my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan was breathing heavily, his hands caressing her thighs, but his eyes still fixed in Alice’s direction. Julie turned around to look and grinned when she saw her roommate still masturbating for Dan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice, telling this story is getting me so hot, will you suck on my nipple while I grind against Dan?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice wasted no time moving to sit next to Dan and wrap her lips around Julie’s nipple. Julie gasped as she sucked more of her breast into the heat of her mouth. She continued rocking her hips, grinding against Dan’s throbbing shaft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice, I was telling Dan about how I was licking your clit while you got fucked.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice purred happily, her tongue dancing around Julie’s nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told him how hot it was to watch, to see you cum, and see his—ah!—see his cock swelling inside you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan was gripping her hips, biting his lip as Julie rubbed against him, and he watched Alice suck on her breast. He looked up at Julie eagerly, and she nodded, pulling his face to her other breast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, you can suck on my other—oh!—nipple. Oh fuck, yeah, keep doing that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie’s grinding was becoming more insistent. She had one hand wrapped around the back of each of their heads. Dan’s cock was unyielding against her, and her clit seemed to crackle with electricity as she dragged it along the length of his shaft. Their tongues swirled around her nipples as she struggled to keep talking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alice, it was so fucking sexy to see your pussy lips wrapped around his cock. When he said he was about to cum — ooh!—I pulled him out of you and into my mouth—ah!—he was covered in your cream, and it tasted so good—fuck!—he was so ready and he thrust forward—uh!—into my throat and suddenly he was—aaaah!—cumming! Cumming!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As if to punctuate the story, Julie’s first orgasm rolled down her spine. She tightened her grip on their hair, pulling them harder against her breasts. Her pussy was clenching, yearning to be filled. Every flick of a tongue against her nipples sent sparks flowing down to her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was too much. She cried out and pushed them both away, dropping her head onto Dan’s shoulder. He held her tight and she shuddered against him as her climax receded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan’s cock throbbed against her, and he spoke softly. “Why don’t you and Alice trade places?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grinning, Julie allowed him to roll her to the side. Alice quickly took her place straddling Dan, hands on his shoulders. She leaned forward to rest her breast against Dan’s face, who eagerly opened his mouth around her nipple. Alice gasped and reached for Julie as he started sucking. Grinning, she leaned in and began tracing circles with her tongue around Alice’s areola. She felt her nipple stiffen and pulled it deeper into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice started moaning as she rolled her hips repeatedly against Dan, rubbing the head of his cock against her opening. He was gripping her hips tightly, pulling her against him. She followed his lead, leaning forward, gasping at the constant stimulation. They all rocked back and forth repeatedly, Alice’s arousal growing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan grunted and reached back to grab her ass, his fingers digging hard into her flesh. Alice squeaked and leaped from his lap. She stood squirming in front of them, wetness running down her thighs, trying to catch her breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh! Oh, sorry. That was a little too much too fast… I… I need a minute.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan groaned with a mixture of desire and frustration, but nodded. “Uh, yeah, that’s probably a good idea, I don’t know how much more of that I could take.” Julie grinned as she noticed the front of his boxers were absolutely soaked with Alice’s creamy juices.
Alice noticed where she was looking and giggled. “I’m sorry, but I seem to have made a mess of your underwear.” She bit her lip, clearly not sorry at all. “Why don’t you take them off?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grinning, Dan got to his feet, and peeled his boxers off, letting them drop to the floor and kicking them aside. Julie nodded appreciatively as he revealed a pleasant cock with well-groomed pubes. It bobbed proudly erect, jutting towards Julie as if asking for her attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan saw her looking and smiled. “Now it’s your turn.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She climbed to her feet to stand with the two of them, slipped her underwear down her hips, and stepped out of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They all stood naked in the middle of the room. Alice slipped an arm around Julie’s waist. Julie allowed herself to be pulled into a slow, soft kiss. Aware of his gaze, she reached out for Dan and pulled him in. She broke off the kiss with Alice and angled up to kiss him. Alice nuzzled her ear and cupped her ass until Julie led Dan to kiss Alice again. Back and forth they went, kissing and caressing each other’s bodies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, as Alice and Dan were kissing, Julie reached down and started rubbing his cock. He gasped but kept kissing Alice, even as his cock twitched in her hand. Julie brushed her lips against Alice’s ear and said, “I want to watch you go down on Dan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan allowed Julie to lead him to the couch, where she gently pushed him down and sat next to him, still stroking his cock. They watched eagerly as Alice got to her knees between his legs. Alice deftly slipped her hand beneath Julie’s and took over stroking, so Julie laid back to watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Alice took him into her mouth, Dan groaned and dropped his head back. He ran his hands through her hair and mumbled her name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie bit her lip and watched happily, lazily rubbing herself. Watching Alice give head was really hot. Dan’s stomach tensed as her head bobbed up and down. Julie imagined Alice’s tongue swirling, teasing the tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, Alice, that feels good,” Dan moaned. In response, Alice pushed forward, swallowing his cock deeper. Julie moaned at the sight and slipped a finger between her slick pussy lips. Alice relaxed and moved back, releasing his cock from her mouth, but continuing to stroke him as she gasped for breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have a really nice cock, Dan,” she murmured before wrapping her lips around his head once again. Dan groaned and put a hand on top of her head, not pushing, but encouraging. Julie’s hand moved more urgently, palm rubbing against her clit as her finger slipped in and out, matching the pace that Alice sucked his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan noticed Julie masturbating, and watched eagerly. Julie grinned and added another finger. Dan was now lifting his hips, trying to push deeper into Alice’s mouth, who was moaning with each thrust. Sensing the need to slow things down before he came, Julie pulled her fingers from her pussy and pushed them abruptly into Dan’s mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He grunted in surprise, but it worked. He relaxed and stopped thrusting, focused on sucking the cream from Julie’s fingers. She leaned in and murmured in his ear, “easy there, Dan, let’s make it last.” She pulled her fingers from his mouth and gave him a soft kiss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice released his cock with a wet sound and stood up, licking her lips. “Julie, will you go get a condom while Dan goes down on me?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie grinned and stood up, wrapping both arms around Alice and kissing her deeply. Alice seemed surprised, but melted into the embrace and kissed her back. Julie pulled back, winked at her, and happily skipped off toward the restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she got the box of condoms out of the cabinet (almost out, she noted), she heard Alice moan in the living room. Eagerly, she jogged back in to see that Alice and Dan had traded places. Alice sprawled lewdly on the couch, slouched low with her ass hanging off the edge and her legs spread wide. Dan was kneeling before her, with his face buried between her thighs, like he was worshipping her. Alice was already breathing heavily and squeezing her breasts. Apparently, Dan wasn’t lying when he said he was good at oral.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice opened her eyes and grinned at Julie, still gasping with pleasure. Julie held up the condom and gave her a thumbs-up. In response, Alice’s eyes rolled up in her head and she swore loudly as Dan did something with his tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie grinned and dropped to her knees behind Dan. Quickly tearing the wrapper, she pulled out the condom, figured out which way it unrolled, and pinched it by the tip. He jumped in surprise when she reached her arms around and grabbed his cock, but Alice grabbed his head and ground his face back against her vulva.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, Julie rolled the condom down the length of his shaft. Once it was in place, she moved around to one side so she could watch. Dan was working his face side to side, his tongue tracing broad circles over Alice’s lips. He would lick upward in a circle around her clit before wrapping his lips around it and sucking. Then, just before it would be too much, he licked downward, pushing between her lips as deep as he could reach, before licking back upward again. Alice’s stomach was tense, her chest flushed, erect nipples peeking between her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie leaned in and murmured in his ear, “I think she’s ready for you now.” She pulled him back upright and kissed him. Alice’s juices coated his face, which Julie didn’t mind at all. She pushed her tongue deep into his mouth, savoring the taste, before breaking off and pushing him gently backward. “Lie down here on the rug.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan obediently lay on his back as Julie helped Alice get to her feet, and walked her over to stand over him. Alice got to her knees and positioned his cock between her lips. They all grinned at each other, savoring the anticipation, until Alice lowered herself, gasping as she took his full length.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice and Dan both seemed to be holding their breath, adjusting to the sensation. She rolled her hips and arched her back, letting out a long, low groan. Dan reached up to cup her breasts, and she squeezed his hands as she started rocking on top of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie found herself kneeling by Dan’s shoulder, rubbing her clit as she watched the two of them fuck. She stared hungrily at the sight of Dan’s cock disappearing between Alice’s lips, which seemed to be devouring him whole. Dan groaned as she moved above him, and squeezed her nipples hard, until she cried out, moving her hips faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan looked up and saw Julie rubbing herself. “Let me taste you,” he gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie didn’t hesitate, swinging her leg over to straddle his face. She felt him raise his head behind her, eager to make contact, and lowered herself until she felt his lips against hers. His tongue slipped between her folds, probing deep inside. She gasped and fell forward with her hands on his torso, pressing her clit against his tongue. Following her lead, he began flicking against her sensitive bud, until she was panting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt a hand on her face and looked up to see Alice watching her, eyes full of desire. Without needing to speak, the girls fell towards each other and began kissing. It was awkward with all three of them moving and rocking, but they were too aroused to care. Alice moaned into Julie’s mouth, and their hands roamed over each other’s bodies. Fingers tangled in hair, squeezing breasts, caressing hips. Gasping as Dan’s tongue lashed her clit, Julie broke the kiss and dropped her face to Alice’s chest. Alice moaned and guided Julie’s mouth to her nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice was grunting and moaning and bouncing faster, grinding Dan’s cock deeper into her, mashing her breast against Julie’s face. She had one hand tangled in Julie’s hair and the other was frantically rubbing her clit. Her breathing came faster and faster until suddenly she cried out and her body stiffened. Julie released her nipple and pulled Alice’s head to her shoulder. For several long moments, Alice shook and moaned into Julie’s neck as the orgasm pulsated through her body. Finally, she climbed to her feet and dropped onto the couch, one hand clamped between her thighs, trying to catch her breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie found herself leaning forward, still grinding her clit against Dan’s mouth. His cock was jutting towards her, slick with Alice’s cream as he thrust upward, desperate for more contact. Julie lowered herself and took his cock in her mouth. The condom tasted rubbery and medicinal, but Alice’s cum was delicious. Dan’s cock throbbed in her mouth, swelling as he tried to push deeper. Julie tried to swallow him and gagged, forced to back off as Dan moaned between her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gasping for breath, she sat up and lifted herself off his face. He looked up at her, face covered in her wetness, panting and eager. “Get behind me, Dan.” He was only too happy to oblige.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan moved behind her as she dropped to her hands and knees. She bit her lip in anticipation as she felt him rub his cock against her, working it between her lips. A guttural moan escaped her lips when he pushed forward, burying himself to the hilt in one thrust. Her pussy responded to being filled by clenching uncontrollably around his girth. It felt delicious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He started moving, gripping her hips and thrusting forward. Each backstroke took him nearly all the way out of her, then he would pull her back, hard, fucking her against him as he pushed deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck your cock feels good in me,” she groaned, eyes rolling. She looked up and saw Alice on the couch, watching her with lust in her eyes. Meeting her hooded gaze, Alice spread her legs again, letting Julie see the two fingers she had buried in her pussy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Get in front of Julie,” Dan gasped from behind her. “I want to watch you touch yourself while I fuck her.” He was practically moaning as he said it, and Julie suspected he wasn’t used to asking for what he wanted so bluntly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice moved down to the floor, laying on her back with her legs spread, rubbing her clit eagerly in front of Julie’s face. Before long, she was gasping and moaning, still holding eye contact with Julie. With every thrust, Julie came closer to Alice’s pussy. The stimulating smell of Alice’s arousal filled her head. She knew Dan was trying to push her closer. She didn’t mind, she wanted the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, Julie!” Alice suddenly blurted, “I’m so close, I need your fingers, please, please put your fingers in me.” Dan moaned appreciatively behind her as Julie shifted her weight to her left elbow. She slipped two fingers into Alice’s sopping pussy and felt her insides immediately clench around her, pulsing in time with Alice’s moans. A hot gush of fluid washed over her fingers as Alice slapped the floor and cried out in wordless pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie felt her own orgasm building and pushed back against Dan. “Fuck me harder, I’m close!” Dan’s pace quickened, clearly as aroused as she was by the sight of Alice’s orgasm. Julie rested her forehead against the rug, eyes screwed shut, focused on the sensation of the cock slamming ever deeper inside. She reached down to rub her clit. She was getting closer, but needed something more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Slap my ass!” She barked, surprising even herself. Dan obliged, a single sharp stinging slap across her ass cheek. She gasped, and moaned, “again!” Another slap on the other cheek, the tingling mixing with the overwhelming sensations from her pussy. Dan gripped her hips even harder, thrusting roughly into her as she panted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god, that feels so good,” Dan groaned. “I can feel your cunt squeezing me.” He gasped as he said the word cunt, and so did she. “I’m gonna cum soon…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuuuuuuck yes, yes, yes, do it,” Julie begged, feeling her body tensing, her climax approaching. “Cum for me, I want you to cum!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan cried out loudly and squeezed her hips so hard it hurt, pulling her tightly against him to reach as deep as possible. She gasped as she felt his cock throbbing inside her, pumping his cum into the condom. Her orgasm was hovering right on the edge, she just needed a little more. Abruptly he pulled out, and she collapsed to the floor, rolling onto her back, and cursing in frustration, she was so close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice dove between her legs. Julie cried out in surprise as she felt her hot tongue moving in tight circles around her clit. She felt fingers enter her, hooking upward. Almost immediately, she felt the wave of her orgasm crash hard. She grabbed a fistful of Alice’s hair and pulled her closer, grinding her clit against her tongue. She heard Alice moan in surprise as she came again, pleasure rolling down her spine, through her pelvis, and into Alice’s mouth. Alice stayed with her, steady, firm pressure until Julie relaxed. Only then did she pull away, making Julie shiver as she withdrew her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They all lay collapsed in a heap on the rug, breathing heavily and laughing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie climbed into Alice’s bed to cuddle. Dan had made a polite and only slightly awkward exit a while ago. Alice was sleepily playing a game on her phone. She stirred as she felt the covers lift, and wrapped an arm around Julie as she curled up against her side, one leg thrown over hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Honestly,” Alice said, with a smile, “I don’t know why we pay for a two-bedroom apartment. We basically only use one bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmm,” Julie agreed drowsily. “…don’t like sleeping alone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lucky for me,” Alice said and kissed her forehead before returning to her game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julie was already asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>One Wild Night 1: Coach Samantha</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/1-coach-samantha/"/>
		<published>2020-10-22T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2020-10-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/one-wild-night/1-coach-samantha/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="oral sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fellatio" />
    <category term="pussy eating" />
    <category term="coworker" />
    <category term="coach" />
    <category term="college" />
    <category term="school" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/one-wild-night-Pyynvvfm4a-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Standing back from the luggage carousel, Samantha yawned and cracked her neck. She’d spotted her purple rolling bag right away, and was just waiting for Jake and the students to find theirs among the cascade of identical black duffles. She rolled her shoulders, trying to work out the kinks from the cramped coach flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake was not-so-subtly admiring the way her shirt pulled tighter across her chest when she arched her back. She stuck out her tongue at him. Not because she minded the way he looked at her, so much as that he was doing it in front of the students. He grinned and turned away, grabbing his bag and loudly encouraging everyone else to find theirs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam sighed and smiled, despite herself. The problem with Jake was that he &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; he was cute. He had carefully tousled hair and just a bit of stubble. He wore a flannel shirt with rolled-up sleeves. He struck a careful balance between casual cool and slovenly. He was charming without trying too hard. There was a reason that most nights, after the Robotics squad went home, she invited him back to her place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had started the Robotics team at Lovelace High School to encourage more young women to pursue an interest in science and technology. As the group became more popular, even a few boys had asked to join. She’d been worried that would affect the dynamic, but for the most part it had been fine. Eventually, the team had grown to the point she needed assistance, and she’d asked Jake to help out. He was great with the girls, always respectful and encouraging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, it was Jake who had suggested the team enter the MIT competition. It was held every summer, and the qualifying teams received a large grant and a paid trip to the MIT campus. Over a long weekend the team would participate in a competition and meet other teams of high schoolers. But perhaps more importantly, they’d get to tour the university’s labs, meet leading roboticists, and make connections. The nature of the trip meant it was restricted to the oldest students, at least age eighteen. All told, Sam and Jake had brought eight of their best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everybody got their bags?” Jake called out, and the students cheered, excited to get moving. “Alright, follow Coach Sam and the guy with the sign over here, he’s brought a van to drive us to campus. Stay together!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The campus rep, who’d met them by the luggage area with a sign reading “Lovelace High,” led them to one of those generic white vans with rows and rows of seats. The students were practically vibrating with excitement after the flight. Sam managed to grab shotgun, and let herself admire the sunset as they drove through Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the van pulled up in front of the student housing, she was pleased to see that they had a large quad dorm all to themselves. She’d been worried about how they would supervise the students if they were spread across multiple units. As Jake and the campus rep chatted about the weekend schedule, she checked the place out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The front door opened into a large open-plan common room, split roughly in half between linoleum flooring in the kitchen/dining area and carpeting in the living area. Two couches sat at the edge of the carpeting with their backs to the kitchen, facing a flatscreen TV mounted to the far wall. Two short hallways opened on either side of the room. Each connected to two bedrooms and a bathroom. The bedrooms were all identical, with twin beds and a window facing the parking lot. The bathrooms each had a shower. Honestly, it was a lot nicer than the dorm room she’d shared in college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The boys, Ian and Wally, grabbed the far room on the right, and the girls split up the other rooms. Sam reminded Jake that Marcy and Bonnie were a couple and needed to be in separate rooms. They protested mightily, but ultimately couldn’t stand in the face of Jake’s cheerful firmness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, everyone, it’s 10pm, time for bed!” Sam called. The students groaned about the early bedtime, but she cut them off. “That’s enough of that. We’re here to work, not party. We’ve still got to unpack all our gear and get it tested before the competition. Everything starts at 9, and we need to be there by 7, which means y’all need to be up at 6. Now go on, get to bed!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They grumbled, but began filtering towards their rooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So,” Sam said, regarding Jake with a sly look. “Four bedrooms, all claimed by teenagers. Is there anywhere for the two of us to sleep?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why, madam, I’ve reserved you the finest spot in the house.” Jake walked into the living room and bowed low, gesturing grandiosely at the larger of the two couches. “Feast your eyes upon this sofa… for hidden within is a bed fit for a queen!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam watched as Lucia, Kara, and Rylie came into the kitchen to brush their teeth. The girls were laughing and chatting, and paid no attention to the adults. She shot a conspiratorial look in Jake’s direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Gracious! Surely, you’re not suggesting what I think you’re suggesting.” She fanned herself dramatically and lowered her voice as she stepped closer. “It wouldn’t be &lt;em&gt;proper&lt;/em&gt; for us to share accommodations while acting as chaperones to these impressionable young people.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t dream of doing anything improper,” he winked. “Naturally, I’ll be sleeping on the other couch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm… That couch doesn’t look very comfortable.” She made a point of inspecting the cushions. “It’s too short to lie down on. And there’s a &lt;em&gt;rather&lt;/em&gt; large stain.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced up as Amy ran past, giggling and waving a stolen pair of men’s pajama pants. Ian was hot on her heels, laughing and protesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’ll just have to endure the discomfort for the sake of propriety. Unless…” Jake moved closer, nearly touching her, “there’s some other option?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I suppose,” she ran her finger lightly over the buttons of his shirt, “it would be rude to leave you to suffer when there appears to be room for you in my bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The girls finished brushing their teeth and retreated to their rooms, leaving Sam and Jake alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That is, if you think you can handle the, ah… proximity?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake leaned in close, and whispered, “That’s not all I can handle.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She shivered as his lips brushed against her ear and then stepped quickly away as Ian loudly ran back through the kitchen with his recovered pajama pants, chased by Amy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, come on, break it up! Everyone to their rooms!” Jake called after them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long all the students were in their rooms with the doors closed, the lights were off, and Sam and Jake were relaxing on the sofa. She leaned companionably against him, and he draped his arm across the back of the cushion. She flipped through the channels, finally landing on one of those HGTV shows where an obnoxious married couple renovates houses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake didn’t even pretend to be interested. She half-heartedly swatted at him as he started nuzzling her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Stoooop iiiiit,” she grinned. “One of the kids might come out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He smiled and leaned back. The married couple was bickering over what type of countertop to put in the kitchen. She bit her lip and tried to ignore Jake’s fingers sliding up the back of her neck to lace into her hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the commercial, she shifted a little closer to him and rested her hand on his thigh. When the show came back, the wife won the argument and ordered the more expensive granite option. Jake began tracing his finger around her ear. Sam found herself increasingly aware of the heat of his body next to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She made herself wait for the next commercial break, then casually reached up and pulled her hair back, exposing her neck. He took the hint, and she shivered when his stubble grazed her skin as he kissed along her jawline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turned to face him as their lips met. The kiss started sweetly, but quickly became passionate. He sucked on her bottom lip, and a smoldering heat grew deep inside her. She purred as he cupped her breast. She moved her hand further up the inside of his thigh, and enjoyed the way his muscles tensed under her touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long he was sucking on her neck as she unbuttoned her shirt. He eagerly slipped his hand into her bra, and she gasped as he brushed against her areola. She’d always been self-conscious about having a large chest, but loved the way Jake worshipped her breasts. She squirmed as he captured her nipple between his thumb and finger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A sudden noise made her freeze and whisper in his ear, “Did you hear a door?” He shrugged noncommittally and continued groping her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She didn’t hear anything else, and soon relaxed back into his touch. He’d been sucking the same spot on her neck long enough that some part of her was worried about getting a hickey. But every time his tongue flicked against her skin, she felt sparks roll down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time she definitely heard a door. Quickly she shifted away from Jake, tugging his hand out of her top. She had just enough time to cross her arms over the stiff nipples poking through her shirt before Amy emerged from the hallway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up, Amy?” Sam asked pointedly. The teen’s face flashed surprise and guilt before settling into carefully nonchalant expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh… I’m, uh, just going to the bathroom.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh.” Sam was now pretty sure the sound she’d heard a few minutes ago was one of the boys going to the bathroom. And suddenly, here was Amy trying to sneak across to the same bathroom. “Any reason you can’t use the one by your room?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh…” Amy tugged nervously at her blonde hair. “I left my… hairbrush in the other bathroom?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam tried to share a “can you believe this?” look with Jake, but he had a pillow covering his lap and was pointedly pretending to be absorbed in the TV show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’m pretty sure someone’s in there right now. I think your hairbrush can wait for morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, uh… sure, that makes sense.” Amy hesitated, clearly trying to think of another reason, but finally turned around and walked back to the other bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam laughed and slid back over to Jake. “Kids these days, right? Always trying to sneak around and hook up.” She made a point of lifting the pillow from his lap to reveal the erection tenting his jeans. “Anyway… whatcha hiding under here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you know, I’m just…” Jake trailed off as she started to rub along the length of his shaft. Before long he was breathing heavily and moving his hips to press against her hand. She leaned in and nibbled on his earlobe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Your pants seem very… constraining,” she whispered. “If you pull up that blanket, maybe we could do something about that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wasted no time pulling the blanket up and spreading it over their laps. Sam leaned forward to kiss him as he fumbled with his belt and unbuttoned his pants. He reclined as she slowly, teasingly, moved her hand down his stomach and under the waistband of his boxers. His cock twitched as she wrapped her fingers around it, squeezing gently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He made the cutest little grunting moans as she started slowly stroking. “Shhh,” she breathed in his ear. “Don’t let the kids hear you.” He nodded and bit his lip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She loved the way he responded to her touch. She pressed her breasts against his arm and enjoyed the growing heat between her thighs. After a few minutes, she rubbed around the rim of his head and against his tip. She shivered with anticipation when she found a drop of precum and eagerly withdrew her hand to lick her thumb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He responded to this sight by growling and rolling towards her. His hands closed roughly around her tits and his thumbs teased her nipples. She laughed and pushed him away, so she could finish unbuttoning her shirt. He watched hungrily as she opened it to reveal her favorite lacy lavender bra. Thankfully it hooked in the front, so she could keep her shirt on in case they were interrupted again. She gestured for him to pull the blanket higher as she undid the clasp and pulled the cups aside. In one smooth movement, she fell back against the cushion as he pulled the blanket up over his head and dove toward her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now it was her turn to try not to make any noise. His lips closed over her nipple and she felt his tongue trace increasingly tight circles. She squirmed lower, squeezing her legs together and running her fingers along his spine. He was kneeling on the couch next to her, and she was pretty sure the hand that wasn’t on her chest was stroking his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She heard a door down the hall towards the boys’ room, and adjusted the blanket to make sure Jake was fully covered if someone walked in. Thankfully no one did, and she realized it was probably the poor guy who was planning to meet Amy, going to bed with blue balls. She felt momentarily guilty, but then Jake switched to her other nipple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her heart was racing and there was a growing need between her thighs. She reached under the blanket to undo her pants, then felt blindly for Jake’s hand. Sure enough, she found it wrapped around his cock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I need your fingers now,” she murmured. He continued sucking on her nipple, but allowed her to pull his wrist toward her hips. He teased along the lace trim of her panties before reaching under and down. She spread her legs wide and shivered in anticipation as he brushed past her trimmed hair toward her cleft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He fumbled a bit clumsily, exploring her folds until he finally found her wetness. She stifled a moan as he slipped a finger in and then slowly pulled it back up to her clit, coating it in her juices. His fingers roamed along her sensitive lips, up and down, in and out. Every time he pushed inside, it put pressure on her clit, and soon she was panting with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She groped under the blanket until she found his cock, and gripped it tightly. He grunted in surprise and sucked harder, his tongue flicking against her nipple. She purred and began rubbing the length of him. He pushed his finger deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was another door noise, coming from the other bathroom. This time Jake spoke up, before Amy tried to sneak past them again. He released Sam’s breast only long enough to bark “Go back to bed!” before sloppily licking around her now-puckered areola and pulling her nipple back into his mouth. The footsteps in the hallway receded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam squirmed, feeling her clit stiffen under his palm and her insides clench around his finger. His cock throbbed in her hand, and she felt flushed as lust flooded her system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“More,” she gasped. Without hesitating, he added a second finger, pushing deep inside, reaching a spot that made colored lights flare behind her eyelids. She felt the pressure begin to build, and started rocking her hips with his movements. It felt like electricity was dancing along her spine, sparking between everywhere he touched her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But before she could build to a satisfying climax, there was a muffled thump from down the left-hand hallway, followed by the sound of giggling and shushing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sighing heavily, Sam reluctantly pushed Jake away and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You got this?” He rolled onto his back and tucked his erection back into his boxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” she said as she re-hooked her bra and zipped up her pants. “Sounds like some of the girls are still up. I’ll go tell them to go to sleep.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t be long,” he grinned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She blew him a kiss and walked down the hall, buttoning her shirt. The giggling had stopped, so she paused at the first door to listen. This was the room Amy and Bonnie were sharing. For a moment, she heard nothing, but then muffled voices. She sighed. Probably they were sitting up gossiping about Amy’s foiled attempt to get lucky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She knocked, and waited, grinning, as she heard the frantic sound of one of the girls jumping back into her bed. After a moment, she opened the door. The room was dark except for a bit of moonlight spilling in the window. She could barely see each girl was back in their beds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Girls, I know you’re excited but you’ve got to go to sleep. I need you up and ready to rock first thing in the morning, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An awkward moment passed, making Sam worried the girls were going to push back, but then she heard some mumbled agreements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Alright. Get some good rest.” She closed the door and turned around. In the dim light from the common room, she noticed with a start that her clothes were in disarray. She’d been in such a hurry she hadn’t noticed her shirt buttons were off by one. She also hadn’t taken a moment to adjust her bra, so her nipples were poking in different directions like her boobs were cross-eyed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her cheeks flushed, like a teenager who’d been caught fooling around by her mother. Thank goodness it had been so dark. The kids hadn’t seemed to notice her disheveled, clearly aroused state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a moment, she considered going back to Jake and telling him they had to stop. This wasn’t professional behavior. If they were caught, they’d probably both be fired. They could fool around again when they got home, but for now, the smart thing would be to catch their breath and try to get some sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when she walked back into the common area she forgot everything. Jake was slouched low on the couch. The blanket was pulled up, so she couldn’t see it, but it was clear he was touching himself. His arm moved rhythmically under the blanket, and he was breathing heavily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam stood in the hall and watched for a minute. It was hot, knowing he was worked up because of her. She wondered if he was imagining her tits in his face. She squeezed her legs together, enjoying the pressure on her slick, puffy lips. One hand idly cupped her breast, teasing her nipple until she shivered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she moved, he started, and looked quickly in her direction. When he caught her eye and knew it was just her, he didn’t stop. She bit her lip and let him see her move her hand down her body to press between her legs. He gestured with his chin for her to come back, and she sauntered closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He watched, still stroking, as she rummaged in her bag and pulled out her pajamas. She put a finger to her lips and stood in front of him, seductively unbuttoning her top. His eyes were locked on her chest as she let the shirt drop to the floor and slowly unhooked her bra. She shrugged the straps from her shoulders and let it fall down, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For just a moment, she stood there, topless, letting him admire her before pulling on her pajama shirt. It was a rather thin deep-cut v-neck that did absolutely nothing to conceal her nipples. From the way his hand continued to move under the blanket, he didn’t seem to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gestured for him to move aside, and fell heavily onto the couch next to him. His hungry gaze followed her as she slowly unzipped her pants again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jake,” she said quietly, “will you help me take off my pants?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wasted no time dropping to his knees before her. She scooted lower and lifted her butt to help him shimmy her pants and panties down over her hips. His erection bobbed between his legs, a wet smear of precum coating the tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam enjoyed the look of uncertainty on his face. She could tell that he desperately wanted more. But she could also tell that if she asked for her pajama pants now, he’d respect that and not try to push her to go further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she parted her legs, wanting him to see that she was just as aroused as him. He watched, hungrily, as she reached down to spread herself open. His attention left her feeling equal parts vulnerable and worshipped. The air felt cool on the wetness coating her engorged lips. Her clit thrummed pleasantly in her hood, eager for more stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now,” she said, voice husky with desire, “will you finish what you started?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake answered by moving closer, pulling the blanket up over his head. It fell around her waist as he buried his face between her thighs. She tried not to squeal as he ran his tongue up the length of her, teasing her clit before circling back down to dip between her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam mentally sent thanks to whatever blessed woman had taught him how to eat pussy. She felt her juices flowing, coating his face as his tongue probed deeper. She wrapped a hand around the back of his head, over the blanket, pressing him more firmly against her. Then she let him go, worried it would look too obvious if another student wandered into the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He shifted higher, tongue flicking as his lips closed around her clit. She gasped as he pushed two fingers deep inside, curling upward to stroke her g-spot. He alternated between suction and pressure, expertly driving her toward the orgasm she felt building deep in her pelvis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giving up any pretense at subtlety, Sam was gasping and squeezing her tits. Jake’s head bobbed rhythmically under the blanket as she rocked her hips, grinding against his face. His tongue strummed against her clit, the sensitive bud seeming to grow in the heat of his mouth. Her pussy was clenching, contracting around his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck!” She struggled to keep her voice at a whisper. “Oh god, Jake, you’re making me cum, keep doing that!” The pressure was building. When she pulled on her nipples, little bolts of lightning arced through her core. Behind her closed eyes, colors flared, yellows and reds, like fireworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, release flooded through her system. Her entire body rocked sympathetically to the pulsing in her pelvis, her entire world contracting down to the stimulation between her thighs. Jake made a startled sound, then moved lower, licking all around her lips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gradually, her body relaxed, melting against the couch cushions, hands falling from her breasts. Jake patiently waited for her heart rate to slow before withdrawing. She watched, breathlessly, as he emerged from under the blanket, licking her cream from his fingers and looking pleased with himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam couldn’t help but notice his left hand was still wrapped around his cock, which looked stiffer than ever. He saw her looking and grinned, getting to his feet to stand over her, offering a hand. She let him pull her back to a sitting position, ending with his swollen head bobbing before her face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without hesitating, she wrapped her lips around it and gave him one deep, passionate suck, just long enough to make him gasp. Then she pulled away, releasing him with a wet slurp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now, sit down before someone sees you!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake grinned and traded places with her, falling onto the couch as she dropped to her knees. He grabbed the blanket and parachuted it over her as she moved between his legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cock twitched excitedly as she wrapped her hand around the base and took him back in her mouth. He was already rock-hard, and she knew he wouldn’t last long. As she began moving her head to take him deeper, she rubbed her clit with her left hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She felt his cock in the back of her mouth and tried to relax her throat. He throbbed and she tasted a sudden squirt of precum. Her fingers moved faster, tracing small tight circles that pulled her hood back, allowing even more intense stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck, his cock felt good in her mouth. She pushed as deep as she could go, and then pulled him out before she started gagging. His hand rested on top of her head, not pushing, but encouraging. She began bobbing her head, fucking him with her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, she reached lower, thrusting her fingers between her dripping wet lips. Imagining jumping up onto the couch to straddle him. His cock filling her pussy the way it filled her mouth. He thrust his hips forward, pushing deeper. She moaned and felt a hot gush around her fingers as she came again. When she pulled up off his cock, gasping for breath, he groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sam, will you use your tits?” His breathing was ragged, and she could tell he was nearing his climax. She grinned. Jake loved her breasts, and it wasn’t the first time he’d asked to fuck them. It didn’t do much for her, but she loved how much it turned him on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, she pulled up the hem of her shirt and moved forward to position his cock against her chest. He inhaled shakily as she squeezed her tits around him. Still sloppy and wet from her blowjob, his shaft glided effortlessly against her skin. She watched down her v-neck as he started thrusting his hips forward, the tip of his cock appearing and disappearing from her cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh god… Sam… I’m about to…” His voice trailed off, but she already knew. His cock was swelling and starting to twitch. She was ready. Quickly, she pulled him out of her shirt and back into her mouth. He moaned and thrust deep, pumping cum down her throat. She swallowed and made encouraging sounds, savoring the way he throbbed against the length of her tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gradually, his muscles unclenched. She continued gently sucking as she eased back, until just the tip of his cock rested between her lips. She milked the last few spurts of cum from him until he shuddered from overstimulation and pulled away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smiling happily, she rocked back on her haunches, allowing the blanket to fall around her shoulders. Her fingers continued to lazily curl in and out of her pussy, coated in her cream. She felt deliciously satiated. At last, she pulled her fingers out and leaned forward to press them to his lips. His eyes were closed, but he enthusiastically licked and sucked each digit clean. His cock had softened and lay against his belly, glistening wet. She gave it one last kiss, causing him to shiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then she gathered the blanket around her hips like a towel, picked up her pajama pants from the floor and walked to the bathroom to clean up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she returned, Jake had changed into his pajamas and was pulling the hide-a-bed open. Before long they were snuggling cozily together under the blanket, watching Conan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She thought he had fallen asleep. His arm was wrapped around her, cupping her breast, and he was breathing slowly against the back of her neck. She was starting to doze off when he quietly spoke:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sam, I really like you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm,” she smiled and wriggled against him. “I like you too, Jake.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What if we, uh,” he hesitated, choosing his words carefully. “What if we liked each other more… openly?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Are you asking me out, Jake?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That depends.” She could feel him smile as he replied. “Would you say yes?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I don’t know. Where would you take me for our first date?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I heard they have a pretty good cafeteria here on campus. There’s a Subway AND a Taco Bell!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I gotta be honest with you,” she laughed, “I’ve had better offers. Where would we go after this unforgettable meal?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, we could catch a movie? Something loud and action-packed. Oh, and you should know I always sit in the front row, so I don’t miss anything.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is a mystery to me why you’re still single.” She laughed and reached back to swat his butt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I give up,” he chuckled. “What can I do to convince you to give me a shot?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She rolled over and kissed him, long and slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you start by coming over to my place after the trip is over. You can make me that Fettuccini Alfredo I like. Then later, you can do that thing with your fingers I like. And depending on how well you do, I’ll consider how big a dealbreaker your many serious character flaws are in a life partner.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s a generous offer.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have no idea,” she laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They kissed a while longer, then she rested her head on his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, Jake?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I really like you, too.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>Rainy Day at the Shop</title>
		<link href="https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/rainy-day-at-the-shop/"/>
		<published>2020-02-01T00:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2020-02-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://rubypinkromance.com/shorts/rainy-day-at-the-shop/</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ruby Pink</name>
    </author>
    <category term="shorts" />
    <category term="pubs" />
    <category term="quickie sex" />
    <category term="blowjob" />
    <category term="cunnilingus" />
    <category term="fingering" />
    <category term="coworkers" />
    <category term="store" />
    <category term="dressing room" />
    <category term="public" />
		<content type="html">
      &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://rubypinkromance.com/images/rainy-day-at-the-shop-K_uBbDhvoA-512w.jpeg&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It was a slow day at the shop. Rain lashed against the front windows. Alice sighed and stretched. She and Liam had already done all the folding, facing, sweeping, and other make-work jobs in the vintage clothing store. No customers were coming in at two in the afternoon in this kind of weather. She was bored, and the chill music that the owner insisted they play wasn’t helping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She drummed her fingers on the counter and watched as Liam puttered with the front window display. He was cute, in a generic sort of way. They’d hooked up once at her roommate Julie’s birthday party a few weeks ago. Julie had insisted on inviting Liam because she had a crush on his friend. When the boys arrived at the party, it wasn’t long before the friend and Julie disappeared into her room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam had chatted Alice up in the kitchen. A few beers later they moved to the couch. And a few beers after that, they moved to her bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things had been a bit awkward at work until he figured out she wasn’t expecting him to ask her out or anything. After that, there was a fun layer of workplace flirting whenever they picked up a shift together. She wasn’t sure if anything more would come of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He bent over to pick something up and she grinned crookedly. He &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; have a nice ass, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam, I’m going to the bathroom, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yep,” he replied without looking up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she lifted her skirt and pulled down her underwear, she wasn’t surprised to find a creamy, sticky spot on the gusset. It was the time of the month when she felt wet all day and found herself prowling for someone to make out with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She bit her lip as she remembered falling onto the bed with Liam. He was a good kisser, if a bit sloppy. She’d appreciated the fact that he didn’t push her head down when she undid his belt. When she’d climbed on top of him, he’d sucked on her tits hard enough to leave a hickey the next day. She remembered squeezing her thighs around him as she came, and then rolling over to let him cum on her chest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wondered what it’d be like to hook up with him sober…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of pulling her underwear back on, she slipped them off and tucked them into her purse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strolling back to the counter, she assessed Liam for another few moments before she made up her mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Liam, come back here for a second.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m bored. Just do it, dummy.” She rolled her eyes. Guys were so dense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam put down the shirt he’d been folding for the fourth time and joined her behind the counter. If he noticed the hunger in her eyes, he didn’t show it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s up, Alice?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of answering, she stepped closer and kissed him. He seemed surprised but didn’t pull away. She pressed her body against his, letting him feel her tits against his chest. Then she reached between them to unbutton his jeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What are you… oh!” He stammered, unsure how to react as she pulled out his cock and dropped to her knees. She pressed her back against the cabinet doors below the counter and pulled him toward her. He followed her lead, standing with one leg on either side of her, facing the window with his elbows on the counter. It was tall enough that anyone walking past the shop would only see a bored clerk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice’s heart was pounding with excitement. She wrapped her lips around his head and pulled him into her mouth. He gasped at the sensation and quickly began to stiffen against her tongue. Before long he was fully erect, and she was bobbing her head, seeing how deep she could take him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His breathing was already ragged, and he was starting to push his hips forward. Every time he bumped against the back of her throat she felt her pussy clench, as though it was jealous. This was getting her so hot. She reached under her skirt to touch herself, finding her lips already slick with her juices. She dipped one finger inside, then pressed it to her clit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked up to see him trying desperately to &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; look like a guy getting a blowjob. He had a pained expression on his face, and his gaze was fixed in the middle distance. Her finger flicked faster as he began thrusting in earnest, fucking her mouth. She moaned when she tasted a spurt of precum, and did her best to relax her throat so she wouldn’t gag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she felt him starting to tense up, she pushed him away. He groaned and withdrew with obvious reluctance. She wiped the wetness from her mouth and grinned wolfishly as she stood up. Slowly, teasingly, she lifted her skirt to let him see the wetness dripping down her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My turn,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam goggled at the sight, and quickly traded places with her, dropping to his knees against the counter. Grinning, she straddled him, positioning her pussy over his mouth. He laughed when she released the hem of her skirt, letting it fall over his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then it was her turn to try and lean against the counter and pretend she wasn’t getting head. She bit her lip as he licked the length of her slit, exploring her folds and teasing her by dipping inside. She gripped the counter with white knuckles, imagining the taste of her cream filling his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly, she started rolling her hips, grinding against his face. Her lips slid easily over his own, and she knew she was coating his face with her juices. His tongue never stopped moving, dancing against her opening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A woman with an umbrella walked past the window, stopping for a moment to peer inside. She felt her pussy flutter, inner walls clenching, trying to seize the probing intruder and pull him deeper. She needed more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Use your fingers,” she whispered as she smiled and waved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The woman nodded and walked away, and Alice tried not to react as his thick fingers entered her. She was so wet that he slipped in with no resistance, but once inside, her pussy walls gripped him tightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He gave her a moment to adjust before starting to slide in and out. She let out a low groan at the sensation, which turned to a squeal as she felt his mouth close around her clit. She tried to play it cool, keeping her eyes fixed on the traffic outside, but her insides were already starting to clench.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her legs tensed, and she gripped the counter tightly as his fingers thrust into her and his tongue danced over her clit. Anyone who walked by now would be unable to mistake the shameless way she was bucking her hips, but there was no resisting the climax rising inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh fuck, don’t stop!” she gasped as she felt a flood of relief. Liam made a surprised noise from between her thighs. She kept grinding against him until the stimulation became too much. Quickly, she stepped back, coming to rest against the wall with shaking knees. Her pussy throbbed and clenched in a way that let her know she wasn’t done yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Holy shit,” Liam laughed as he stood up, swallowing and wiping an astonishing amount of her juices from his chin. “I think you squirted on me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of answering, she just rubbed his still-hard cock through his boxers. He moaned happily as she leaned in to kiss him, and then whispered in his ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I need you inside me right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He looked confused, so she grabbed his hand and pulled him toward the dressing room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But what if someone comes in?” He worried as she pulled the curtain shut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ll hear them,” she answered, not caring at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She pulled her skirt up and turned away from him, bending forward to put her hands on either side of the mirror on the wall. She watched him drop his pants around his knees and step forward, stroking his cock. A shiver rolled down her spine as he rubbed the head between her lips, coating himself in her creamy lube.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Fuck me, Liam,” she gasped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wasted no time, gripping her hips tightly and pushing forward. She moaned as his cock slipped deep inside, savoring the way he filled her. She pushed back against him, and he began to thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They quickly fell into a rhythm. She watched his face as he fucked her, his eyes screwed shut in a look of nearly overwhelmed pleasure. He wouldn’t last long, not in the state she’d left him in. But fast and hard suited her fine at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tried to reach around to rub her clit, but she swatted his hand away, too sensitive for a direct touch. Undaunted, he reached up her shirt to squeeze her breast, pinching her nipple through her bra. That sent sparks rolling down her spine, and she felt another gush of fluid run down her thighs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh my god,” He managed to gasp as she clenched around him. “Where… where do you want me to cum?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmm… In my mouth, baby,” she purred. “Cum in my mouth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within seconds he groaned and pulled out, hand already wrapped around his cock and pumping. She dropped to her knees, making encouraging noises, licking and kissing the tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m cumming!” He gasped, at the same moment the door chimed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam was in no position to stop. His cock was already throbbing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll… ah! I’ll be right out!” She called, as the first hot rope of cum splashed across her cheek. She frantically wrapped her lips around his head, sucking and swallowing as his cum flooded her mouth. Her heart was pounding so fast, and she felt a confusing mix of emotions: Arousal and shame, embarrassment and pride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam twitched and gasped as quietly as he could before finally collapsing onto the bench.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice looked in the mirror and quickly cleaned herself up. She wiped the cum from her cheek, then licked it off her fingers, since she had nowhere else to put it. Grinning at her reflection, she left the dressing room, pulling the curtain closed behind her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hello!” An older woman was waiting behind the counter, holding a dripping umbrella. “I’m just here to get a gift card for my daughter. She loves this shop.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’d be happy to help you with that,” Alice replied, coming around to the register. She hoped she didn’t look as flushed and obvious as she felt, but the woman was perfectly sweet as she rung her up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you so much,” the woman said as Alice handed her the gift card. She hesitated for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry, but you missed a spot just there,” she whispered conspiratorially, pointing to Alice’s cleavage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mortified, Alice’s hand flew to her chest, finding a sticky bit of cum that she hadn’t noticed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry, dear, it happens to the best of us,” the woman winked. “Have a nice day!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She smiled cheerfully and walked out of the shop as Alice turned bright red.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liam poked his head out from behind the curtain when he heard the door close. He was still buttoning his jeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Is she gone?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Alice shook her head to clear her shock. “Oh, yeah, you can come out now.” She started digging for the package of wet wipes in her purse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Jeez, that was close, huh?” He chuckled and smacked her ass as he walked past her toward the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh no, you don’t!” She protested, grabbing his arm and spinning him around. “I get to clean up first, you left me literally &lt;em&gt;dripping&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, what am I supposed to do?” He groused, half-jokingly. “You creamed all over me!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, I did.” She gave him a quick kiss. “And if you mop the floor before it gets sticky I might do it again sometime.”&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
	</entry>
</feed>
